<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eternal thought on MyNovel - A Chinese Internet Literature World</title>
    <link>http://www.mynovel.top/tags/eternal-thought/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Eternal thought on MyNovel - A Chinese Internet Literature World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:57:24 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.mynovel.top/tags/eternal-thought/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 47 Xiaochun&#39;s coming out</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-47-xiaochuns-coming-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:57:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-47-xiaochuns-coming-out/</guid>
      <description>In the morning, when the first ray of sunlight fell, Bai Xiaochun felt the vibration of his identity token. Standing outside his yard, he looked back at his house, which had lived for more than two years, and sighed.
&amp;ldquo;You must be careful during this trip. You can&amp;rsquo;t lose your life&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; Bai Xiaochun put on seven or eight leather clothes and carried Zhang Da Pang&amp;rsquo;s black pot on his back. He was thin and small, but now he looks like a ball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 46 tasks of law enforcement hall!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-46-tasks-of-law-enforcement-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:57:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-46-tasks-of-law-enforcement-hall/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
The token is dark, but in the middle of the token, there is a raised word &amp;ldquo;Fa&amp;rdquo;. When you look at it, you can&amp;rsquo;t help but feel a sense of awe.
While Bai Xiaochun was stunned, a cold voice came out of the token and reverberated throughout the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 45 it&#39;s not hard to kill you!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-45-its-not-hard-to-kill-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:57:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-45-its-not-hard-to-kill-you/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun is short of breath. He has already forgotten himself. He has not considered his success several times, nor paid attention to the result of this assessment. His eyes are full of bloodshot. At the moment, there is only one thing he can think about, that is, how to make himself fully confident when he turns on the furnace next time.
If you are not sure, never open the furnace!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 44 it&#39;s morning</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-44-its-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:56:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-44-its-morning/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
After studying the last plant and solving the most difficult problem, he didn&amp;rsquo;t pay attention to the cheers of the people around him. From the moment he picked up the prescription of the jade slips, he was immersed in the herbs, and the whole person was in a state of selflessness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 43 is very slow Very slow</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-43-is-very-slow-very-slow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:56:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-43-is-very-slow-very-slow/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Is it He&amp;rsquo;s the little tortoise There was an uproar.
Compared with all the people, the most shocking thing here is Xu Baocai. He looks at Bai Xiaochun and feels that his eyes will come out. Just now, he despises Bai Xiaochun and doesn&amp;rsquo;t take the three chapters of spirit and beast seriously. At this moment, Bai Xiaochun should not be taken seriously
&amp;ldquo;Great success of plants and animals Bai Xiaochun here, he just clearly is teasing me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 42 promotion assessment</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-42-promotion-assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:56:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-42-promotion-assessment/</guid>
      <description>On the south side of Xiangyun mountain, the pharmacist&amp;rsquo;s Pavilion is surrounded by green trees and a winding blue stone road, which connects with the main road of Xiangyun mountain. When there is no promotion assessment in this area, almost no one comes here. Only when there is a promotion assessment, can there be a large number of visitors.
In addition to the students to be assessed, most of them are friends of these people, or those who want to participate but feel uncertain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 41 the effect of soul refining</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-41-the-effect-of-soul-refining/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:56:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-41-the-effect-of-soul-refining/</guid>
      <description>There are no mice in Xiangyun mountain. The rats can&amp;rsquo;t exist unless they are spirit animals. However, there are many ants in the mountains.
These ants are natural things, usually in the cracks of some rocks, they will not be boring, as if they are part of the mountain, so no one cares.
But today, around the alchemy Pavilion, the disciple who was guarding there suddenly stood up. In an instant, he found that countless ants appeared on the ground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 40 pursuit of perfection</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-40-pursuit-of-perfection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:55:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-40-pursuit-of-perfection/</guid>
      <description>Humming a little song, Bai Xiaochun is very happy to step into the door, back to the yard, he also sighed.
&amp;ldquo;The purpose of cultivating immortals is to live forever. These people are always fighting and killing, and they have brain problems.&amp;rdquo;
In the yard, Bai Xiaochun tidies up the storage bags of Chen Fei and Chen Fei. They are not rich and their pockets are shriveled. Bai Xiaochun does not get much harvest, but he doesn&amp;rsquo;t care too much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 39 rolling</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-39-rolling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:55:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-39-rolling/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Chen Fei?&amp;rdquo; Bai Xiaochun blinked. Her eyes quickly swept over Chen Fei and the two people around him. After realizing their accomplishments, he was determined.
&amp;ldquo;Bai Xiaochun, even if you kneel down to beg for mercy, it&amp;rsquo;s too late. At the beginning, your idea made us become disciples of other schools. I, Chen Fei, have been waiting for this day for a long time.&amp;rdquo; Chen Fei laughs and raises his right hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 38 Ziqi Huading</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-38-ziqi-huading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:55:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-38-ziqi-huading/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun was excited. He got up and moved his body. He also controlled the small wooden sword to fly back and forth in the courtyard. Sometimes he quickly roared away, sometimes he stopped suddenly, which implied a sense of great importance.
The whole wooden sword is unpredictable in this yard, and soon forms bursts of sword spirit. It seems that a strong wind is blowing out of thin air, which makes Bai Xiaochun more excited here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 37 lifting lightly is as important</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-37-lifting-lightly-is-as-important/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:21:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-37-lifting-lightly-is-as-important/</guid>
      <description>Ten steles, first!
Lingxi is located in the three mountains on the south bank, which is a complete sensation.
Inside and outside the Wanyao Pavilion, at this moment, the sound was booming and spread all over the world. Many people came to the Wanyao Pavilion quickly, looking at the ten stone tablets all being the first little tortoise, they took a breath one after another.
&amp;ldquo;Ten steles are the first. The little turtle has really done it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 36 little tortoise dominates!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-36-little-tortoise-dominates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:21:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-36-little-tortoise-dominates/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s desire to build a foundation was aroused by Xu Baocai&amp;rsquo;s words. In the following days, he went to the Sutra Pavilion several times, and even to the Shenwu hall.
In the Shenwu hall, there are many common sense in the Xiuzhen area, and there are also more detailed descriptions about the foundation. When I saw that what was written in it was really similar to what Xu Baocai said, Bai Xiaochun suddenly burst into flames.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 35 see Xu Baocai again</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-35-see-xu-baocai-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:20:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-35-see-xu-baocai-again/</guid>
      <description>[latest broadcast] tomorrow is 515, the start of the anniversary, the most welfare day. In addition to the gift bag and schoolbag, this &amp;ldquo;515 red envelope crazily flipping&amp;rdquo; must see that there is no reason why the red envelope should not be robbed~
Half a month later, Bai Xiaochun finally crushed Du Lingfei in xiaobizhong, which caused quite a stir in the clan.
As a result, every time Bai Xiaochun went out, some other disciples met and said hello with a smile, which made Bai Xiaochun immediately feel that she was also a celebrity, so she liked to go out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 34 rolling of vegetation</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-34-rolling-of-vegetation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:20:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-34-rolling-of-vegetation/</guid>
      <description>[latest broadcast] tomorrow is 515, the start of the anniversary, the most welfare day. In addition to the gift bag and schoolbag, this &amp;ldquo;515 red envelope crazily flipping&amp;rdquo; must see that there is no reason why the red envelope should not be robbed~
Du Lingfei&amp;rsquo;s words made the outside disciples laugh. They didn&amp;rsquo;t believe that Bai Xiaochun could be better than Du Lingfei in this aspect.
In particular, Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s last words, to their ears, are simply impossible, which is clearly in the same blind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 33 defeat Bai Xiaochun!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-33-defeat-bai-xiaochun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:20:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-33-defeat-bai-xiaochun/</guid>
      <description>[broadcast] students who pay attention to &amp;ldquo;starting reading&amp;rdquo; and get the first-hand news of 515 red envelopes can show their skills this time.
Around the outside disciples, as well as those who were eliminated, one by one immediately shared a common hatred against the enemy and roared at Bai Xiaochun.
&amp;ldquo;Shameless, Bai Xiaochun, you are so shameless!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;We won&amp;rsquo;t accept such a victory!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Down with Bai Xiaochun!&amp;rdquo;
Seeing the fierce voice of the crowd, Bai Xiaochun was terrified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 32 luck against heaven</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-32-luck-against-heaven/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:20:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-32-luck-against-heaven/</guid>
      <description>[broadcast] students who pay attention to &amp;ldquo;starting reading&amp;rdquo; and get the first-hand news of 515 red envelopes can show their skills this time.
Not only are the hearts of the people around complicated, even Du Lingfei is jealous of Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s luck. Chen Ziang and others are the same. The four of them have entered the top five, and each battle has its own consumption. If this time, the four of them have got the qualification of being in the air and have a rest, they will certainly have a great advantage in the later battles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 31 shame!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-31-shame/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:19:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-31-shame/</guid>
      <description>The wooden sword of the thin young man set off an extraordinary momentum and turned into a rainbow. He went straight to Bai Xiaochun. But he didn&amp;rsquo;t wait to get close to his body. Outside Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s four feet away, in the thick light of protection, the wooden sword popped back.
Bai Xiaochun in the protection of the light in front of a bright, immediately relieved, dry cough a sound, simply sit cross knee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 30 come on!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-30-come-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:19:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-30-come-on/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Three days later, in the morning.
At the beginning of the day, Bai Xiaochun opened his eyes. He took a deep breath and looked very dignified. It was the first time for him to have a competition with other families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 29 lifting heavy as light</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-29-lifting-heavy-as-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:19:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-29-lifting-heavy-as-light/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Bai Xiaochun tried the degree of protection, immediately laughed, and then looked at his own wooden sword, which he had when he was a beginner. Now, he has experienced two times of soul refining. [love to go to the small</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 28 pressure is the driving force</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-28-pressure-is-the-driving-force/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:19:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-28-pressure-is-the-driving-force/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Bai Xiaochun was also stunned. Looking at the exclamation of people around him, and looking at Zhao Yiduo and Chen Ziang, who were swept away in the distance, it seemed that they did not care about the whole body pain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 25 Immortal iron sheet!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-25-immortal-iron-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:26:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-25-immortal-iron-sheet/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Until a month later, the wind was so tight that even the old lady in Zhang&amp;rsquo;s mouth and Xu Meixiang, the palm of ziding mountain, had heard something about it. Bai Xiaochun and Zhang daphou had to give up and stay in ziding mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 24 who are you</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-24-who-are-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:26:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-24-who-are-you/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
In the courtyard of Xiangyun mountain, Bai Xiaochun looks at the jade pendant in her hand, and her spirit moves. Immediately, the jade pendant emits a soft blue light, covering her whole body.
He pinched the key with his left hand, and immediately the wooden sword flew out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 23 chicken stealing maniac</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-23-chicken-stealing-maniac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:26:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-23-chicken-stealing-maniac/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to present today&amp;rsquo;s update. By the way, I&amp;rsquo;d like to draw a vote for the &amp;ldquo;starting point&amp;rdquo; 515 fan Festival. Everyone has 8 tickets. I&amp;rsquo;d like to give you some money to vote for!
Late at night, Xiangyun mountain is shrouded in darkness, and there is no sign of five fingers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 22 don&#39;t worry, elder martial sister!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-22-dont-worry-elder-martial-sister/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:26:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-22-dont-worry-elder-martial-sister/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to present today&amp;rsquo;s update. By the way, I&amp;rsquo;d like to draw a vote for the &amp;ldquo;starting point&amp;rdquo; 515 fan Festival. Everyone has 8 tickets. I&amp;rsquo;d like to give you some money to vote for!
&amp;ldquo;Look at the second stone tablet, little turtle Reproduction</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 21 brother Xiaochun</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-21-brother-xiaochun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:26:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-21-brother-xiaochun/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to present today&amp;rsquo;s update. By the way, I&amp;rsquo;d like to draw a vote for the &amp;ldquo;starting point&amp;rdquo; 515 fan Festival. Everyone has 8 tickets. I&amp;rsquo;d like to give you some money to vote for!
Wanyao Pavilion is one of the most lively places on Xiangyun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 20 chicken feather</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-20-chicken-feather/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:25:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-20-chicken-feather/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to present today&amp;rsquo;s update. By the way, I&amp;rsquo;d like to draw a vote for the &amp;ldquo;starting point&amp;rdquo; 515 fan Festival. Everyone has 8 tickets. I&amp;rsquo;d like to give you some money to vote for!
The body of Lingwei chicken is much larger than that of ordinary domestic chicken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 19 The Legend of the white rat and Wolf</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-19-the-legend-of-the-white-rat-and-wolf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:25:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-19-the-legend-of-the-white-rat-and-wolf/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to present today&amp;rsquo;s update. By the way, I&amp;rsquo;d like to draw a vote for the &amp;ldquo;starting point&amp;rdquo; 515 fan Festival. Everyone has 8 tickets. I&amp;rsquo;d like to give you some money to vote for!
In Xiangyun mountain, Bai Xiaochun, as a foreign disciple, lived a very moist life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 18 lead the atmosphere!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-18-lead-the-atmosphere/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:25:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-18-lead-the-atmosphere/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
That is the stone tablet of the fourth chapter of the spirit beast. If you calculate it, it can be regarded as the ninth stone tablet. At the moment, the first one on the top has become a treasure vase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 17 little tortoise</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-17-little-tortoise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:04:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-17-little-tortoise/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
The next morning, Bai Xiaochun walked out of the wooden house early. At a glance, he saw that the Lingdong bamboo in the holy field had grown to more than half a person&amp;rsquo;s height. He nodded with satisfaction. Then he walked out of the yard and walked along the mountain road towards the Wanyao Pavilion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 16 meticulous</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-16-meticulous/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:03:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-16-meticulous/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
With this persistence, Bai Xiaochun lies in the yard. Although his body is sour and soft, he can vaguely see that his skin seems to be obviously harder. This scene makes him more eager to become a pharmacist.
After lying in the yard for more than half an hour, Bai Xiaochun immediately got up and sat down on her knees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 15 immortal longevity!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-15-immortal-longevity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:03:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-15-immortal-longevity/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
The moon is bright and falls on Lingxi zongxiangyun mountain, diluting some clouds and fog, making the whole mountain show more than half of the whole mountain, which looks like a unique beauty.
At the east of the mountain, at the end of a forked mountain road, there is a yard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 13 you too!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-13-you-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:03:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-13-you-too/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
The fight between the supervisor&amp;rsquo;s office and the fire stove room has lasted for many years, and there are many frictions between them. However, they all have a good grasp of the yardstick. They will not let things go too far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 12 fence wall</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-12-fence-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:03:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-12-fence-wall/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
This time, the trial of promotion from a mixed servant to a layman was over. As Hou Xiaomei and Hou Xiaomei stepped on the top of the mountain and gradually left, Zhang daphou looked at Hou Xiaomei&amp;rsquo;s back, touched her plump chin, and his face was meaningful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 11 Hou Xiaomei</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-11-hou-xiaomei/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:02:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-11-hou-xiaomei/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
This is the first reaction in his mind after hearing Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s words. However, he hesitated when his eyes fell on the two evil meat mountains behind Bai Xiaochun.
&amp;ldquo;You&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
Bai Xiaochun, with a smile on her face, looks lovely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 10 don&#39;t go, elder martial brother</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-10-dont-go-elder-martial-brother/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:02:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-10-dont-go-elder-martial-brother/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Looking around, several fat elder martial brothers are staring at themselves. The light of the spirit stone seems to flash in those small eyes. Especially when Zhang daphou looks at himself, his eyes are like fire Bai Xiaochun had a dry cough and felt a little proud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 9 longevity pill</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-9-longevity-pill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:02:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-9-longevity-pill/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
A month later, when the cold wind gradually rose and the autumn leaves fluttered down the Tongtian River, Bai Xiaochun suddenly found that he had been here for a year. [love to go to the small
In this year, too many things happened to him, from a mortal to a monk, with the cultivation of three layers of condensation gas, which also resolved a series of disputes caused by becoming a member of the fire kitchen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 8 I&#39;ll fight with you!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-8-ill-fight-with-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:02:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-8-ill-fight-with-you/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Here is the May day update. Don&amp;rsquo;t hurry to play after watching it. Remember to vote for a monthly ticket first. From now on, you can enjoy double monthly tickets at 515 fan Festival. You can also have a look at ang for other activities!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 7 turtle pattern recognition</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-7-turtle-pattern-recognition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:43:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-7-turtle-pattern-recognition/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Here is the May day update. Don&amp;rsquo;t hurry to play after watching it. Remember to vote for a monthly ticket first. From now on, you can enjoy double monthly tickets at 515 fan Festival. You can also have a look at ang for other activities!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 6 Aura</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-6-aura/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:43:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-6-aura/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Here is the May day update. Don&amp;rsquo;t hurry to play after watching it. Remember to vote for a monthly ticket first. From now on, you can enjoy double monthly tickets at 515 fans&amp;rsquo; day. You can also have a look at other activities!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter five what to do if I lose my life</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-five-what-to-do-if-i-lose-my-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:42:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-five-what-to-do-if-i-lose-my-life/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
As soon as the wooden sword fell into the pot, there was no special change. Bai Xiaochun uttered a light cry and opened her eyes unwillingly, staring at the wooden sword carefully.
But after waiting for a long time, nothing strange happened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 4 soul refining</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-4-soul-refining/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:42:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-4-soul-refining/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
When they looked at Bai Xiaochun, they felt that Bai Xiaochun was not only cute, but also had a lot of bad water in his stomach. So Zhang daphou made the decision and rewarded Bai Xiaochun with a grain of LingMi, which was put in Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s hands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter three six true words</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-three-six-true-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:41:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-three-six-true-words/</guid>
      <description>Chapter three
When Bai Xiaochun stretched out her head like this, the young man with yellow complexion and thin immediately saw her, and her eyes fell on her face, and she was furious.
&amp;ldquo;You took my place!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Not me!&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s too late for Bai Xiaochun to shrink her head and pretend to be innocent.
&amp;ldquo;Nonsense, you are so thin and your head is so small, you are definitely NEW!&amp;rdquo; Xu Baocai clenched his fist and glared at Bai Xiaochun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter II fire kitchen</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-ii-fire-kitchen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 11:25:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-ii-fire-kitchen/</guid>
      <description>Chapter two.
Lingxizong, located in donglinzhou, is the downstream branch of Tongtian River. Based on the north and south sides of Tongtian River, lingxizong has a history of ten thousand years and has shocked all quarters.
Eight cloud shrouded Jingtian peaks lie across the Tongtian River, including four on the north bank and three on the south bank. As for the Tongtian River in the middle, there is a most majestic peak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter one his name is Bai Xiaochun</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-one-his-name-is-bai-xiaochun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 11:25:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-one-his-name-is-bai-xiaochun/</guid>
      <description>Maoershan is located in the Donglin mountains. There is a village at the foot of the mountain. The people are simple and live on farming. They are isolated from the world.
In the early morning, in front of the gate of the village, the villagers in the whole village were seeing off a 15-year-old boy. The young man was thin, but white, and looked very clever. Although his clothes were ordinary blue clothes, they were washed white.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>