<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eternal thought on MyNovel - A Chinese Internet Literature World</title>
    <link>http://www.mynovel.top/tags/eternal-thought/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Eternal thought on MyNovel - A Chinese Internet Literature World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:29:05 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.mynovel.top/tags/eternal-thought/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 77 auction</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-77-auction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:29:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-77-auction/</guid>
      <description>Remember the website address; the book path
After a while, on Xiangyun mountain, Bai Xiaochun limped, his head was erect, his face was a little dark, and he crawled back to the yard with fear. At the thought of countless lightning chasing him, he felt a shiver in his heart and immediately swore that he would never fly in thunderstorm days.
It&amp;rsquo;s not flying, it&amp;rsquo;s playing with your life!
In the wooden house, Bai Xiaochun grinned, and it took a long time to settle down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 76 eighth condensate layer!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-76-eighth-condensate-layer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:28:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-76-eighth-condensate-layer/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
At the same time, the foundation building friars of the three mountains were laughing and watching Bai Xiaochun being chased. They knew that Zhou Changlao was just a bluff. But just then, they saw that Bai Xiaochun was fighting against the lightning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 75 I am wronged!!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-75-i-am-wronged/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:28:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-75-i-am-wronged/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
The roar startled the sky and shook. All the trees around him trembled, and many leaves fell down one after another, and a strong wind swept over and rolled up in all directions.
When Bai Xiaochun heard the roar, he almost jumped up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 74 turns out to be Bai Xiaochun!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-74-turns-out-to-be-bai-xiaochun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:28:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-74-turns-out-to-be-bai-xiaochun/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Elder Zhou&amp;rsquo;s voice spread all over Xiangyun mountain and reverberated everywhere. After hearing this, countless disciples looked strange. What happened in Xiangyun mountain that day shocked everyone
The other elders of Xiangyun mountain are also shocking. However, the Phoenix is the favorite of Zhou Changlao, and it is inconvenient for other people to stop it by force.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 73 who did it!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-73-who-did-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:28:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-73-who-did-it/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Bai Xiaochun left Hou Yunfei&amp;rsquo;s residence with emotion and went back to his yard. He looked at the sky and the earth. He first thought about the inheritance sequence, and then thought about those Xiuzhen families. He thought that the leader and elder martial brother were too overbearing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 72 discipline</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-72-discipline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:28:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-72-discipline/</guid>
      <description>A few days later, in the alchemy room where Bai Xiaochun is, a roar comes out, and Bai Xiaochun walks out with a sad face.
&amp;ldquo;The first-class pills are almost skilled, but the second-class pills are so difficult&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; Bai Xiaochun raised his voice in sorrow. During these days, in addition to practicing medicine, he spent almost all the plants in his pocket. He planned to try to make second-order miraculous medicine, but now it is more difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 71 living glory seedling</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-71-living-glory-seedling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:27:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-71-living-glory-seedling/</guid>
      <description>As for soul refining, Bai Xiaochun paid more attention to it because of the turtle shaped pot. He had known for a long time that there was an elder who built foundation on the purple tripod mountain in the zongmen, who was good at refining spirits.
Some disciples of the sect also went to him and asked the elder to help him after paying a certain contribution. Once or twice, the chance of success dropped sharply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 70 Hi, senior brother Li</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-70-hi-senior-brother-li/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:27:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-70-hi-senior-brother-li/</guid>
      <description>Qingfeng mountain near the top of the mountain, there is a separate path, the end of the road, there is a pool, in which there are gold fish swimming.
Beside the water pool is a cave. It has a single door and a single courtyard. It is very quiet and full of aura, far more than other residences.
At the moment, by the pool, a young man was sitting. He was dressed in the long clothes of his disciples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 69 Bai Xiaochun, the little Lord wants you to see him</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-69-bai-xiaochun-the-little-lord-wants-you-to-see-him/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:27:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-69-bai-xiaochun-the-little-lord-wants-you-to-see-him/</guid>
      <description>A month later, all the disciples of ziding mountain are going crazy. This month, Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s appearance has taught them what it means to regard being a martial uncle as a career.
They found that no matter where they were, as long as they were on the purple tripod mountain, they would see a white and clean man with a thin body. His face was full of pride, but he could not hide his pride.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 68 nephews, don&#39;t run!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-68-nephews-dont-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:27:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-68-nephews-dont-run/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun is a person who is very good at finding fun in everything At the moment, he found his pleasure as the leader&amp;rsquo;s younger brother, so he was elated and swaggered along the mountain road of zongmen. From a distance, he saw the mission.
With a dry cough, Bai Xiaochun tidied up her clothes and put on a look of an elder. She raised her chin and slowly approached with her back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 66 for the family to go through fire and water</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-66-for-the-family-to-go-through-fire-and-water/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 18:26:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-66-for-the-family-to-go-through-fire-and-water/</guid>
      <description>In the jungle, as he kept on moving forward, Bai Xiaochun gradually saw some clues. His guess was more certain until he got out of the mountain. A few days later, at this extreme speed, he returned to the Luoxing mountain range and found the Luochen family which had become a ruin.
&amp;ldquo;It seems that Du Lingfei and Hou Yunfei have indeed sent the news back to zongmen.&amp;rdquo; Bai Xiaochun recalled the previous tragic, full of regret, turned for a long time, the wind boat appeared, he jumped up and sat down, control the wind boat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 65 tomb watchers</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-65-tomb-watchers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 18:26:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-65-tomb-watchers/</guid>
      <description>At the moment of sneezing, Bai Xiaochun also woke up, and his consciousness was still immersed in the serious injury state before coma. As soon as he woke up, he subconsciously held his left arm and screamed, but the scream stopped suddenly. He looked down at his left arm in surprise, looked at his body, touched here, touched there, and even lifted his clothes to see himself White and tender stomach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 64 spirit and funeral</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-64-spirit-and-funeral/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 18:26:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-64-spirit-and-funeral/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Spread out and try our best to find Bai Xiaochun. If I find someone, I will reward him for his contribution. If you see any other members of the Luochen family outside, kill them all!&amp;rdquo; Ouyang Jie took back his eyes and looked at Li Qinghou&amp;rsquo;s back. When he opened his mouth slowly, all the disciples around him immediately spread.
Over 2000 people have been searching for it for a month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 63 rolling down the old!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-63-rolling-down-the-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 18:26:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-63-rolling-down-the-old/</guid>
      <description>Li Qinghou was close at the moment. Standing in the array, his look was gloomy and incomparable. The whole person was like a knife out of the body, full of evil spirit.
Ouyang Jie took a look at Li Qinghou, and his eyes narrowed slightly. In the whole south bank and the palm seat of Sanshan mountain, what he cared most about was this Li Qinghou. At the same time, the other party was also the one cared about by the whole Lingxi clan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 62 killing a chicken with a knife!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-62-killing-a-chicken-with-a-knife/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 18:25:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-62-killing-a-chicken-with-a-knife/</guid>
      <description>Unknown mountains, deep in the jungle, thunderstorm from what time, gradually weak, until dusk, the rain stopped, although there is only a dim sunset in the distance, can vaguely see some incomplete rainbow.
It seems that with the setting sun, the rainbow is also gradually fragmented.
It was quiet in the jungle, and even the smell of blood disappeared. Only the corpses along the way witnessed a fierce killing here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 61 a fatal blow!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-61-a-fatal-blow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 18:25:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-61-a-fatal-blow/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s speed is too fast. At the moment, he is surrounded by Chen Heng and does not give him any chance to react. He punches and kicks, forming a strong wind.
Chen Heng&amp;rsquo;s face was unsightly. The light of his whole body was diffused and a large amount of fog was scattered. He and Bai Xiaochun were fighting with each other in the jungle and in the thunder and rain, and a series of roars were heard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 60 battle of life and death</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-60-battle-of-life-and-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 18:25:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-60-battle-of-life-and-death/</guid>
      <description>This scene is too fast. In the room of electric light and flint, three members of the Luochen family with eight layers of gas condensate are killed immediately. The other two breathe. But they have no time to think about it and kill Bai Xiaochun.
White Xiaochun spilled blood from the corner of his mouth, shivered and fell back on the tree behind him. When the long sword in his chest was suddenly knocked out, he grabbed the sword with his right hand, pulled it out suddenly and swept towards one of them with a sword.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 59 life and death!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-59-life-and-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 18:25:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-59-life-and-death/</guid>
      <description>Almost at the moment when Chen Heng&amp;rsquo;s voice came out, Bai Xiaochun, who was nailed to the tree, suddenly raised his head. His eyes showed fierceness. His left hand lifted up, and he grabbed the tail of the arrow outside his right shoulder. Regardless of the barb in his body, he pulled it out.
When a large amount of blood was sprayed out, the arrow was pulled out by him with several pieces of flesh and blood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 58 trapped animals still fight!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-58-trapped-animals-still-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 18:25:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-58-trapped-animals-still-fight/</guid>
      <description>Rain night, thunder roaring, lightning across the sky, so that the sky and earth suddenly bright and dark, loud reverberation, beans big raindrops continue to fall on the earth, issued a loud sound.
From a distance, the whole world is shrouded in the rain, a blur, breeding boundless killing.
On the ground, Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s body trembled and her eyes were red. She was exploding at full speed. Sometimes she stepped on the ground fiercely and suddenly jumped up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 57 we all have to live!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-57-we-all-have-to-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:35:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-57-we-all-have-to-live/</guid>
      <description>With the help of the fire, you can see a big man standing outside the cave.
This big man is very big, holding a long gun, his eyes are cold, and his body is eight layers of condensate gas. He looks more powerful than Chen Yue.
&amp;ldquo;The young Lord has judged correctly. On such a cold and rainy day, you are injured and can&amp;rsquo;t stand the cold. You will surely escape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 56 living together</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-56-living-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:34:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-56-living-together/</guid>
      <description>At this moment, it was the next evening. Bai Xiaochun and Bai Xiaochun ran at a gallop. From time to time, they took out the jade slips and tried. But they could not contact zongmen. Although they were anxious, they had no way.
Fortunately, there are enough pills. There are also some in the storage bags of the seven people killed by Bai Xiaochun. Although they are not as good as Lingxi clan, they are better than none at this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 55 little Lord Chen Heng!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-55-little-lord-chen-heng/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:34:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-55-little-lord-chen-heng/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Purple gas into tripod!&amp;rdquo; Hou Yunfei and Du Lingfei, at the same time, exclaimed. Both of them showed a stronger shock.
Du Lingfei, in particular, has already mastered the difficulty of lifting a heavy vessel like a light, and clearly knows the difficulty of turning the purple gas into a tripod, which is a magic power that few people can master on the south bank, even in the purple tripod mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 54 morality in the heart!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-54-morality-in-the-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:34:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-54-morality-in-the-heart/</guid>
      <description>Seeing that the two clansmen with six layers of condensation gas are about to escape, Bai Xiaochun pinches the formula, and with the whistling of the small wooden sword, she immediately flies across the neck of a six layer condensed gas clansman.
Until death, the eyes of the six layers of condensed gas were filled with unprecedented horror and fear.
They were supposed to be hunters, but now On the contrary, he became the slain!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 53 courage!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-53-courage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:34:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-53-courage/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun was pale and trembling in the bottom of his heart. The sense of crisis that came from all over his body made him tremble constantly.
He had never been so afraid, whether he was lighting incense in the village, hearing thunder, being taken to the ten thousand snake Valley by Li Qinghou in the clan gate, or seeing all kinds of powerful creatures along the way.
In those days, although he was nervous, he knew he was It won&amp;rsquo;t die!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 52 betrayal of Chen</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-52-betrayal-of-chen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:34:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-52-betrayal-of-chen/</guid>
      <description>At the same time, there is a huge underground palace at the bottom of the house where the Luochen family is located. There is a blood lake where countless bones are soaked.
There is a shining array around. Countless people of the Luochen family are kneeling around one by one. Men and women, old and young, are densely packed. The kneeling place of each clan is a node of this array.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 51 elder martial brother Feng is a good man</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-51-elder-martial-brother-feng-is-a-good-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:33:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-51-elder-martial-brother-feng-is-a-good-man/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s scalp was about to explode. His eyes were red and roared. A large number of Rune papers were taken out by him and pressed on his body. The protective light curtain outside his body suddenly increased, which was more than half a foot high.
At the moment when the light curtain appeared, the woman in red suddenly stepped out of the darkness on the side of Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s body and hit the light curtain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 50 weird courtyard</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-50-weird-courtyard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:33:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-50-weird-courtyard/</guid>
      <description>At the moment when the gate of the house opened, Du Lingfei and the three of them looked at it with vigilance. Bai Xiaochun was nervous and took out a large number of runes and pasted them in front of him, making a crackling noise all over his body.
The figure that appeared, holding a lantern in his hand, stood in the open door. His whole body seemed to blend with the darkness and looked at the three people in a secluded way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 49 the Luo Chen family</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-49-the-luo-chen-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:33:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-49-the-luo-chen-family/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Although Feng Yan went out for many missions, he never had one so far away. After seeing the scene behind the scenes, he felt numb, not to mention Du Lingfei.
Fortunately, all the tough creatures we met along the way didn&amp;rsquo;t launch any attacks on them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 48 the world</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-48-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:33:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-48-the-world/</guid>
      <description>One day later, when the first spirit stone in the boat was exhausted, Feng Yan withdrew his sails and the three fell on the top of a mountain. It was dusk. The sun was setting in the distance, and the earth was getting dark.
At the foot of the mountain, the sound of birds and beasts was heard from time to time, and there was a lot of moisture around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 47 Xiaochun&#39;s coming out</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-47-xiaochuns-coming-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:57:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-47-xiaochuns-coming-out/</guid>
      <description>In the morning, when the first ray of sunlight fell, Bai Xiaochun felt the vibration of his identity token. Standing outside his yard, he looked back at his house, which had lived for more than two years, and sighed.
&amp;ldquo;You must be careful during this trip. You can&amp;rsquo;t lose your life&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; Bai Xiaochun put on seven or eight leather clothes and carried Zhang Da Pang&amp;rsquo;s black pot on his back. He was thin and small, but now he looks like a ball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 46 tasks of law enforcement hall!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-46-tasks-of-law-enforcement-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:57:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-46-tasks-of-law-enforcement-hall/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
The token is dark, but in the middle of the token, there is a raised word &amp;ldquo;Fa&amp;rdquo;. When you look at it, you can&amp;rsquo;t help but feel a sense of awe.
While Bai Xiaochun was stunned, a cold voice came out of the token and reverberated throughout the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 45 it&#39;s not hard to kill you!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-45-its-not-hard-to-kill-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:57:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-45-its-not-hard-to-kill-you/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun is short of breath. He has already forgotten himself. He has not considered his success several times, nor paid attention to the result of this assessment. His eyes are full of bloodshot. At the moment, there is only one thing he can think about, that is, how to make himself fully confident when he turns on the furnace next time.
If you are not sure, never open the furnace!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 44 it&#39;s morning</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-44-its-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:56:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-44-its-morning/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
After studying the last plant and solving the most difficult problem, he didn&amp;rsquo;t pay attention to the cheers of the people around him. From the moment he picked up the prescription of the jade slips, he was immersed in the herbs, and the whole person was in a state of selflessness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 43 is very slow Very slow</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-43-is-very-slow-very-slow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:56:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-43-is-very-slow-very-slow/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Is it He&amp;rsquo;s the little tortoise There was an uproar.
Compared with all the people, the most shocking thing here is Xu Baocai. He looks at Bai Xiaochun and feels that his eyes will come out. Just now, he despises Bai Xiaochun and doesn&amp;rsquo;t take the three chapters of spirit and beast seriously. At this moment, Bai Xiaochun should not be taken seriously
&amp;ldquo;Great success of plants and animals Bai Xiaochun here, he just clearly is teasing me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 42 promotion assessment</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-42-promotion-assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:56:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-42-promotion-assessment/</guid>
      <description>On the south side of Xiangyun mountain, the pharmacist&amp;rsquo;s Pavilion is surrounded by green trees and a winding blue stone road, which connects with the main road of Xiangyun mountain. When there is no promotion assessment in this area, almost no one comes here. Only when there is a promotion assessment, can there be a large number of visitors.
In addition to the students to be assessed, most of them are friends of these people, or those who want to participate but feel uncertain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 41 the effect of soul refining</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-41-the-effect-of-soul-refining/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:56:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-41-the-effect-of-soul-refining/</guid>
      <description>There are no mice in Xiangyun mountain. The rats can&amp;rsquo;t exist unless they are spirit animals. However, there are many ants in the mountains.
These ants are natural things, usually in the cracks of some rocks, they will not be boring, as if they are part of the mountain, so no one cares.
But today, around the alchemy Pavilion, the disciple who was guarding there suddenly stood up. In an instant, he found that countless ants appeared on the ground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 40 pursuit of perfection</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-40-pursuit-of-perfection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:55:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-40-pursuit-of-perfection/</guid>
      <description>Humming a little song, Bai Xiaochun is very happy to step into the door, back to the yard, he also sighed.
&amp;ldquo;The purpose of cultivating immortals is to live forever. These people are always fighting and killing, and they have brain problems.&amp;rdquo;
In the yard, Bai Xiaochun tidies up the storage bags of Chen Fei and Chen Fei. They are not rich and their pockets are shriveled. Bai Xiaochun does not get much harvest, but he doesn&amp;rsquo;t care too much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 39 rolling</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-39-rolling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:55:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-39-rolling/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Chen Fei?&amp;rdquo; Bai Xiaochun blinked. Her eyes quickly swept over Chen Fei and the two people around him. After realizing their accomplishments, he was determined.
&amp;ldquo;Bai Xiaochun, even if you kneel down to beg for mercy, it&amp;rsquo;s too late. At the beginning, your idea made us become disciples of other schools. I, Chen Fei, have been waiting for this day for a long time.&amp;rdquo; Chen Fei laughs and raises his right hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 38 Ziqi Huading</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-38-ziqi-huading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:55:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-38-ziqi-huading/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun was excited. He got up and moved his body. He also controlled the small wooden sword to fly back and forth in the courtyard. Sometimes he quickly roared away, sometimes he stopped suddenly, which implied a sense of great importance.
The whole wooden sword is unpredictable in this yard, and soon forms bursts of sword spirit. It seems that a strong wind is blowing out of thin air, which makes Bai Xiaochun more excited here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 37 lifting lightly is as important</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-37-lifting-lightly-is-as-important/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:21:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-37-lifting-lightly-is-as-important/</guid>
      <description>Ten steles, first!
Lingxi is located in the three mountains on the south bank, which is a complete sensation.
Inside and outside the Wanyao Pavilion, at this moment, the sound was booming and spread all over the world. Many people came to the Wanyao Pavilion quickly, looking at the ten stone tablets all being the first little tortoise, they took a breath one after another.
&amp;ldquo;Ten steles are the first. The little turtle has really done it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 36 little tortoise dominates!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-36-little-tortoise-dominates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:21:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-36-little-tortoise-dominates/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s desire to build a foundation was aroused by Xu Baocai&amp;rsquo;s words. In the following days, he went to the Sutra Pavilion several times, and even to the Shenwu hall.
In the Shenwu hall, there are many common sense in the Xiuzhen area, and there are also more detailed descriptions about the foundation. When I saw that what was written in it was really similar to what Xu Baocai said, Bai Xiaochun suddenly burst into flames.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 35 see Xu Baocai again</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-35-see-xu-baocai-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:20:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-35-see-xu-baocai-again/</guid>
      <description>[latest broadcast] tomorrow is 515, the start of the anniversary, the most welfare day. In addition to the gift bag and schoolbag, this &amp;ldquo;515 red envelope crazily flipping&amp;rdquo; must see that there is no reason why the red envelope should not be robbed~
Half a month later, Bai Xiaochun finally crushed Du Lingfei in xiaobizhong, which caused quite a stir in the clan.
As a result, every time Bai Xiaochun went out, some other disciples met and said hello with a smile, which made Bai Xiaochun immediately feel that she was also a celebrity, so she liked to go out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 34 rolling of vegetation</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-34-rolling-of-vegetation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:20:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-34-rolling-of-vegetation/</guid>
      <description>[latest broadcast] tomorrow is 515, the start of the anniversary, the most welfare day. In addition to the gift bag and schoolbag, this &amp;ldquo;515 red envelope crazily flipping&amp;rdquo; must see that there is no reason why the red envelope should not be robbed~
Du Lingfei&amp;rsquo;s words made the outside disciples laugh. They didn&amp;rsquo;t believe that Bai Xiaochun could be better than Du Lingfei in this aspect.
In particular, Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s last words, to their ears, are simply impossible, which is clearly in the same blind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 33 defeat Bai Xiaochun!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-33-defeat-bai-xiaochun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:20:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-33-defeat-bai-xiaochun/</guid>
      <description>[broadcast] students who pay attention to &amp;ldquo;starting reading&amp;rdquo; and get the first-hand news of 515 red envelopes can show their skills this time.
Around the outside disciples, as well as those who were eliminated, one by one immediately shared a common hatred against the enemy and roared at Bai Xiaochun.
&amp;ldquo;Shameless, Bai Xiaochun, you are so shameless!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;We won&amp;rsquo;t accept such a victory!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Down with Bai Xiaochun!&amp;rdquo;
Seeing the fierce voice of the crowd, Bai Xiaochun was terrified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 32 luck against heaven</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-32-luck-against-heaven/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:20:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-32-luck-against-heaven/</guid>
      <description>[broadcast] students who pay attention to &amp;ldquo;starting reading&amp;rdquo; and get the first-hand news of 515 red envelopes can show their skills this time.
Not only are the hearts of the people around complicated, even Du Lingfei is jealous of Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s luck. Chen Ziang and others are the same. The four of them have entered the top five, and each battle has its own consumption. If this time, the four of them have got the qualification of being in the air and have a rest, they will certainly have a great advantage in the later battles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 31 shame!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-31-shame/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:19:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-31-shame/</guid>
      <description>The wooden sword of the thin young man set off an extraordinary momentum and turned into a rainbow. He went straight to Bai Xiaochun. But he didn&amp;rsquo;t wait to get close to his body. Outside Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s four feet away, in the thick light of protection, the wooden sword popped back.
Bai Xiaochun in the protection of the light in front of a bright, immediately relieved, dry cough a sound, simply sit cross knee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 30 come on!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-30-come-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:19:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-30-come-on/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Three days later, in the morning.
At the beginning of the day, Bai Xiaochun opened his eyes. He took a deep breath and looked very dignified. It was the first time for him to have a competition with other families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 29 lifting heavy as light</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-29-lifting-heavy-as-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:19:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-29-lifting-heavy-as-light/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Bai Xiaochun tried the degree of protection, immediately laughed, and then looked at his own wooden sword, which he had when he was a beginner. Now, he has experienced two times of soul refining. [love to go to the small</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 28 pressure is the driving force</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-28-pressure-is-the-driving-force/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:19:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-28-pressure-is-the-driving-force/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Bai Xiaochun was also stunned. Looking at the exclamation of people around him, and looking at Zhao Yiduo and Chen Ziang, who were swept away in the distance, it seemed that they did not care about the whole body pain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 25 Immortal iron sheet!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-25-immortal-iron-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:26:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-25-immortal-iron-sheet/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Until a month later, the wind was so tight that even the old lady in Zhang&amp;rsquo;s mouth and Xu Meixiang, the palm of ziding mountain, had heard something about it. Bai Xiaochun and Zhang daphou had to give up and stay in ziding mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 24 who are you</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-24-who-are-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:26:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-24-who-are-you/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
In the courtyard of Xiangyun mountain, Bai Xiaochun looks at the jade pendant in her hand, and her spirit moves. Immediately, the jade pendant emits a soft blue light, covering her whole body.
He pinched the key with his left hand, and immediately the wooden sword flew out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 23 chicken stealing maniac</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-23-chicken-stealing-maniac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:26:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-23-chicken-stealing-maniac/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to present today&amp;rsquo;s update. By the way, I&amp;rsquo;d like to draw a vote for the &amp;ldquo;starting point&amp;rdquo; 515 fan Festival. Everyone has 8 tickets. I&amp;rsquo;d like to give you some money to vote for!
Late at night, Xiangyun mountain is shrouded in darkness, and there is no sign of five fingers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 22 don&#39;t worry, elder martial sister!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-22-dont-worry-elder-martial-sister/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:26:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-22-dont-worry-elder-martial-sister/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to present today&amp;rsquo;s update. By the way, I&amp;rsquo;d like to draw a vote for the &amp;ldquo;starting point&amp;rdquo; 515 fan Festival. Everyone has 8 tickets. I&amp;rsquo;d like to give you some money to vote for!
&amp;ldquo;Look at the second stone tablet, little turtle Reproduction</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 21 brother Xiaochun</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-21-brother-xiaochun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:26:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-21-brother-xiaochun/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to present today&amp;rsquo;s update. By the way, I&amp;rsquo;d like to draw a vote for the &amp;ldquo;starting point&amp;rdquo; 515 fan Festival. Everyone has 8 tickets. I&amp;rsquo;d like to give you some money to vote for!
Wanyao Pavilion is one of the most lively places on Xiangyun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 20 chicken feather</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-20-chicken-feather/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:25:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-20-chicken-feather/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to present today&amp;rsquo;s update. By the way, I&amp;rsquo;d like to draw a vote for the &amp;ldquo;starting point&amp;rdquo; 515 fan Festival. Everyone has 8 tickets. I&amp;rsquo;d like to give you some money to vote for!
The body of Lingwei chicken is much larger than that of ordinary domestic chicken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 19 The Legend of the white rat and Wolf</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-19-the-legend-of-the-white-rat-and-wolf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:25:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-19-the-legend-of-the-white-rat-and-wolf/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to present today&amp;rsquo;s update. By the way, I&amp;rsquo;d like to draw a vote for the &amp;ldquo;starting point&amp;rdquo; 515 fan Festival. Everyone has 8 tickets. I&amp;rsquo;d like to give you some money to vote for!
In Xiangyun mountain, Bai Xiaochun, as a foreign disciple, lived a very moist life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 18 lead the atmosphere!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-18-lead-the-atmosphere/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:25:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-18-lead-the-atmosphere/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
That is the stone tablet of the fourth chapter of the spirit beast. If you calculate it, it can be regarded as the ninth stone tablet. At the moment, the first one on the top has become a treasure vase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 17 little tortoise</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-17-little-tortoise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:04:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-17-little-tortoise/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
The next morning, Bai Xiaochun walked out of the wooden house early. At a glance, he saw that the Lingdong bamboo in the holy field had grown to more than half a person&amp;rsquo;s height. He nodded with satisfaction. Then he walked out of the yard and walked along the mountain road towards the Wanyao Pavilion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 16 meticulous</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-16-meticulous/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:03:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-16-meticulous/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
With this persistence, Bai Xiaochun lies in the yard. Although his body is sour and soft, he can vaguely see that his skin seems to be obviously harder. This scene makes him more eager to become a pharmacist.
After lying in the yard for more than half an hour, Bai Xiaochun immediately got up and sat down on her knees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 15 immortal longevity!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-15-immortal-longevity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:03:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-15-immortal-longevity/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
The moon is bright and falls on Lingxi zongxiangyun mountain, diluting some clouds and fog, making the whole mountain show more than half of the whole mountain, which looks like a unique beauty.
At the east of the mountain, at the end of a forked mountain road, there is a yard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 13 you too!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-13-you-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:03:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-13-you-too/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
The fight between the supervisor&amp;rsquo;s office and the fire stove room has lasted for many years, and there are many frictions between them. However, they all have a good grasp of the yardstick. They will not let things go too far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 12 fence wall</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-12-fence-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:03:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-12-fence-wall/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
This time, the trial of promotion from a mixed servant to a layman was over. As Hou Xiaomei and Hou Xiaomei stepped on the top of the mountain and gradually left, Zhang daphou looked at Hou Xiaomei&amp;rsquo;s back, touched her plump chin, and his face was meaningful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 11 Hou Xiaomei</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-11-hou-xiaomei/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:02:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-11-hou-xiaomei/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
This is the first reaction in his mind after hearing Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s words. However, he hesitated when his eyes fell on the two evil meat mountains behind Bai Xiaochun.
&amp;ldquo;You&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
Bai Xiaochun, with a smile on her face, looks lovely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 10 don&#39;t go, elder martial brother</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-10-dont-go-elder-martial-brother/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:02:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-10-dont-go-elder-martial-brother/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Looking around, several fat elder martial brothers are staring at themselves. The light of the spirit stone seems to flash in those small eyes. Especially when Zhang daphou looks at himself, his eyes are like fire Bai Xiaochun had a dry cough and felt a little proud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 9 longevity pill</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-9-longevity-pill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:02:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-9-longevity-pill/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
A month later, when the cold wind gradually rose and the autumn leaves fluttered down the Tongtian River, Bai Xiaochun suddenly found that he had been here for a year. [love to go to the small
In this year, too many things happened to him, from a mortal to a monk, with the cultivation of three layers of condensation gas, which also resolved a series of disputes caused by becoming a member of the fire kitchen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 8 I&#39;ll fight with you!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-8-ill-fight-with-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:02:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-8-ill-fight-with-you/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Here is the May day update. Don&amp;rsquo;t hurry to play after watching it. Remember to vote for a monthly ticket first. From now on, you can enjoy double monthly tickets at 515 fan Festival. You can also have a look at ang for other activities!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 7 turtle pattern recognition</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-7-turtle-pattern-recognition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:43:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-7-turtle-pattern-recognition/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Here is the May day update. Don&amp;rsquo;t hurry to play after watching it. Remember to vote for a monthly ticket first. From now on, you can enjoy double monthly tickets at 515 fan Festival. You can also have a look at ang for other activities!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 6 Aura</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-6-aura/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:43:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-6-aura/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Here is the May day update. Don&amp;rsquo;t hurry to play after watching it. Remember to vote for a monthly ticket first. From now on, you can enjoy double monthly tickets at 515 fans&amp;rsquo; day. You can also have a look at other activities!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter five what to do if I lose my life</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-five-what-to-do-if-i-lose-my-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:42:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-five-what-to-do-if-i-lose-my-life/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
As soon as the wooden sword fell into the pot, there was no special change. Bai Xiaochun uttered a light cry and opened her eyes unwillingly, staring at the wooden sword carefully.
But after waiting for a long time, nothing strange happened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 4 soul refining</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-4-soul-refining/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:42:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-4-soul-refining/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
When they looked at Bai Xiaochun, they felt that Bai Xiaochun was not only cute, but also had a lot of bad water in his stomach. So Zhang daphou made the decision and rewarded Bai Xiaochun with a grain of LingMi, which was put in Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s hands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter three six true words</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-three-six-true-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:41:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-three-six-true-words/</guid>
      <description>Chapter three
When Bai Xiaochun stretched out her head like this, the young man with yellow complexion and thin immediately saw her, and her eyes fell on her face, and she was furious.
&amp;ldquo;You took my place!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Not me!&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s too late for Bai Xiaochun to shrink her head and pretend to be innocent.
&amp;ldquo;Nonsense, you are so thin and your head is so small, you are definitely NEW!&amp;rdquo; Xu Baocai clenched his fist and glared at Bai Xiaochun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter II fire kitchen</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-ii-fire-kitchen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 11:25:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-ii-fire-kitchen/</guid>
      <description>Chapter two.
Lingxizong, located in donglinzhou, is the downstream branch of Tongtian River. Based on the north and south sides of Tongtian River, lingxizong has a history of ten thousand years and has shocked all quarters.
Eight cloud shrouded Jingtian peaks lie across the Tongtian River, including four on the north bank and three on the south bank. As for the Tongtian River in the middle, there is a most majestic peak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter one his name is Bai Xiaochun</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-one-his-name-is-bai-xiaochun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 11:25:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-one-his-name-is-bai-xiaochun/</guid>
      <description>Maoershan is located in the Donglin mountains. There is a village at the foot of the mountain. The people are simple and live on farming. They are isolated from the world.
In the early morning, in front of the gate of the village, the villagers in the whole village were seeing off a 15-year-old boy. The young man was thin, but white, and looked very clever. Although his clothes were ordinary blue clothes, they were washed white.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>