<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eternal thought on MyNovel - A Chinese Internet Literature World</title>
    <link>http://www.mynovel.top/tags/eternal-thought/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Eternal thought on MyNovel - A Chinese Internet Literature World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:43:26 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.mynovel.top/tags/eternal-thought/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 7 turtle pattern recognition</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-7-turtle-pattern-recognition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:43:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-7-turtle-pattern-recognition/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Here is the May day update. Don&amp;rsquo;t hurry to play after watching it. Remember to vote for a monthly ticket first. From now on, you can enjoy double monthly tickets at 515 fan Festival. You can also have a look at ang for other activities!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 6 Aura</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-6-aura/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:43:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-6-aura/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Here is the May day update. Don&amp;rsquo;t hurry to play after watching it. Remember to vote for a monthly ticket first. From now on, you can enjoy double monthly tickets at 515 fans&amp;rsquo; day. You can also have a look at other activities!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter five what to do if I lose my life</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-five-what-to-do-if-i-lose-my-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:42:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-five-what-to-do-if-i-lose-my-life/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
As soon as the wooden sword fell into the pot, there was no special change. Bai Xiaochun uttered a light cry and opened her eyes unwillingly, staring at the wooden sword carefully.
But after waiting for a long time, nothing strange happened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 4 soul refining</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-4-soul-refining/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:42:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-4-soul-refining/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
When they looked at Bai Xiaochun, they felt that Bai Xiaochun was not only cute, but also had a lot of bad water in his stomach. So Zhang daphou made the decision and rewarded Bai Xiaochun with a grain of LingMi, which was put in Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s hands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter three six true words</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-three-six-true-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:41:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-three-six-true-words/</guid>
      <description>Chapter three
When Bai Xiaochun stretched out her head like this, the young man with yellow complexion and thin immediately saw her, and her eyes fell on her face, and she was furious.
&amp;ldquo;You took my place!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Not me!&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s too late for Bai Xiaochun to shrink her head and pretend to be innocent.
&amp;ldquo;Nonsense, you are so thin and your head is so small, you are definitely NEW!&amp;rdquo; Xu Baocai clenched his fist and glared at Bai Xiaochun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter II fire kitchen</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-ii-fire-kitchen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 11:25:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-ii-fire-kitchen/</guid>
      <description>Chapter two.
Lingxizong, located in donglinzhou, is the downstream branch of Tongtian River. Based on the north and south sides of Tongtian River, lingxizong has a history of ten thousand years and has shocked all quarters.
Eight cloud shrouded Jingtian peaks lie across the Tongtian River, including four on the north bank and three on the south bank. As for the Tongtian River in the middle, there is a most majestic peak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter one his name is Bai Xiaochun</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-one-his-name-is-bai-xiaochun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 11:25:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-one-his-name-is-bai-xiaochun/</guid>
      <description>Maoershan is located in the Donglin mountains. There is a village at the foot of the mountain. The people are simple and live on farming. They are isolated from the world.
In the early morning, in front of the gate of the village, the villagers in the whole village were seeing off a 15-year-old boy. The young man was thin, but white, and looked very clever. Although his clothes were ordinary blue clothes, they were washed white.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>