<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eternal thought on MyNovel - A Chinese Internet Literature World</title>
    <link>http://www.mynovel.top/tags/eternal-thought/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Eternal thought on MyNovel - A Chinese Internet Literature World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 11:25:50 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.mynovel.top/tags/eternal-thought/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter II fire kitchen</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-ii-fire-kitchen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 11:25:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-ii-fire-kitchen/</guid>
      <description>Chapter two.
Lingxizong, located in donglinzhou, is the downstream branch of Tongtian River. Based on the north and south sides of Tongtian River, lingxizong has a history of ten thousand years and has shocked all quarters.
Eight cloud shrouded Jingtian peaks lie across the Tongtian River, including four on the north bank and three on the south bank. As for the Tongtian River in the middle, there is a most majestic peak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter one his name is Bai Xiaochun</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-one-his-name-is-bai-xiaochun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 11:25:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-one-his-name-is-bai-xiaochun/</guid>
      <description>Maoershan is located in the Donglin mountains. There is a village at the foot of the mountain. The people are simple and live on farming. They are isolated from the world.
In the early morning, in front of the gate of the village, the villagers in the whole village were seeing off a 15-year-old boy. The young man was thin, but white, and looked very clever. Although his clothes were ordinary blue clothes, they were washed white.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>