<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MyNovel - A Chinese Internet Literature World</title>
    <link>http://www.mynovel.top/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MyNovel - A Chinese Internet Literature World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 16:17:49 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.mynovel.top/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 107 Tianlei Lotion</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-107-tianlei-lotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 16:17:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-107-tianlei-lotion/</guid>
      <description>When he returned to Xiangyun mountain, Bai Xiaochun was sad. He didn&amp;rsquo;t dare to continue to test many strange pills left in his storage bag. Especially when he was walking on the road of Xiangyun mountain, all Xiangyun mountain disciples, when they saw themselves, were either eccentric or fierce, and they were angry.
&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s so hard to stick to the great ideal It&amp;rsquo;s not my fault. Uncle Li asked me to study it myself&amp;hellip; &amp;quot; Bai Xiaochun sighed, trotted all the way back to the cave, sat there, looking at the distant sky in a daze.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 106 Crazy Rabbit!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-106-crazy-rabbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 16:17:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-106-crazy-rabbit/</guid>
      <description>At the moment, Xu Baocai and many other disciples are in the process of medicine apprenticeship promotion. Elder Xu is watching. It was a very serious thing, but at this time, a group of birds flew through the sky, and the sound of puff and puff came up and down Innumerable bird droppings fall in an instant, like rain. Xu Baocai, other disciples participating in the promotion, as well as the onlookers around, and even elder Xu&amp;rsquo;s hair, are all bird droppings at the moment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 105 animal escape!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-105-animal-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 16:17:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-105-animal-escape/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun looked at the overwhelming stones, and immediately ran back to the cave. When the cave array shook and blocked tens of thousands of stones, Bai Xiaochun was in tears and knew that he had committed public anger, but he was also wronged. He really didn&amp;rsquo;t mean to.
&amp;ldquo;I promise, this is the last time. I&amp;rsquo;m very sure!&amp;rdquo; He hastened to speak.
After all the people outside expressed their anger, Bai Xiaochun talked about it in the cave, and all the talents left with their anger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 104 I promise</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-104-i-promise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 16:17:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-104-i-promise/</guid>
      <description>With melancholy, Bai Xiaochun went back to the cave, where he sighed and sighed, and finally sighed.
&amp;ldquo;If a person is too good, it&amp;rsquo;s not a good thing. It&amp;rsquo;s just like me. Zongmen are worried that they have exempted me from the task of ten years and give me some contribution every month.&amp;rdquo; Bai xiaochunmei is worried and thinks that she is really excellent. What should I do if she goes on like this</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 103 I want to contribute to the clan!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-103-i-want-to-contribute-to-the-clan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 16:17:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-103-i-want-to-contribute-to-the-clan/</guid>
      <description>In this barren mountain range, there are not many disciples of Lingxi sect. There are about a dozen of them. After all, although there are few ferocious beasts for the inner disciples, there are still some dangers.
Therefore, those who think they are strong will come.
Under the intense call of Bai Xiaochun, all the disciples here heard his voice one after another. Most of them listened to Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s advice and left with the apology and thanks given by Bai Xiaochun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 102 is anybody there</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-102-is-anybody-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 16:16:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-102-is-anybody-there/</guid>
      <description>In a flash of time, in the past few months, Bai Xiaochun was very familiar with the area of Xiangyun mountain&amp;rsquo;s inner disciples, and the freshness of becoming an inner disciple gradually diminished.
Most of them are in the cave. They either practice or refine the elixir in the refining pharmacy. He also refined a lot of oestrus pills.
In such a day, he felt very happy. For him, practice is for long life, so that his cultivation is higher and higher, so as to obtain a longer life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 101 water Kingdom and Yuan Ciyi!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-101-water-kingdom-and-yuan-ciyi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 16:16:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-101-water-kingdom-and-yuan-ciyi/</guid>
      <description>There was a cold hum from the palm seat of sunset peak and a wave of his right sleeve. All the disciples of sunset peak were trembling all over the place. They felt as if the mountains were at the top of the mountain, and they were crying in their hearts.
In particular, the two brothers of beihanlie were under such pressure, their faces were miserable, their accomplishments in their bodies were shaking, and their hearts were more cruel to Bai Xiaochun, but they did not dare to show any.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 100 don&#39;t admit your mistake to your uncle Bai</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-100-dont-admit-your-mistake-to-your-uncle-bai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 16:16:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-100-dont-admit-your-mistake-to-your-uncle-bai/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun is even more aggrieved. He has found that he always makes a fool of himself every time he meets the need to explain.
It&amp;rsquo;s not his intention. He doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to
Beihanlie&amp;rsquo;s elder brother, beihanfeng, was also explained by Bai Xiaochun. After taking a deep breath, his right hand actually appeared bursts of black light at this moment. In the blink of an eye, a black crescent moon appeared in his palm!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 99 come to the door</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-99-come-to-the-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 16:16:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-99-come-to-the-door/</guid>
      <description>Zhou Xinqi looks ugly. She didn&amp;rsquo;t expect that the cave she chose was next to Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s cave. When she was outside, she knew that Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s hobby of calling his uncle was uncomfortable, so she avoided it every time.
But now, it was blocked at the door.
&amp;ldquo;White Uncle Zhou Xinqi took a deep breath. After she spoke lightly, she did not look at Bai Xiaochun. She flew off on the blue silk, and her long skirt danced to set off her beautiful face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 98 the classic of dragon and elephant</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-98-the-classic-of-dragon-and-elephant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 16:15:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-98-the-classic-of-dragon-and-elephant/</guid>
      <description>This battle of arrogance has accomplished Zhang daphou Even when the leader and others looked at Zhang daphou, they were all curious. Especially the leader, he was shocked after a look.
&amp;ldquo;Mindfulness He looked dignified. When he said his words, all the elders and palms around him were shocked. After carefully looking at them, their eyes brightened.
Xu Meixiang took LV Tianlei away to heal her wounds. Otherwise, it would be incredible at the moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 97 I am Zhang daphou!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-97-i-am-zhang-daphou/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 14:43:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-97-i-am-zhang-daphou/</guid>
      <description>At this moment, the disciples around have been buzzing in their minds, staring at the two people on the stage, and everyone&amp;rsquo;s mind has set off a huge wave.
The people on the south bank are in a trance. They finally understand why Bai Xiaochun can survive in the first World War of the Luochen family and why he can be listed as a glorious disciple!
&amp;ldquo;So He&amp;rsquo;s so strong This is the only shock in the heart of every disciple on the south bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 96 battle ghost tooth</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-96-battle-ghost-tooth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 14:42:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-96-battle-ghost-tooth/</guid>
      <description>Nan&amp;rsquo;an is shocked. All the disciples who know Bai Xiaochun seem to have never known him at this moment. At this moment, Bai Xiaochun gives them a very strange feeling, which is totally different from the figure in memory who likes to call him uncle Bai, cheap and always makes people want to beat him up.
There are countless inspirations coming from the north bank. All of them are staring at Bai Xiaochun at this moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 95 sword, not in this way!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-95-sword-not-in-this-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 14:42:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-95-sword-not-in-this-way/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Uncle Bai What a man of God
&amp;ldquo;Uncle Bai, this is the rhythm of going to the end on the road of public enemy on the north bank&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; When people on the south bank looked at Bai Xiaochun one by one, they all showed admiration. They were convinced from the bottom of their hearts.
Even a lot of people are glad that such a disaster as Bai Xiaochun is not from the north bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 94 uncle Bai, we are our own people</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-94-uncle-bai-we-are-our-own-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 14:42:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-94-uncle-bai-we-are-our-own-people/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;This battle of pride Ah On the terrace, the headmaster Zheng Yuandong shook his head helplessly. All the mountain leaders around him laughed bitterly.
They all know that this should be serious Tianjiao battle, now has completely changed the flavor Originally good, because more a white small pure, directly rancid.
&amp;ldquo;Bai Xiaochun His name is very good, but it&amp;rsquo;s not pure at all Zhou Changlao smiles bitterly, looking at Bai Xiaochun hiding in the crowd below, and the countless crazy disciples on the north bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 93 this pill is also useful to people</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-93-this-pill-is-also-useful-to-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 14:42:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-93-this-pill-is-also-useful-to-people/</guid>
      <description>In the second area, the ghost tooth retracts the two fingers that he has stretched out to deal with others. He only needs one finger, but Gongsun Yun in front of him can resist his first finger.
At the moment, Gongsun Yun looks pale, quickly retreats, and bitterly admits defeat. Resistance to the first finger is the limit. He can&amp;rsquo;t be hurt too much. Even if he can&amp;rsquo;t fight for the first, he has to fight for the second.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 92 the despair of Gongsun Waner</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-92-the-despair-of-gongsun-waner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 14:41:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-92-the-despair-of-gongsun-waner/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Too Too strong
&amp;ldquo;This ghost tooth, I&amp;rsquo;m afraid even the inner disciples can crush it directly. It&amp;rsquo;s really the first person to build the foundation!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;The pinnacle of this kind of condensed gas combat power must have touched the realm of mind. It must be so. Only with the mysterious and unpredictable mind can we have this kind of terrifying power!&amp;rdquo; After a brief silence, low voices came out from the south bank and the north bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 91 crazy north shore</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-91-crazy-north-shore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 14:41:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-91-crazy-north-shore/</guid>
      <description>With the end of the first round, we ushered in the rest time of three sticks of incense. At this moment, all the disciples on the north bank were furious, staring at the south bank, staring at Bai Xiaochun!
They are waiting for the second round to start. They want to use all means to defeat Bai Xiaochun. Even if the north bank wins this time, they don&amp;rsquo;t pay attention to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 90 public enemy on the north bank</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-90-public-enemy-on-the-north-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 14:41:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-90-public-enemy-on-the-north-bank/</guid>
      <description>With the departure of beihanlie&amp;rsquo;s master and apprentice, all the disciples on both sides of the battle platform are stunned. They are buzzing in their minds. They don&amp;rsquo;t know what to say. They are full of pictures of the big dog crawling on beihanlie
Not only are they confused at the moment, but even the leaders on the terrace and the heads of the peaks, as well as the elders, are all stupidly looking at the innocent face of Bai Xiaochun on the battle platform below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 89 give up</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-89-give-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 14:41:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-89-give-up/</guid>
      <description>Almost at the moment when Bai Xiaochun looked up, beihanlie, one of the five Tianjiao on the north bank, suddenly gave a smile. He was already handsome. At the moment, such a smile made many of the young disciples on the south bank shine brilliantly.
With a smile on his face, he patted the ferocious and ferocious nocturnal beast lying beside him, and walked forward. The nocturnal beast&amp;rsquo;s head shook, and his eyes showed a dark light, and he stood up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 88 the mighty north bank</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-88-the-mighty-north-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 14:41:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-88-the-mighty-north-bank/</guid>
      <description>Almost at the moment when Zheng Yuandong&amp;rsquo;s words came out, all the disciples on both sides of the Taiwan Strait were shocked and subconsciously looked up at the terrace above.
Almost as soon as they saw it, there were four earthshaking thoughts of divine consciousness, which suddenly appeared from the top of Zhongdao mountain and the snow covered forbidden area, sweeping all the people.
After being swept away by these four divine senses, all the disciples of the outer sect, including Bai Xiaochun, trembled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 87 The Battle of Tianjiao in the outer gate of the north and the South</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-87-the-battle-of-tianjiao-in-the-outer-gate-of-the-north-and-the-south/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 09:39:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-87-the-battle-of-tianjiao-in-the-outer-gate-of-the-north-and-the-south/</guid>
      <description>As time went by, Bai Xiaochun was shut up in his residence and could not get out of the house. Ten days later, when the solemn bell echoed the whole clan gate, waves came from his jade slips.
The Tianjiao battle between the two sides of the Taiwan Strait was officially held on the 10th day after the qualification competition!
Every half of Jiazi&amp;rsquo;s outer gate Tianjiao battle is carried out on Zhongdao mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 86 again</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-86-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 09:39:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-86-again/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun was frightened all the way. He ran down the mountain or even out of the zongmen. He wandered around for a long time in the city outside the Zongshan gate of Lingxi.
&amp;ldquo;What to do.&amp;rdquo; Bai Xiaochun has a sad face. He is deeply aggrieved. When he thinks of it, it is clear that the bird came by himself and took the pill. But now he can&amp;rsquo;t explain it clearly, and elder Zhou is unreasonable</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 85 he is First</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-85-he-is-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 09:38:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-85-he-is-first/</guid>
      <description>Just when Zhou Xinqi was shocked, the wind came again from behind her. Zhou walked with a big stride and a smile on her face. She nodded to Zhou Xinqi when she passed by.
At the same time, with this smile, there was a vicious voice in my mouth.
&amp;ldquo;Bai Xiaochun, I changed my mind again. After catching you, I&amp;rsquo;ll starve for a month, and then I&amp;rsquo;ll lock you up with a group of birds and a large number of fierce animals!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 84 incredible outburst</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-84-incredible-outburst/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 09:38:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-84-incredible-outburst/</guid>
      <description>When Bai Xiaochun heard the roar, he was startled. He turned around and saw elder Zhou, who had rushed to kill him. His eyes suddenly widened, and he only felt that he was out of his wits.
In particular, Zhou Chang was ferocious. Although his words didn&amp;rsquo;t mean Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s life, he could feel the sadness of the Phoenix in person. When Bai Xiaochun thought that the Phoenix had almost all the birds in Xiangyun mountain all day, even the Lingwei chicken, he felt creepy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 83 asking the elder Zhou to come forward</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-83-asking-the-elder-zhou-to-come-forward/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 09:38:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-83-asking-the-elder-zhou-to-come-forward/</guid>
      <description>Not only did Zheng Yuandong notice Bai Xiaochun. After all, other people were in an uproar, but Bai Xiaochun stood beside the statue and posed as an elder. The temperament of the whole person was different, especially obvious.
&amp;ldquo;Bai Xiaochun has also reached the eighth floor of condensate gas, and even died in the first battle of the Luochen family. I think this son must be in the top ten today, and even hope to compete for the top five.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 82 Tianjiao on the south bank</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-82-tianjiao-on-the-south-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 09:38:17 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-82-tianjiao-on-the-south-bank/</guid>
      <description>In the past thousand years, the south bank has always been oppressed by the north bank. Most of the top ten disciples of the outer gate Tianjiao battle are the north bank disciples, which makes the south bank unable to raise its head, let alone the first place. For thousands of years, it has been taken away by the north bank.
Among them, there are four peaks on the north bank and three mountains on the south bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 81 the ancient method of chanting spirits</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-81-the-ancient-method-of-chanting-spirits/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 09:38:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-81-the-ancient-method-of-chanting-spirits/</guid>
      <description>Zhang Dazhou was nervous at the bottom of his heart. After hearing Bai Xiaochun saying that, he felt that there was some reason, so he nodded quickly.
&amp;ldquo;Yes, the master also said, let me not see failure and success. Junior brother nine, please go back to the room and try to be spiritual.&amp;rdquo; Zhang Dazhou coughs, so he said calmly.
Bai Xiaochun turned and walked quickly. After returning to the room, he saw the sword in his hand, frowned, worried about hitting Zhang Dazhou, and did not try it easily, but pinched the key and immediately appeared the tortoise pot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 80 the talent of Zhang daphou</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-80-the-talent-of-zhang-daphou/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 09:37:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-80-the-talent-of-zhang-daphou/</guid>
      <description>With enough spirit stones, Bai Xiaochun doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to think about the little turtle any more. His heart is full of wounds, so he can only be immersed in the medicine refining pavilion to recover slowly.
Gradually, the second-order elixir in Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s hands has been perfect, and the success rate has been raised to an amazing level. Only then did he begin to try to refine the third-order elixir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 79 Xiaochun, we believe it</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-79-xiaochun-we-believe-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 09:37:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-79-xiaochun-we-believe-it/</guid>
      <description>Remember the website address; the book path
Bai Xiaochun suddenly opened her eyes and was full of 3000 spirit stones Looking at Hou Xiaomei, his eyes are shining. At this moment, how much he wants to go up and hold Hou Xiaomei and give her 3000 thumbs
Tell her, you are good!
All the people in the auction house were in a state of uproar at such a high price. After Hou Xiaomei&amp;rsquo;s voice came out, they all stayed for a moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 78 are they talking about me</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-78-are-they-talking-about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 09:37:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-78-are-they-talking-about-me/</guid>
      <description>Remember the website address; the book path
After hearing Qian song&amp;rsquo;s words, all the people in the auction house showed interest and looked at them together.
However, most of the inner disciples who have been trained in the eighth floor of condensate gas pay no attention. Some are talking to each other, while others are keeping their eyes closed.
&amp;ldquo;You can have a look at this pill, and then Qian will tell you the price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 77 auction</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-77-auction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:29:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-77-auction/</guid>
      <description>Remember the website address; the book path
After a while, on Xiangyun mountain, Bai Xiaochun limped, his head was erect, his face was a little dark, and he crawled back to the yard with fear. At the thought of countless lightning chasing him, he felt a shiver in his heart and immediately swore that he would never fly in thunderstorm days.
It&amp;rsquo;s not flying, it&amp;rsquo;s playing with your life!
In the wooden house, Bai Xiaochun grinned, and it took a long time to settle down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 76 eighth condensate layer!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-76-eighth-condensate-layer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:28:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-76-eighth-condensate-layer/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
At the same time, the foundation building friars of the three mountains were laughing and watching Bai Xiaochun being chased. They knew that Zhou Changlao was just a bluff. But just then, they saw that Bai Xiaochun was fighting against the lightning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 75 I am wronged!!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-75-i-am-wronged/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:28:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-75-i-am-wronged/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
The roar startled the sky and shook. All the trees around him trembled, and many leaves fell down one after another, and a strong wind swept over and rolled up in all directions.
When Bai Xiaochun heard the roar, he almost jumped up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 74 turns out to be Bai Xiaochun!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-74-turns-out-to-be-bai-xiaochun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:28:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-74-turns-out-to-be-bai-xiaochun/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Elder Zhou&amp;rsquo;s voice spread all over Xiangyun mountain and reverberated everywhere. After hearing this, countless disciples looked strange. What happened in Xiangyun mountain that day shocked everyone
The other elders of Xiangyun mountain are also shocking. However, the Phoenix is the favorite of Zhou Changlao, and it is inconvenient for other people to stop it by force.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 73 who did it!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-73-who-did-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:28:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-73-who-did-it/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Bai Xiaochun left Hou Yunfei&amp;rsquo;s residence with emotion and went back to his yard. He looked at the sky and the earth. He first thought about the inheritance sequence, and then thought about those Xiuzhen families. He thought that the leader and elder martial brother were too overbearing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 72 discipline</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-72-discipline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:28:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-72-discipline/</guid>
      <description>A few days later, in the alchemy room where Bai Xiaochun is, a roar comes out, and Bai Xiaochun walks out with a sad face.
&amp;ldquo;The first-class pills are almost skilled, but the second-class pills are so difficult&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; Bai Xiaochun raised his voice in sorrow. During these days, in addition to practicing medicine, he spent almost all the plants in his pocket. He planned to try to make second-order miraculous medicine, but now it is more difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 71 living glory seedling</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-71-living-glory-seedling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:27:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-71-living-glory-seedling/</guid>
      <description>As for soul refining, Bai Xiaochun paid more attention to it because of the turtle shaped pot. He had known for a long time that there was an elder who built foundation on the purple tripod mountain in the zongmen, who was good at refining spirits.
Some disciples of the sect also went to him and asked the elder to help him after paying a certain contribution. Once or twice, the chance of success dropped sharply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 70 Hi, senior brother Li</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-70-hi-senior-brother-li/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:27:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-70-hi-senior-brother-li/</guid>
      <description>Qingfeng mountain near the top of the mountain, there is a separate path, the end of the road, there is a pool, in which there are gold fish swimming.
Beside the water pool is a cave. It has a single door and a single courtyard. It is very quiet and full of aura, far more than other residences.
At the moment, by the pool, a young man was sitting. He was dressed in the long clothes of his disciples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 69 Bai Xiaochun, the little Lord wants you to see him</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-69-bai-xiaochun-the-little-lord-wants-you-to-see-him/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:27:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-69-bai-xiaochun-the-little-lord-wants-you-to-see-him/</guid>
      <description>A month later, all the disciples of ziding mountain are going crazy. This month, Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s appearance has taught them what it means to regard being a martial uncle as a career.
They found that no matter where they were, as long as they were on the purple tripod mountain, they would see a white and clean man with a thin body. His face was full of pride, but he could not hide his pride.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 68 nephews, don&#39;t run!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-68-nephews-dont-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 11:27:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-68-nephews-dont-run/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun is a person who is very good at finding fun in everything At the moment, he found his pleasure as the leader&amp;rsquo;s younger brother, so he was elated and swaggered along the mountain road of zongmen. From a distance, he saw the mission.
With a dry cough, Bai Xiaochun tidied up her clothes and put on a look of an elder. She raised her chin and slowly approached with her back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 66 for the family to go through fire and water</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-66-for-the-family-to-go-through-fire-and-water/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 18:26:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-66-for-the-family-to-go-through-fire-and-water/</guid>
      <description>In the jungle, as he kept on moving forward, Bai Xiaochun gradually saw some clues. His guess was more certain until he got out of the mountain. A few days later, at this extreme speed, he returned to the Luoxing mountain range and found the Luochen family which had become a ruin.
&amp;ldquo;It seems that Du Lingfei and Hou Yunfei have indeed sent the news back to zongmen.&amp;rdquo; Bai Xiaochun recalled the previous tragic, full of regret, turned for a long time, the wind boat appeared, he jumped up and sat down, control the wind boat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 65 tomb watchers</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-65-tomb-watchers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 18:26:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-65-tomb-watchers/</guid>
      <description>At the moment of sneezing, Bai Xiaochun also woke up, and his consciousness was still immersed in the serious injury state before coma. As soon as he woke up, he subconsciously held his left arm and screamed, but the scream stopped suddenly. He looked down at his left arm in surprise, looked at his body, touched here, touched there, and even lifted his clothes to see himself White and tender stomach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 64 spirit and funeral</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-64-spirit-and-funeral/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 18:26:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-64-spirit-and-funeral/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Spread out and try our best to find Bai Xiaochun. If I find someone, I will reward him for his contribution. If you see any other members of the Luochen family outside, kill them all!&amp;rdquo; Ouyang Jie took back his eyes and looked at Li Qinghou&amp;rsquo;s back. When he opened his mouth slowly, all the disciples around him immediately spread.
Over 2000 people have been searching for it for a month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 63 rolling down the old!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-63-rolling-down-the-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 18:26:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-63-rolling-down-the-old/</guid>
      <description>Li Qinghou was close at the moment. Standing in the array, his look was gloomy and incomparable. The whole person was like a knife out of the body, full of evil spirit.
Ouyang Jie took a look at Li Qinghou, and his eyes narrowed slightly. In the whole south bank and the palm seat of Sanshan mountain, what he cared most about was this Li Qinghou. At the same time, the other party was also the one cared about by the whole Lingxi clan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 62 killing a chicken with a knife!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-62-killing-a-chicken-with-a-knife/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 18:25:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-62-killing-a-chicken-with-a-knife/</guid>
      <description>Unknown mountains, deep in the jungle, thunderstorm from what time, gradually weak, until dusk, the rain stopped, although there is only a dim sunset in the distance, can vaguely see some incomplete rainbow.
It seems that with the setting sun, the rainbow is also gradually fragmented.
It was quiet in the jungle, and even the smell of blood disappeared. Only the corpses along the way witnessed a fierce killing here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 61 a fatal blow!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-61-a-fatal-blow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 18:25:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-61-a-fatal-blow/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s speed is too fast. At the moment, he is surrounded by Chen Heng and does not give him any chance to react. He punches and kicks, forming a strong wind.
Chen Heng&amp;rsquo;s face was unsightly. The light of his whole body was diffused and a large amount of fog was scattered. He and Bai Xiaochun were fighting with each other in the jungle and in the thunder and rain, and a series of roars were heard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 60 battle of life and death</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-60-battle-of-life-and-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 18:25:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-60-battle-of-life-and-death/</guid>
      <description>This scene is too fast. In the room of electric light and flint, three members of the Luochen family with eight layers of gas condensate are killed immediately. The other two breathe. But they have no time to think about it and kill Bai Xiaochun.
White Xiaochun spilled blood from the corner of his mouth, shivered and fell back on the tree behind him. When the long sword in his chest was suddenly knocked out, he grabbed the sword with his right hand, pulled it out suddenly and swept towards one of them with a sword.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 59 life and death!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-59-life-and-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 18:25:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-59-life-and-death/</guid>
      <description>Almost at the moment when Chen Heng&amp;rsquo;s voice came out, Bai Xiaochun, who was nailed to the tree, suddenly raised his head. His eyes showed fierceness. His left hand lifted up, and he grabbed the tail of the arrow outside his right shoulder. Regardless of the barb in his body, he pulled it out.
When a large amount of blood was sprayed out, the arrow was pulled out by him with several pieces of flesh and blood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 58 trapped animals still fight!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-58-trapped-animals-still-fight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 18:25:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-58-trapped-animals-still-fight/</guid>
      <description>Rain night, thunder roaring, lightning across the sky, so that the sky and earth suddenly bright and dark, loud reverberation, beans big raindrops continue to fall on the earth, issued a loud sound.
From a distance, the whole world is shrouded in the rain, a blur, breeding boundless killing.
On the ground, Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s body trembled and her eyes were red. She was exploding at full speed. Sometimes she stepped on the ground fiercely and suddenly jumped up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 57 we all have to live!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-57-we-all-have-to-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:35:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-57-we-all-have-to-live/</guid>
      <description>With the help of the fire, you can see a big man standing outside the cave.
This big man is very big, holding a long gun, his eyes are cold, and his body is eight layers of condensate gas. He looks more powerful than Chen Yue.
&amp;ldquo;The young Lord has judged correctly. On such a cold and rainy day, you are injured and can&amp;rsquo;t stand the cold. You will surely escape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 56 living together</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-56-living-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:34:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-56-living-together/</guid>
      <description>At this moment, it was the next evening. Bai Xiaochun and Bai Xiaochun ran at a gallop. From time to time, they took out the jade slips and tried. But they could not contact zongmen. Although they were anxious, they had no way.
Fortunately, there are enough pills. There are also some in the storage bags of the seven people killed by Bai Xiaochun. Although they are not as good as Lingxi clan, they are better than none at this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 55 little Lord Chen Heng!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-55-little-lord-chen-heng/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:34:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-55-little-lord-chen-heng/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Purple gas into tripod!&amp;rdquo; Hou Yunfei and Du Lingfei, at the same time, exclaimed. Both of them showed a stronger shock.
Du Lingfei, in particular, has already mastered the difficulty of lifting a heavy vessel like a light, and clearly knows the difficulty of turning the purple gas into a tripod, which is a magic power that few people can master on the south bank, even in the purple tripod mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 54 morality in the heart!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-54-morality-in-the-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:34:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-54-morality-in-the-heart/</guid>
      <description>Seeing that the two clansmen with six layers of condensation gas are about to escape, Bai Xiaochun pinches the formula, and with the whistling of the small wooden sword, she immediately flies across the neck of a six layer condensed gas clansman.
Until death, the eyes of the six layers of condensed gas were filled with unprecedented horror and fear.
They were supposed to be hunters, but now On the contrary, he became the slain!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 53 courage!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-53-courage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:34:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-53-courage/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun was pale and trembling in the bottom of his heart. The sense of crisis that came from all over his body made him tremble constantly.
He had never been so afraid, whether he was lighting incense in the village, hearing thunder, being taken to the ten thousand snake Valley by Li Qinghou in the clan gate, or seeing all kinds of powerful creatures along the way.
In those days, although he was nervous, he knew he was It won&amp;rsquo;t die!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 52 betrayal of Chen</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-52-betrayal-of-chen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:34:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-52-betrayal-of-chen/</guid>
      <description>At the same time, there is a huge underground palace at the bottom of the house where the Luochen family is located. There is a blood lake where countless bones are soaked.
There is a shining array around. Countless people of the Luochen family are kneeling around one by one. Men and women, old and young, are densely packed. The kneeling place of each clan is a node of this array.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 51 elder martial brother Feng is a good man</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-51-elder-martial-brother-feng-is-a-good-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:33:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-51-elder-martial-brother-feng-is-a-good-man/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s scalp was about to explode. His eyes were red and roared. A large number of Rune papers were taken out by him and pressed on his body. The protective light curtain outside his body suddenly increased, which was more than half a foot high.
At the moment when the light curtain appeared, the woman in red suddenly stepped out of the darkness on the side of Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s body and hit the light curtain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 50 weird courtyard</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-50-weird-courtyard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:33:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-50-weird-courtyard/</guid>
      <description>At the moment when the gate of the house opened, Du Lingfei and the three of them looked at it with vigilance. Bai Xiaochun was nervous and took out a large number of runes and pasted them in front of him, making a crackling noise all over his body.
The figure that appeared, holding a lantern in his hand, stood in the open door. His whole body seemed to blend with the darkness and looked at the three people in a secluded way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 49 the Luo Chen family</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-49-the-luo-chen-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:33:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-49-the-luo-chen-family/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Although Feng Yan went out for many missions, he never had one so far away. After seeing the scene behind the scenes, he felt numb, not to mention Du Lingfei.
Fortunately, all the tough creatures we met along the way didn&amp;rsquo;t launch any attacks on them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 48 the world</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-48-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:33:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-48-the-world/</guid>
      <description>One day later, when the first spirit stone in the boat was exhausted, Feng Yan withdrew his sails and the three fell on the top of a mountain. It was dusk. The sun was setting in the distance, and the earth was getting dark.
At the foot of the mountain, the sound of birds and beasts was heard from time to time, and there was a lot of moisture around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 47 Xiaochun&#39;s coming out</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-47-xiaochuns-coming-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:57:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-47-xiaochuns-coming-out/</guid>
      <description>In the morning, when the first ray of sunlight fell, Bai Xiaochun felt the vibration of his identity token. Standing outside his yard, he looked back at his house, which had lived for more than two years, and sighed.
&amp;ldquo;You must be careful during this trip. You can&amp;rsquo;t lose your life&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; Bai Xiaochun put on seven or eight leather clothes and carried Zhang Da Pang&amp;rsquo;s black pot on his back. He was thin and small, but now he looks like a ball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 46 tasks of law enforcement hall!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-46-tasks-of-law-enforcement-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:57:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-46-tasks-of-law-enforcement-hall/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
The token is dark, but in the middle of the token, there is a raised word &amp;ldquo;Fa&amp;rdquo;. When you look at it, you can&amp;rsquo;t help but feel a sense of awe.
While Bai Xiaochun was stunned, a cold voice came out of the token and reverberated throughout the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 45 it&#39;s not hard to kill you!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-45-its-not-hard-to-kill-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:57:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-45-its-not-hard-to-kill-you/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun is short of breath. He has already forgotten himself. He has not considered his success several times, nor paid attention to the result of this assessment. His eyes are full of bloodshot. At the moment, there is only one thing he can think about, that is, how to make himself fully confident when he turns on the furnace next time.
If you are not sure, never open the furnace!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 44 it&#39;s morning</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-44-its-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:56:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-44-its-morning/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
After studying the last plant and solving the most difficult problem, he didn&amp;rsquo;t pay attention to the cheers of the people around him. From the moment he picked up the prescription of the jade slips, he was immersed in the herbs, and the whole person was in a state of selflessness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 43 is very slow Very slow</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-43-is-very-slow-very-slow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:56:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-43-is-very-slow-very-slow/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Is it He&amp;rsquo;s the little tortoise There was an uproar.
Compared with all the people, the most shocking thing here is Xu Baocai. He looks at Bai Xiaochun and feels that his eyes will come out. Just now, he despises Bai Xiaochun and doesn&amp;rsquo;t take the three chapters of spirit and beast seriously. At this moment, Bai Xiaochun should not be taken seriously
&amp;ldquo;Great success of plants and animals Bai Xiaochun here, he just clearly is teasing me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 42 promotion assessment</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-42-promotion-assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:56:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-42-promotion-assessment/</guid>
      <description>On the south side of Xiangyun mountain, the pharmacist&amp;rsquo;s Pavilion is surrounded by green trees and a winding blue stone road, which connects with the main road of Xiangyun mountain. When there is no promotion assessment in this area, almost no one comes here. Only when there is a promotion assessment, can there be a large number of visitors.
In addition to the students to be assessed, most of them are friends of these people, or those who want to participate but feel uncertain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 41 the effect of soul refining</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-41-the-effect-of-soul-refining/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:56:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-41-the-effect-of-soul-refining/</guid>
      <description>There are no mice in Xiangyun mountain. The rats can&amp;rsquo;t exist unless they are spirit animals. However, there are many ants in the mountains.
These ants are natural things, usually in the cracks of some rocks, they will not be boring, as if they are part of the mountain, so no one cares.
But today, around the alchemy Pavilion, the disciple who was guarding there suddenly stood up. In an instant, he found that countless ants appeared on the ground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 40 pursuit of perfection</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-40-pursuit-of-perfection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:55:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-40-pursuit-of-perfection/</guid>
      <description>Humming a little song, Bai Xiaochun is very happy to step into the door, back to the yard, he also sighed.
&amp;ldquo;The purpose of cultivating immortals is to live forever. These people are always fighting and killing, and they have brain problems.&amp;rdquo;
In the yard, Bai Xiaochun tidies up the storage bags of Chen Fei and Chen Fei. They are not rich and their pockets are shriveled. Bai Xiaochun does not get much harvest, but he doesn&amp;rsquo;t care too much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 39 rolling</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-39-rolling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:55:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-39-rolling/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Chen Fei?&amp;rdquo; Bai Xiaochun blinked. Her eyes quickly swept over Chen Fei and the two people around him. After realizing their accomplishments, he was determined.
&amp;ldquo;Bai Xiaochun, even if you kneel down to beg for mercy, it&amp;rsquo;s too late. At the beginning, your idea made us become disciples of other schools. I, Chen Fei, have been waiting for this day for a long time.&amp;rdquo; Chen Fei laughs and raises his right hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 38 Ziqi Huading</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-38-ziqi-huading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 22:55:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-38-ziqi-huading/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun was excited. He got up and moved his body. He also controlled the small wooden sword to fly back and forth in the courtyard. Sometimes he quickly roared away, sometimes he stopped suddenly, which implied a sense of great importance.
The whole wooden sword is unpredictable in this yard, and soon forms bursts of sword spirit. It seems that a strong wind is blowing out of thin air, which makes Bai Xiaochun more excited here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 37 lifting lightly is as important</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-37-lifting-lightly-is-as-important/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:21:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-37-lifting-lightly-is-as-important/</guid>
      <description>Ten steles, first!
Lingxi is located in the three mountains on the south bank, which is a complete sensation.
Inside and outside the Wanyao Pavilion, at this moment, the sound was booming and spread all over the world. Many people came to the Wanyao Pavilion quickly, looking at the ten stone tablets all being the first little tortoise, they took a breath one after another.
&amp;ldquo;Ten steles are the first. The little turtle has really done it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 36 little tortoise dominates!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-36-little-tortoise-dominates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:21:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-36-little-tortoise-dominates/</guid>
      <description>Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s desire to build a foundation was aroused by Xu Baocai&amp;rsquo;s words. In the following days, he went to the Sutra Pavilion several times, and even to the Shenwu hall.
In the Shenwu hall, there are many common sense in the Xiuzhen area, and there are also more detailed descriptions about the foundation. When I saw that what was written in it was really similar to what Xu Baocai said, Bai Xiaochun suddenly burst into flames.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 35 see Xu Baocai again</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-35-see-xu-baocai-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:20:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-35-see-xu-baocai-again/</guid>
      <description>[latest broadcast] tomorrow is 515, the start of the anniversary, the most welfare day. In addition to the gift bag and schoolbag, this &amp;ldquo;515 red envelope crazily flipping&amp;rdquo; must see that there is no reason why the red envelope should not be robbed~
Half a month later, Bai Xiaochun finally crushed Du Lingfei in xiaobizhong, which caused quite a stir in the clan.
As a result, every time Bai Xiaochun went out, some other disciples met and said hello with a smile, which made Bai Xiaochun immediately feel that she was also a celebrity, so she liked to go out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 34 rolling of vegetation</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-34-rolling-of-vegetation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:20:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-34-rolling-of-vegetation/</guid>
      <description>[latest broadcast] tomorrow is 515, the start of the anniversary, the most welfare day. In addition to the gift bag and schoolbag, this &amp;ldquo;515 red envelope crazily flipping&amp;rdquo; must see that there is no reason why the red envelope should not be robbed~
Du Lingfei&amp;rsquo;s words made the outside disciples laugh. They didn&amp;rsquo;t believe that Bai Xiaochun could be better than Du Lingfei in this aspect.
In particular, Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s last words, to their ears, are simply impossible, which is clearly in the same blind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 33 defeat Bai Xiaochun!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-33-defeat-bai-xiaochun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:20:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-33-defeat-bai-xiaochun/</guid>
      <description>[broadcast] students who pay attention to &amp;ldquo;starting reading&amp;rdquo; and get the first-hand news of 515 red envelopes can show their skills this time.
Around the outside disciples, as well as those who were eliminated, one by one immediately shared a common hatred against the enemy and roared at Bai Xiaochun.
&amp;ldquo;Shameless, Bai Xiaochun, you are so shameless!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;We won&amp;rsquo;t accept such a victory!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Down with Bai Xiaochun!&amp;rdquo;
Seeing the fierce voice of the crowd, Bai Xiaochun was terrified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 32 luck against heaven</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-32-luck-against-heaven/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:20:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-32-luck-against-heaven/</guid>
      <description>[broadcast] students who pay attention to &amp;ldquo;starting reading&amp;rdquo; and get the first-hand news of 515 red envelopes can show their skills this time.
Not only are the hearts of the people around complicated, even Du Lingfei is jealous of Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s luck. Chen Ziang and others are the same. The four of them have entered the top five, and each battle has its own consumption. If this time, the four of them have got the qualification of being in the air and have a rest, they will certainly have a great advantage in the later battles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 31 shame!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-31-shame/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:19:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-31-shame/</guid>
      <description>The wooden sword of the thin young man set off an extraordinary momentum and turned into a rainbow. He went straight to Bai Xiaochun. But he didn&amp;rsquo;t wait to get close to his body. Outside Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s four feet away, in the thick light of protection, the wooden sword popped back.
Bai Xiaochun in the protection of the light in front of a bright, immediately relieved, dry cough a sound, simply sit cross knee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 30 come on!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-30-come-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:19:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-30-come-on/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Three days later, in the morning.
At the beginning of the day, Bai Xiaochun opened his eyes. He took a deep breath and looked very dignified. It was the first time for him to have a competition with other families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 29 lifting heavy as light</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-29-lifting-heavy-as-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:19:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-29-lifting-heavy-as-light/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Bai Xiaochun tried the degree of protection, immediately laughed, and then looked at his own wooden sword, which he had when he was a beginner. Now, he has experienced two times of soul refining. [love to go to the small</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 28 pressure is the driving force</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-28-pressure-is-the-driving-force/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:19:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-28-pressure-is-the-driving-force/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Bai Xiaochun was also stunned. Looking at the exclamation of people around him, and looking at Zhao Yiduo and Chen Ziang, who were swept away in the distance, it seemed that they did not care about the whole body pain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 25 Immortal iron sheet!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-25-immortal-iron-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:26:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-25-immortal-iron-sheet/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Until a month later, the wind was so tight that even the old lady in Zhang&amp;rsquo;s mouth and Xu Meixiang, the palm of ziding mountain, had heard something about it. Bai Xiaochun and Zhang daphou had to give up and stay in ziding mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 24 who are you</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-24-who-are-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:26:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-24-who-are-you/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
In the courtyard of Xiangyun mountain, Bai Xiaochun looks at the jade pendant in her hand, and her spirit moves. Immediately, the jade pendant emits a soft blue light, covering her whole body.
He pinched the key with his left hand, and immediately the wooden sword flew out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 23 chicken stealing maniac</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-23-chicken-stealing-maniac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:26:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-23-chicken-stealing-maniac/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to present today&amp;rsquo;s update. By the way, I&amp;rsquo;d like to draw a vote for the &amp;ldquo;starting point&amp;rdquo; 515 fan Festival. Everyone has 8 tickets. I&amp;rsquo;d like to give you some money to vote for!
Late at night, Xiangyun mountain is shrouded in darkness, and there is no sign of five fingers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 22 don&#39;t worry, elder martial sister!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-22-dont-worry-elder-martial-sister/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:26:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-22-dont-worry-elder-martial-sister/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to present today&amp;rsquo;s update. By the way, I&amp;rsquo;d like to draw a vote for the &amp;ldquo;starting point&amp;rdquo; 515 fan Festival. Everyone has 8 tickets. I&amp;rsquo;d like to give you some money to vote for!
&amp;ldquo;Look at the second stone tablet, little turtle Reproduction</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 21 brother Xiaochun</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-21-brother-xiaochun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:26:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-21-brother-xiaochun/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to present today&amp;rsquo;s update. By the way, I&amp;rsquo;d like to draw a vote for the &amp;ldquo;starting point&amp;rdquo; 515 fan Festival. Everyone has 8 tickets. I&amp;rsquo;d like to give you some money to vote for!
Wanyao Pavilion is one of the most lively places on Xiangyun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 20 chicken feather</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-20-chicken-feather/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:25:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-20-chicken-feather/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to present today&amp;rsquo;s update. By the way, I&amp;rsquo;d like to draw a vote for the &amp;ldquo;starting point&amp;rdquo; 515 fan Festival. Everyone has 8 tickets. I&amp;rsquo;d like to give you some money to vote for!
The body of Lingwei chicken is much larger than that of ordinary domestic chicken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 19 The Legend of the white rat and Wolf</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-19-the-legend-of-the-white-rat-and-wolf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:25:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-19-the-legend-of-the-white-rat-and-wolf/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to present today&amp;rsquo;s update. By the way, I&amp;rsquo;d like to draw a vote for the &amp;ldquo;starting point&amp;rdquo; 515 fan Festival. Everyone has 8 tickets. I&amp;rsquo;d like to give you some money to vote for!
In Xiangyun mountain, Bai Xiaochun, as a foreign disciple, lived a very moist life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 18 lead the atmosphere!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-18-lead-the-atmosphere/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:25:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-18-lead-the-atmosphere/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
That is the stone tablet of the fourth chapter of the spirit beast. If you calculate it, it can be regarded as the ninth stone tablet. At the moment, the first one on the top has become a treasure vase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 17 little tortoise</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-17-little-tortoise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:04:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-17-little-tortoise/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
The next morning, Bai Xiaochun walked out of the wooden house early. At a glance, he saw that the Lingdong bamboo in the holy field had grown to more than half a person&amp;rsquo;s height. He nodded with satisfaction. Then he walked out of the yard and walked along the mountain road towards the Wanyao Pavilion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 16 meticulous</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-16-meticulous/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:03:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-16-meticulous/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
With this persistence, Bai Xiaochun lies in the yard. Although his body is sour and soft, he can vaguely see that his skin seems to be obviously harder. This scene makes him more eager to become a pharmacist.
After lying in the yard for more than half an hour, Bai Xiaochun immediately got up and sat down on her knees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 15 immortal longevity!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-15-immortal-longevity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:03:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-15-immortal-longevity/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
The moon is bright and falls on Lingxi zongxiangyun mountain, diluting some clouds and fog, making the whole mountain show more than half of the whole mountain, which looks like a unique beauty.
At the east of the mountain, at the end of a forked mountain road, there is a yard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 13 you too!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-13-you-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:03:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-13-you-too/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
The fight between the supervisor&amp;rsquo;s office and the fire stove room has lasted for many years, and there are many frictions between them. However, they all have a good grasp of the yardstick. They will not let things go too far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 12 fence wall</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-12-fence-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:03:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-12-fence-wall/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
This time, the trial of promotion from a mixed servant to a layman was over. As Hou Xiaomei and Hou Xiaomei stepped on the top of the mountain and gradually left, Zhang daphou looked at Hou Xiaomei&amp;rsquo;s back, touched her plump chin, and his face was meaningful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 11 Hou Xiaomei</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-11-hou-xiaomei/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:02:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-11-hou-xiaomei/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
This is the first reaction in his mind after hearing Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s words. However, he hesitated when his eyes fell on the two evil meat mountains behind Bai Xiaochun.
&amp;ldquo;You&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
Bai Xiaochun, with a smile on her face, looks lovely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 10 don&#39;t go, elder martial brother</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-10-dont-go-elder-martial-brother/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:02:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-10-dont-go-elder-martial-brother/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Looking around, several fat elder martial brothers are staring at themselves. The light of the spirit stone seems to flash in those small eyes. Especially when Zhang daphou looks at himself, his eyes are like fire Bai Xiaochun had a dry cough and felt a little proud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 9 longevity pill</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-9-longevity-pill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:02:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-9-longevity-pill/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
A month later, when the cold wind gradually rose and the autumn leaves fluttered down the Tongtian River, Bai Xiaochun suddenly found that he had been here for a year. [love to go to the small
In this year, too many things happened to him, from a mortal to a monk, with the cultivation of three layers of condensation gas, which also resolved a series of disputes caused by becoming a member of the fire kitchen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 8 I&#39;ll fight with you!</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-8-ill-fight-with-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 11:02:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-8-ill-fight-with-you/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Here is the May day update. Don&amp;rsquo;t hurry to play after watching it. Remember to vote for a monthly ticket first. From now on, you can enjoy double monthly tickets at 515 fan Festival. You can also have a look at ang for other activities!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 7 turtle pattern recognition</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-7-turtle-pattern-recognition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:43:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-7-turtle-pattern-recognition/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Here is the May day update. Don&amp;rsquo;t hurry to play after watching it. Remember to vote for a monthly ticket first. From now on, you can enjoy double monthly tickets at 515 fan Festival. You can also have a look at ang for other activities!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 6 Aura</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-6-aura/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:43:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-6-aura/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
Here is the May day update. Don&amp;rsquo;t hurry to play after watching it. Remember to vote for a monthly ticket first. From now on, you can enjoy double monthly tickets at 515 fans&amp;rsquo; day. You can also have a look at other activities!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter five what to do if I lose my life</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-five-what-to-do-if-i-lose-my-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:42:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-five-what-to-do-if-i-lose-my-life/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
As soon as the wooden sword fell into the pot, there was no special change. Bai Xiaochun uttered a light cry and opened her eyes unwillingly, staring at the wooden sword carefully.
But after waiting for a long time, nothing strange happened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter 4 soul refining</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-4-soul-refining/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:42:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-4-soul-refining/</guid>
      <description>Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read. A kind of Go to &amp;ldquo;small talk → net&amp;rdquo; to provide you with wonderful novels to read.
When they looked at Bai Xiaochun, they felt that Bai Xiaochun was not only cute, but also had a lot of bad water in his stomach. So Zhang daphou made the decision and rewarded Bai Xiaochun with a grain of LingMi, which was put in Bai Xiaochun&amp;rsquo;s hands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter three six true words</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-three-six-true-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 15:41:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-three-six-true-words/</guid>
      <description>Chapter three
When Bai Xiaochun stretched out her head like this, the young man with yellow complexion and thin immediately saw her, and her eyes fell on her face, and she was furious.
&amp;ldquo;You took my place!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Not me!&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s too late for Bai Xiaochun to shrink her head and pretend to be innocent.
&amp;ldquo;Nonsense, you are so thin and your head is so small, you are definitely NEW!&amp;rdquo; Xu Baocai clenched his fist and glared at Bai Xiaochun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter II fire kitchen</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-ii-fire-kitchen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 11:25:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-ii-fire-kitchen/</guid>
      <description>Chapter two.
Lingxizong, located in donglinzhou, is the downstream branch of Tongtian River. Based on the north and south sides of Tongtian River, lingxizong has a history of ten thousand years and has shocked all quarters.
Eight cloud shrouded Jingtian peaks lie across the Tongtian River, including four on the north bank and three on the south bank. As for the Tongtian River in the middle, there is a most majestic peak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eternal thought--Chapter one his name is Bai Xiaochun</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-one-his-name-is-bai-xiaochun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 11:25:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/eternal-thought-chapter-one-his-name-is-bai-xiaochun/</guid>
      <description>Maoershan is located in the Donglin mountains. There is a village at the foot of the mountain. The people are simple and live on farming. They are isolated from the world.
In the early morning, in front of the gate of the village, the villagers in the whole village were seeing off a 15-year-old boy. The young man was thin, but white, and looked very clever. Although his clothes were ordinary blue clothes, they were washed white.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 256 killing Immortals</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-256-killing-immortals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 17:54:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-256-killing-immortals/</guid>
      <description>The red light of blood covered the sky and floated over the sky. Looking at the sky peak, the whole sky curtain turned red, and the dark red clouds rolled and tossed, which made people feel breathless. Under this red cloud, everything is dyed red. The sky is red, the mountains are red, the clouds on the sea of clouds are red, and the water drops on the Hongqiao bridge are red, even as if the cold mountain wind is blowing, as if it were red.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 255 the way of heaven</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-255-the-way-of-heaven/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 17:54:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-255-the-way-of-heaven/</guid>
      <description>﻿ 、、、、、、、。
Zhang Xiaofan never thought that he would open his eyes to see such a world.
Everything in front of him was not a cave hidden in the deep of the mountain in his imagination. In front of him, it was another ancient, desolate and strange place.
In front of him, there were no trees, flowers and plants, only dark gray rocks and sand. The strong wind blew over the Gobi with a whistling sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Summon chapter 254</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-254-summon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 17:53:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-254-summon/</guid>
      <description>The ruins of Caomiao village at the foot of Qingyun Mountain.
As the sun rises and sets and the day and night change, Lu Xueqi doesn&amp;rsquo;t remember how many days she has been here. She seems to have lost control of her love for more than ten years. She can&amp;rsquo;t and doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to endure any more. Every day and night, she will accompany the man and accompany him. If there is a future, then forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 253 Lingpai</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-253-lingpai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 17:45:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-253-lingpai/</guid>
      <description>The vast land of Shenzhou, the vast mountains, and the fertile land of central China, still seem to be a peaceful scene at this time, and there is no sense of the strange occurrence of the remote mountains in the southwest border.
However, at the moment, there are two people flying to Huqi mountain, where the former general Hall of the ghost King clan was located. It was the former secret who sneaked into Qingyun Mountain and secretly broke the &amp;ldquo;tianjilock&amp;rdquo; of jinpinger and Cangsong Taoist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 252 cuddle up</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-252-cuddle-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 17:45:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-252-cuddle-up/</guid>
      <description>A white shadow flashed across the sky and fell down on a small hill tens of miles away from Huqi mountain. The light light flickered for a moment and then dispersed to reveal the figure of nine tail Tianhu Xiaobai.
She gently held the body in her hands and put it on the ground. Then she checked it carefully to make sure that he was not seriously injured. Then she took a breath and stood up slowly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 251 farewell to death</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-251-farewell-to-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 17:44:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-251-farewell-to-death/</guid>
      <description>On the platform of the blood pool, both GUI Li and Mr. GUI look up at the Fu Long Ding suspended in the air. However, their expressions and eyes are quite different. GUI Li is shocked with astonishment, and Mr. GUI&amp;rsquo;s eyes behind the black veil are completely excited and ecstatic.
Without the lock of heaven and earth, which is the last and most important shuanjiao, the mysterious power of fulongding mountain seems to have been completely revived at the moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 250 monsters</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-250-monsters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 17:44:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-250-monsters/</guid>
      <description>The ground was shaking violently, and the rocks were falling all around, and the astrolabe was full of light, illuminating the whole ghost king room. In the air, the smell of blood came, and the strong smell almost made people think that they were immersed in a bloody sea.
GUI Li didn&amp;rsquo;t know why this kind of change happened suddenly, but after the initial consternation, he suddenly woke up and turned and yelled: &amp;ldquo;Xiao Hui!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 249 fierce monkey</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-249-fierce-monkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 17:43:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-249-fierce-monkey/</guid>
      <description>The red light and shadow twinkled ceaselessly, and the huge space was as bright as day. There was a pungent smell of blood all around. A wide platform road extended from the entrance to the middle of the huge cave. Xiaohui stepped out of the passage carefully and jumped onto the platform. Its weak body looked very small in the huge cave.
Obviously, this is a place that is quite different from other places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 248 secret combat</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-248-secret-combat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 17:43:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-248-secret-combat/</guid>
      <description>Three days passed.
The watchman in the ghost King&amp;rsquo;s stone chamber, his face has changed from calm and indifferent to uneasiness, and then to anxiety, and now is full of irritability and impatience. For him, although he had made this astrolabe, after all, was not an ordinary treasure, and it took quite a long time to prepare for the mystery. But he never thought that it would take him three days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 247 waiting</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-247-waiting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 17:42:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-247-waiting/</guid>
      <description>At this time, a cruel and terrible thing happened, especially among the disciples of the ghost King sect who had finally obtained ten days&amp;rsquo; peace. This once again came ten times more crazy and terrifying than before, which had already made people&amp;rsquo;s nerves stretch to the extreme.
Soon after the violent earthquake, there were people who wanted to escape.
There were not many people who escaped. There was only one, and he was not an important person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 246 astrolabe</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-246-astrolabe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 17:42:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-246-astrolabe/</guid>
      <description>It has been ten days since GUI Li returned to Huqi mountain, but his biggest and only purpose has not made any progress.
In recent days, the Qiankun samsara plate and the Albizzia bell in Biyao&amp;rsquo;s hands have never reacted again. Every time he tries with hope, he always gets a cold answer. And that strange underground mysterious force on that day seems to have disappeared since then, and it has never happened again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 245</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-245/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 17:41:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-245/</guid>
      <description>As the world went on, the smooth bundle seemed to be awakened, brighter and brighter, echoing something.
On the platform, Mr. ghost&amp;rsquo;s body moved for a moment. He seemed to feel something, but he was not sure. After a moment&amp;rsquo;s hesitation, he slowly opened his eyes and looked up to the Fulong Ding.
After a slight movement of his body, he slowly woke up from a confused void, turned over and sat up on the bed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 244 heaven and earth lock</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-244-heaven-and-earth-lock/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 17:41:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-244-heaven-and-earth-lock/</guid>
      <description>The blood pool is deep in the cave of guiwangzong in Huqi mountain.
The huge space is still covered by a strong smell of blood, even the hard stone walls have been dyed with bright blood red color. In the pool of blood bubbling with bubbles from the depths of blood, the four ancient spirit beasts all showed tired and powerless appearance. Immersed in the blood pool, the dark red light and shadow shot from the mysterious and empty volong tripod in the sky now looks much dimmer than before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 243 hope</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-243-hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 17:41:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-243-hope/</guid>
      <description>The heavy stone door closed behind Xiaobai with a deep voice, and at the same time isolated those noisy voices in the distance. Xiaobai&amp;rsquo;s bright eyes swept in the room. Then it fell on the man sitting behind the desk in front of him. The man was tall, dignified and majestic. He was the king of ghosts.
At the moment, the ghost king also raised his eyes to Xiaobai, but he didn&amp;rsquo;t speak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 242 fear</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-242-fear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 17:40:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-242-fear/</guid>
      <description>Xumi mountain, Tianyin temple.
There was silence in the remote wooden house. Both master Puhong and master Pude were silent. FA Xiang stood aside with a look of error and consternation on his face. However, he remained silent. The ghost was staring at the treasure in front of him. The soft white light made his face bright and dark.
The black cloth curtain is wrapped in it, which is a magic weapon of jade plate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 241 foreign treasures</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-241-foreign-treasures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 17:40:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-241-foreign-treasures/</guid>
      <description>Ghost calendar is silent, the house is silent.
After a moment, master Pu Hong said slowly, &amp;ldquo;younger martial brother, you all know the cause and effect of this matter. I don&amp;rsquo;t need to say more. Today, this ghost calendar benefactor came here to borrow a treasure from Tianyin temple to save people. &amp;quot;
Master Pude is still looking at the ghost calendar. His eyes have gradually softened from his initial shock and amazement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 240 pud</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-240-pud/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 10:22:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-240-pud/</guid>
      <description>To eliminate the mountain, Tianyin temple.
The steep mountain road meanders and stretches in the mountains. As in the past, in the warm sunshine of this day, the head is still surging. Countless devout believers go to the temple to worship and worship the gods in their hearts. The monks of Tianyin temple are distributed all over the place, and then the common people come up. In some dangerous places on the cliffs, there are usually several monks standing in case of emergency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 239 conspiracy</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-239-conspiracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 10:22:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-239-conspiracy/</guid>
      <description>Huqi mountain, the blood pool of ghost King clan.
At present, the situation of the four spirits and blood array in the blood pool is different from that of the previous few days. The four huge spirit beasts seem to have lost their spirituality completely. They just lie down in the blood pool and water, and the dark red light curtain that covers them becomes weak. If you don&amp;rsquo;t watch carefully, you can hardly see them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 238 parting</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-238-parting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 10:22:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-238-parting/</guid>
      <description>At the foot of Qingyun Mountain, outside Heyang City, there is an ancient Wilderness Road.
Monday immortals still hold that piece of fairy pointing the way in the wind, bamboo pole cloth curtain, swaggering along the ancient road, with him walking side by side is the ghost, and behind them are the small ring and wild dog Taoist.
The four of them walked slowly away from the Heyang city behind him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 237 sorrow</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-237-sorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 10:21:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-237-sorrow/</guid>
      <description>Different from the undercurrent of the gate valves in the Middle Earth, the people of all ethnic groups in southern Xinjiang, thousands of miles away, are rebuilding their homes in silence after the monster catastrophe. Although this is the place where the victims suffered the most, it seems that no one remembers this place. Anyway, the wasteland in southern Xinjiang is not in the eyes of the rich in the middle land.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 236 killing intention</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-236-killing-intention/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 10:21:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-236-killing-intention/</guid>
      <description>Out of the jingshe, Wen Min saw Lu Xueqi standing on one side, and went over and said, &amp;ldquo;younger martial sister, are you going back now?&amp;rdquo;.
Lu Xueqi shook her head slightly and said, &amp;ldquo;since I&amp;rsquo;m out, I want to walk around. I feel bored sitting in the house all the time.&amp;rdquo;.
Wen Min nodded and said, &amp;ldquo;that&amp;rsquo;s right. Be careful. I&amp;rsquo;ll go back first.&amp;rdquo;.
Lu Xueqi nodded slightly and said, &amp;ldquo;yes, elder martial sister, walk slowly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 235 confusion</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-235-confusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 10:21:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-235-confusion/</guid>
      <description>At night, from the head of Heyang City, looking into the city, although the lights of thousands of homes can not be said, but the little light still gives people a warm feeling.
For GUI Li, or is it the most strange place for him?.
He silently gazed at the lights, then turned to the wall which was not tall and not strong. At the moment, the desolate night wind blew from the open fields outside Heyang City, and swept over the city walls which had been injured in the monster disaster, and blew on him and Monday immortal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 234 no regrets</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-234-no-regrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 10:21:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-234-no-regrets/</guid>
      <description>In his current way, he suddenly dumped all the flowers and trees on both sides of the road, like a gap in the sea. The face of the wind, because he was too fast and blowing face faint pain, but he did not care.
At the moment, in his heart, there was only Su Ru&amp;rsquo;s figure in the bamboo forest behind the mountain.
The bark of rhubarb is still in my ears, which is extremely manic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 233 despair</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-233-despair/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 10:20:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-233-despair/</guid>
      <description>Qingyun Mountain, xiaozhufeng.
It has been three days since Tian Buyi&amp;rsquo;s body was sent back to dazhufeng by the ghost. However, Su Ru is still strangely preventing the disciples of dazhufeng from passing on bad news to his classmates. This not only makes song Daren and others feel puzzled, but also surprised GUI Li.
However, no one dares to talk about it to Su Ru. Facing her husband, who is in the Jingjing hall and uses the treasures of the immortal family to protect her body, Su Ru&amp;rsquo;s face is so sad that Zongren can&amp;rsquo;t speak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 232 Blood Omen</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-232-blood-omen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 23:55:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-232-blood-omen/</guid>
      <description>Qingyun Mountain, xiaozhufeng.
The mountains blow through the green bamboo forest, with bursts of bamboo waves, echoing in the valley forest.
Wen Min looked up at the sky and saw that the sky was cloudless and blue. It seemed to have a transparent feeling. She took a deep breath and felt better. However, she did not slow down. She walked through the bamboo path, and soon she saw the little bamboo house where master Shuiyue was resting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 231 relatives</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-231-relatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 23:55:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-231-relatives/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t know how long I&amp;rsquo;ve been sleeping, but I feel the familiar smell all around me. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how long I haven&amp;rsquo;t felt this kind of peace of mind.
Therefore, I also fell into a deep dream, as if I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to wake up. But in the deep of the dream, there was always a tingling feeling, which lingered around and refused to disperse, and constantly pierced my heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 230 going home</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-230-going-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 23:42:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-230-going-home/</guid>
      <description>After the rain, the dark night finally passed, and the first glimmer of light came out of the sky, quietly sprinkling to the world.
Qingyun Mountain, bamboo peak, or a quiet. Although the disciples are diligent, they will not get up so early. Outside the Shoujing hall, among the eaves and tiles, there is the residual dew left last night, which turns into water drops and slides down intermittently. The bamboo forest in the distance is still as green as ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 229 wounds</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-229-wounds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 23:42:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-229-wounds/</guid>
      <description>Qingyun Mountain, Dazhu peak.
In the dead of the night, only the sound of bamboo waves coming from the wind in the distance reverberates gently in the night sky. The lights have already been extinguished, and the disciples of dazhufeng are all at rest. Only in the back of Shoujing hall, there is a solitary lamp flashing in the dark.
The night wind is light and cool. It blows in from the half open window, making a slight &amp;ldquo;whine&amp;rdquo; sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 228 parting</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-228-parting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 23:42:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-228-parting/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Ah&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
It was like the voice squeezed out from the deep throat. It was hoarse and dull. Tian didn&amp;rsquo;t cry softly. His body began to tremble slightly, but he soon calmed down. Only his face, which used to be a faint, faint black air, now full-bodied as if to cover his whole face.
Lu Xueqi&amp;rsquo;s palm is suddenly full of cold sweat.
In that moment, she finally untied her mind has been haunting a puzzle, a puzzle about why tianbuyi suddenly looked a little fat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 227 the heart of death</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-227-the-heart-of-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 23:41:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-227-the-heart-of-death/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Tut &amp;ldquo;A hoarse and strange smile came from the mysterious man, who awoke them for a moment.&amp;rdquo; goodbye, master and apprentice. It&amp;rsquo;s really moving! &amp;quot;
GUI Li took a long breath. No matter what, although he was excited, elated, surprised, and many doubts were pouring in at the moment, after all, he was not an ignorant young man at that time, and soon calmed down his mind. However, he could not help looking at the field and feeling mixed in his heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 226 reunion</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-226-reunion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 23:41:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-226-reunion/</guid>
      <description>Field not easy to grow a breath, the face showed a smile.
But Lu Xueqi, after all, is a man with a close mind. She pondered for a moment, looked at Tian Bu Yi and said, &amp;ldquo;Uncle Tian, what you just meant was that he Can you go back to Qingyun? &amp;quot;
Tian Bu Yi snorted and said, &amp;ldquo;ten years ago, the truth was revealed on Qingyun Mountain. Lao Qi ran away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 225 mind</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-225-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 23:41:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-225-mind/</guid>
      <description>A burst of coughing was heard nearby. The sound was not loud, but it seemed a little urgent. When Lu Xueqi and his party looked at the place where the sound was made, they saw that Tian Bu Yi, sitting on the stone steps, showed a trace of pain on his face and coughed constantly.
Lu Xueqi frowned slightly, with a trace of worry in her eyes. She had already reached the point where all kinds of diseases could not be invaded by Tian Buyi, let alone this small cough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 224 help each other</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-224-help-each-other/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 23:41:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-224-help-each-other/</guid>
      <description>In the abandoned villa, with the sudden appearance of Lu Xueqi, the atmosphere suddenly changed.
Monday fairy frowned, forced a smile, and said, &amp;ldquo;isn&amp;rsquo;t this Lu nvxia from Qingyun Mountain? Why have you been to such a place? &amp;quot;
Lu Xueqi takes a look at Zhou Xian, and then falls on Xiao Bai. Xiaobai smiles, her eyes are rippling, is also looking at her.
Lu Xueqi frowned slightly, then turned to Xiaohuan and said, &amp;ldquo;miss Xiaohuan, is the magic weapon you just mentioned really used by the one who saved you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 223 meeting</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-223-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 23:40:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-223-meeting/</guid>
      <description>At the moment, the whole body was covered with a layer of dust. It seemed that he had been lying in that coffin for a long time. Some of the original daoguxianfeng had disappeared.
Xiaobai looked him up and down. Naturally, he didn&amp;rsquo;t think about the boring question of whether Zhouxian was going to lie in the coffin. He said, &amp;ldquo;how could you be in the coffin?&amp;rdquo;
Monday fairy wry smile, way: &amp;ldquo;I was naturally caught and thrown in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 222 obscenity</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-222-obscenity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 23:40:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-222-obscenity/</guid>
      <description>Shangguance only felt numb around the wound on his back. At the same time, the cold Yin and cold Qi constantly rushed from the Yin charm to the Qi pulse in his body. If he was bitten by ten thousand ants, he was extremely painful.
But for a moment, his forehead was sweating and his face turned pale. Xiaobai, standing on the roof, looked at shangguance&amp;rsquo;s embarrassment in his eyes, and his smile became stronger, which meant gloating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 221 conspiracy</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-221-conspiracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 23:40:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-221-conspiracy/</guid>
      <description>The night is dark and the wind is high, the lights are off, the sky is dark, the clouds are heavy, there is no moon, only the stars in the sky are twinkling.
The night wind &amp;ldquo;swished&amp;rdquo; over Heyang City, like a wild ghost crying at night. It is really chilly and terrifying. I think that there has just been a catastrophe here, and there is no one in the street outside the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 220 hometown</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-220-hometown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 00:18:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-220-hometown/</guid>
      <description>Under Qingyun Mountain.
The sky is high and the clouds are light. Standing at the foot of the mountain and looking up, you can see a piece of blue. The breeze is blowing slowly, which makes you feel refreshed.
Lu Xueqi watched for a long time. Nobody was around. Naturally, no one would notice that there was such a beautiful woman watching the sky at the foot of the secluded mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 219 blood array</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-219-blood-array/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 00:18:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-219-blood-array/</guid>
      <description>Huqishan, the general Hall of ghost king.
Along the way, he only felt a blank in his mind. Only the mysterious and fuzzy figure of a woman lingered in front of him. However, he clearly knew that it should be an illusion, right?
Isn&amp;rsquo;t it?
In a daze, he found that he did not know when he had gone back to his stone room. The stone door was open. When you look in from the door, you can still see the chaos inside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 218 killing a division</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-218-killing-a-division/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 00:18:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-218-killing-a-division/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A hundred years ago, the evil cult was rampant and powerful, and the way to eliminate demons was strong. Under the arrogance of the demons, they invaded Qingyun when they wanted to smooth the way. After a fierce battle, the ancestors of our ancestors fought hard. At the foot of Qingyun Mountain, please use the ancient sword to kill the immortals, and sacrifice the &amp;ldquo;Zhuxian sword array&amp;rdquo;. Finally, we turned the defeat into victory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 217 Secrets</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-217-secrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 00:17:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-217-secrets/</guid>
      <description>Curling up like smoke of white cold, quietly floating in the ice stone room, this day, the cold in the ice stone room seems to be much thicker than usual, even look at the past, there is a bit of hazy feeling, no longer have the past one eye to see the bottom of the clear.
Stone door issued a low roar, in slowly opened, just that into the eyes of the slim figure, but somehow, some appear fuzzy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 216 heart demons</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-216-heart-demons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 00:17:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-216-heart-demons/</guid>
      <description>The ghost king went up to Taotie with steady and peaceful steps. Xiao Hui, who was sitting on GUI Li&amp;rsquo;s shoulder, turned his head and looked at the ghost King&amp;rsquo;s back. He called twice and suddenly became quiet.
Taotie, lying on the ground, seemed to feel something. The huge head moved to one side and lifted it up. The huge eyes also opened. Two fierce lights fell on the ghost king who came by.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 215 return</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-215-return/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 00:17:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-215-return/</guid>
      <description>Qingyun Mountain, xiaozhufeng.
The dark clouds, like dark clouds, can only be seen from the sky. Far away from the horizon, faintly came the rumbling thunder. I don&amp;rsquo;t know whether there will be more violent wind and rain coming.
Lu Xueqi, one of the disciples of Qingyun gate who went to southern Xinjiang, has been back for several days. Lu Xueqi, one of the disciples, went back to xiaozhufeng after meeting the elders of the school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 214 embrace</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-214-embrace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 00:17:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-214-embrace/</guid>
      <description>Incense valley.
At the moment, the majestic mountain and river hall is silent. Except for Li Xun and a group of elite disciples who enter the mysterious 100000 mountain noble childe, most of the disciples of the burning incense Valley either patrol the valley Zhongzhong gang or stay in their own rooms to practice their lessons. They seldom come to the main Hall of the burning incense valley. This is also in addition to late at night, the most desolate time of the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 213 the end of the day</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-213-the-end-of-the-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 00:16:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-213-the-end-of-the-day/</guid>
      <description>The roar seemed to come from a far away place, because in the roaring heat waves and flames, the terrible sound of dragon singing of the eight wild fire dragons seemed to be a little far away. What GUI Li and Lu Xueqi face directly is the huge flame from the raging waves, and the once hard ground under their feet, but now it completely collapses and turns into a lava hell, with huge cracks and countless cracks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 212 eight famine Fire Dragon</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-212-eight-famine-fire-dragon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 00:16:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-212-eight-famine-fire-dragon/</guid>
      <description>Zhenmo ancient cave, cave entrance.
Before the exquisite witch statue, black wood stands in silence, and the evil spirit black tiger is also silent, standing behind him. Lu Xueqi and others have been in the cave for a long time, not to mention ghost and Li, and for such a long time, no one knows what happened in that ancient cave?
However, the two brothers did not seem to show any concern.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 211 terror</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-211-terror/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 00:16:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-211-terror/</guid>
      <description>The hard ground, under the burning of the blazing fire, even began to have the sign of melting. The flaming flame continuously spurted out from the huge mouth of the red flame Warcraft, which had the momentum of destroying everything, turned this huge stone chamber space into a terrible sea of fire.
The ghostly figure disappeared in the fire from the beginning, and never appeared again.
After spitting out a wave of mountain fire, the flaming eyes of red flame Warcraft looked hard at the depth of the fire sea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 210 pursuit</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-210-pursuit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 14:41:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-210-pursuit/</guid>
      <description>At the moment, Jin pinger&amp;rsquo;s face looked very tired, as if she had just experienced a great war and was exhausted. However, in the face of these righteous disciples, Jin pinger still showed a moving smile. In the dark, she looked extremely miserable.
&amp;ldquo;Naturally, it&amp;rsquo;s me, the young master of the burning incense valley. Why, we only met a few times, so you never forget me?&amp;rdquo;
Li Xun&amp;rsquo;s face turned red and stepped back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 209 Warcraft</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-209-warcraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 14:41:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-209-warcraft/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;OK,&amp;rdquo; he said with a faint smile. He turned around, and his tired face seemed to be deeper. He said, &amp;ldquo;what are you doing here? Are you trying to kill me?&amp;rdquo;
The ghost shook his head.
The animal God was stunned for a moment and then said with a smile: &amp;ldquo;I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect that there would be someone who didn&amp;rsquo;t want to kill me. If you don&amp;rsquo;t want to kill people in the world, how can I kill them</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 208</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-208/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 14:41:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-208/</guid>
      <description>South Xinjiang, 100000 mountains.
The cold wind gradually makes people feel cold. The dark clouds in the sky and the gradually obvious deep cave show that the legendary devil&amp;rsquo;s cave is gradually approaching. Lu Xueqi and his party stood more than ten feet away from the zhenmenggu cave and looked at the cave.
In the distance, a stone statue facing the deep of the cave with its back to them stands alone at the entrance of the ancient cave, and there is nothing else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 207 broken sword</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-207-broken-sword/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 14:40:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-207-broken-sword/</guid>
      <description>Zhongtu, outside Heyang City, abandoned village.
This mysterious figure broke through the magic of Monday immortal in one fell swoop, and awed the whole audience with his overwhelming and unfathomable Taoist behavior. He even saw through the escape skill of his family. However, in his speech and behavior, he did not deny the mysterious connection with Qingyun gate. In addition, he was incredibly high in Taiji Xuanqing Taoism. The origin of this mysterious figure is unimaginable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 206 reunion</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-206-reunion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 14:40:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-206-reunion/</guid>
      <description>Qingyun Mountain, Dazhu peak.
Outside the Shoujing hall, the disciples of dazhufeng, starting from Song Daren to Du Bishu, stood outside the door in a row, their faces worried and worried, and they looked at the hall from time to time.
After a while, Shoujing hall sounded the sound of footsteps, out of a woman, but xiaozhufeng Wenmin.
Song Daren and other disciples of dazhufeng gathered around. Song Daren and Wen Min knew each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 205 mysterious man</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-205-mysterious-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 14:40:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-205-mysterious-man/</guid>
      <description>Zhongtu, outside Heyang City, abandoned village.
Above the wilderness, at a glance, the terrain is relatively flat. In addition to looking northward, there is such a towering Qingyun Mountain range in the distance, and there are few rolling hills in other directions. Far and near, there are a lot of woods, large or small, distributed on this field. Around the villa, there are also a few sparse trees standing.
The sky is the darkest time, and the sky is very thick, blocking the moon, only a few small stars at the edge of the light, shining on the desolate land.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 204 Tianhu</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-204-tianhu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 14:39:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-204-tianhu/</guid>
      <description>Xiao Hui&amp;rsquo;s figure disappeared in the dark in an instant. It seemed that he didn&amp;rsquo;t expect that Xiaohui would suddenly make such a strange move. He was surprised. But then he did not get up to chase him. Instead, he slowly raised his head and listened to the faint song coming out of the darkness.
This song is a little familiar, as if I had heard it before?
How many years of time, just like this song, in a hurry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 203 alien</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-203-alien/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 14:39:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-203-alien/</guid>
      <description>Zhongtu, twenty miles outside Heyang city.
The sky is getting dark, and the pedestrians on the ancient road are gradually disappearing. In times of chaos, demons are in vogue. Although it is said that at the foot of Qingyun Gate Mountain, the giant of the right way, no one can say whether they will suddenly encounter any monsters or ghosts.
Everyone has only one life. Even ordinary people cherish their own lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 202 black bat</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-202-black-bat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 14:39:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-202-black-bat/</guid>
      <description>In the dark cave, there was a slight sound of footsteps, and a faint blue light flashed from the front. After the light, there is the figure of GUI Li and Jin Ping er.
The two men have entered the deep part of the ancient magic cave. However, the grotesque cave seems to never have an end. The dark and humid road twists and turns, and seems to extend forward endlessly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 201 emotional injury</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-201-emotional-injury/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 14:39:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-201-emotional-injury/</guid>
      <description>Strange breath, with the heat wave, wave by wave reverberates in this empty space. The dragon was fierce, but it did not continue to expand. It seemed that the current appearance was its limit. Rao is so, in that blazing fire, even the hard surface of the ground began to have cracks, on the contrary, it seems that the old and crude brazier, on the contrary, is safe and sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 200 mystery</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-200-mystery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 15:17:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-200-mystery/</guid>
      <description>The ancestral hall of Qingyun Mountain is still shrouded in the pines and cypresses, and the huge figure looms. However, this silence was soon broken by the chaotic steps. A large group of people under the Qingyun gate rushed to this holy land for worshiping the ancestors of Qingyun ancestors.
From the appearance, it seems that everything is still as quiet as before. But before we get to the hall of the ancestral hall, both the confused disciples of Tongtian peak and the anxious Su Ru stop for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 199 true anger</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-199-true-anger/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 15:17:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-199-true-anger/</guid>
      <description>Qingyun Mountain, Tongtian peak.
On the Yuqing hall, the solemn and solemn scene of the past seems to have changed on this day. The disorderly steps ring ceaselessly inside and outside the Yuqing hall, and the suppressed but flustered whispers seem to spread here like waves of water. In the distance, there seems to be a noisy voice, which in the past can not be imagined that it would happen openly on the Tongtian peak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 198 merit and virtue</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-198-merit-and-virtue/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 15:16:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-198-merit-and-virtue/</guid>
      <description>The Yin wind blows more and more fiercely, and the clothes of jinpinger and jinpinger are hunting. They stood at the entrance of the ancient cave of Zhenmo and watched the huge and strange evil spirits gradually appear in front of them.
The eyes of the size of a copper bell suddenly opened in the white air, and there was a faint blood red light shining through. The huge figure of the evil spirit shrouded him, and his eyes fell on the two mortals standing under him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 197 old land</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-197-old-land/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 15:16:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-197-old-land/</guid>
      <description>Qingyun Mountain, Tongtian peak, ancestral hall.
The green forest is still the same as before, dense and vigorous growth, light morning fog is floating in the forest, everywhere you can see the leaves and branches, grass and wild flowers on the leaf petals, there are crystal dew gently shaking in the breeze. In the distance, there are still clear and pleasant birds singing in the deep forest. Listening to it, it is one of the clearness of mind and body, like a fairyland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 196 footprints</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-196-footprints/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 15:16:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-196-footprints/</guid>
      <description>Black peaks.
After stepping on that mountain, a strong smell was always floating in the air, which was a little choking, with a smell of sulfur. Both GUI Li and Jin Ping&amp;rsquo;er are people of profound cultivation, and can tolerate such peculiar smell. However, as they go deeper into the mountain, the increasingly strong wind gradually makes them frown.
It was a cold and penetrating wind. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how, when it was blowing over my face, although the wind was not so big, it was so gloomy and miserable that it really made me feel cold from the bottom of my heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 195 decisions</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-195-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 15:15:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-195-decisions/</guid>
      <description>South Xinjiang, 100000 mountains.
In front of the vast black forest where GUI Li and Jin pinger once crossed, there are more than a dozen people standing in front of them. Most of them are the elite disciples headed by Li Xun in the burning incense valley of Southern Xinjiang. Among them, only two outsiders are Lu Xueqi and Zeng Shushu of Qingyun gate. As for Wen Min, who had been with Lu Xueqi and Zeng Shushu earlier, she was unexpectedly missing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 194 hidden injury</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-194-hidden-injury/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 15:15:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-194-hidden-injury/</guid>
      <description>After a long time, Zeng Shushu and other talents recovered from their consternation. The three people looked at each other and saw the incomparable shock from each other&amp;rsquo;s eyes. But what is different is that Lu Xueqi and Wen Min have more panic and confusion in their eyes.
Is this secret that only a few disciples of dazhufeng and xiaozhufeng knew and was forbidden to be spread out by Taoist immortal daoxuan several times and times?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 193 disclosure of Secrets</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-193-disclosure-of-secrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 15:15:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-193-disclosure-of-secrets/</guid>
      <description>South Xinjiang, 100000 mountains.
After crossing the black mountains and entering the 100000 mountains, GUI li felt that he had entered a truly wild and primitive world. In fact, in the demon religion, wilderness originally refers to a vast and uninhabited area in the extreme northwest of the vast land of Shenzhou. Most of the places there are Gobi desert, where there is no grass. Even if there is life, it is also a very tenacious wild heritage, so named.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 192 unusual</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-192-unusual/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 15:14:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-192-unusual/</guid>
      <description>The setting sun, hanging far from the horizon, spreads the residual warmth to the land of Southern Xinjiang behind the tall, steep and rolling mountains. The yellow light fell on the silent earth, and the wild was desolate.
Leaving the ghostly and Golden Vase of the burning incense Valley, standing on the wasteland in front of 100000 mountains, facing the endless towering mountains and vast land, they seem to be just two insignificant little creatures, looking up at the huge existence between heaven and earth, looking at the setting sun on that day, little by little, falling behind the boundless mountains, and the sky was slowly darkening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 191 blood</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-191-blood/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 15:14:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-191-blood/</guid>
      <description>GUI Li gazed at Jin Ping&amp;rsquo;er for a long time, her eyebrows wrinkled slightly, but she didn&amp;rsquo;t speak. However, Jin Ping&amp;rsquo;er seemed to be doing nothing under the ghostly and sharp eyes. She didn&amp;rsquo;t feel that her words at the moment were wrong at all. She looked at GUI Li with a smile.
In the dark fire altar, for a time, it was quiet. The monkey Xiaohui, who was lying on his fierce shoulder, seemed to dislike the atmosphere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 190</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-190/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 16:44:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-190/</guid>
      <description>On Monday, the three men rest here to treat wild dogs. When the wild dogs learned that their lives were picked up, they felt more lucky. In private, they were confused about their unexpected bravery. However, after this time, the relationship between Zhouxian and Xiaohuan has become closer. After all, they have lived and died together. After all, Zhouxian doesn&amp;rsquo;t have the same cold words to him as before. When he is asked to work, he is still the same as before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 189 ghost Road</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-189-ghost-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 16:44:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-189-ghost-road/</guid>
      <description>The night was deep.
The wild dog Taoist, who has entered the hell&amp;rsquo;s gate but is lucky to be pulled back, has been bandaged up several wounds on his body at the moment. It seems that he is still weak, but lying on the ground, his breath is weak but gentle, and he is no longer worried about his life.
Xiao Huan, who saved the wild dog Taoist priest, is also in a coma at the moment, but she is just exerting too much energy, which is not a big problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 188 soul recovery</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-188-soul-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 16:44:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-188-soul-recovery/</guid>
      <description>After a rest, the people who were lucky to escape were silent or left a few words of comfort, and then all left the bloody and horrible place one by one. In this troubled world, whose life is not life, who can control whose life? Every day and night, in every strange and secluded place, is not the same scene staged?
On Monday, the fairy and the little ring also left there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 187 mad dog</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-187-mad-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 16:43:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-187-mad-dog/</guid>
      <description>After the monster catastrophe, from north to south, we can see the bleak scenery everywhere. There is no smoke in thousands of miles, and there is no voice in a hundred villages. In the north, because the days of tea poisoning are short, it is better. The more we go south, the more serious the scene is.
Broken walls, towns, everywhere. Even in the open land beside the field, it is even more shocking to find the forest white bones from time to time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 186 secret orders</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-186-secret-orders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 16:43:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-186-secret-orders/</guid>
      <description>In a blink of an eye, monkey Xiaohui has been back on the Dazhu peak for several days. During this period, it seems that he has been away from Dazhu peak for almost ten years. The monkey is still so familiar with the plants and plants here. All day, Xiao Hui and rhubarb are playing and running around. It seems that in the past few days, it seems that Xiaohui and rhubarb have become more and more lively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 185 difficult passage</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-185-difficult-passage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 16:43:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-185-difficult-passage/</guid>
      <description>As usual countless days, the melodious morning bell rings again, reverberating between the Xumi mountains and in the misty mountain breeze. It has gone through countless years, and it will reverberate day after day in the future.
Standing in the morning light, he stood with his hands and listened.
He closed his eyes slightly, as if the bell was ringing to savor. At the moment, I don&amp;rsquo;t know why, his appearance has not changed much, but it seems that he has changed his personal feeling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 184 punishment by heaven</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-184-punishment-by-heaven/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 16:42:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-184-punishment-by-heaven/</guid>
      <description>On the jade wall without words, countless ancient and clumsy gold characters appeared. Such strange things are under the people of Puhong, and none of the monks in Tianyin temple have ever seen it. On the jade wall, there were auspicious rising and dark red flickering. The solemn golden light with strange and unpredictable red light gave people a feeling of breathlessness.
In the middle of the sky, he looked up to the sky and screamed, and his eyes seemed to be very painful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 183 wordless jade wall</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-183-wordless-jade-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 16:42:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-183-wordless-jade-wall/</guid>
      <description>The long bell, once again echoed in Xumi mountain, announced the beginning of a new day.
Rising sun, from the eastern horizon out of a small halo, the first ray of sunlight sprinkled on the world. In the early morning, there are many people walking along the steps of the mountain road to the magnificent temple. Most of them are holding incense candles and offering sacrifices. They are full of piety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 182 haze</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-182-haze/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 16:42:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-182-haze/</guid>
      <description>Qingyun Mountain, Dazhu peak.
It has been many days since the end of the battle of Qingyun. The battlefield, which once changed its color, has gradually become quiet. All traces of the war have been quietly erased in the process of people cleaning up.
On that day, I don&amp;rsquo;t know how many people lost their friends and relatives. On Tongtian peak, I don&amp;rsquo;t know how many corpses were piled up. From the top of the mountain to the foot of the mountain, it was like the legendary underworld prison.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 181 resolution</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-181-resolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 16:41:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-181-resolution/</guid>
      <description>The morning bell is long and the evening drum is heavy. The Xumi mountain is bathed in the misty clouds. From the rising sun to the dusk, the sky changes and the white clouds and dogs roll by. Time never stops for anyone.
Tianyin temple is majestic and majestic. It stands on Xumi mountain like a compassionate giant looking at the world. Countless ordinary people come from all over the world in the early morning to worship the statues in the temple, telling their wishes of happiness or sorrow and praying for the blessing of gods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 180 evil fate</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-180-evil-fate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 10:38:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-180-evil-fate/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It was more than ten years ago, but in my mind, it seems to be the same as what happened yesterday. It&amp;rsquo;s so clear and clear that I haven&amp;rsquo;t forgotten it at all.&amp;rdquo;
Master Pu Hong&amp;rsquo;s voice floated quietly and slowly in the room and began to tell the past.
&amp;ldquo;I remember very clearly that it was a cloudy day, gloomy. That day, from the beginning of the morning, I felt a little uneasy, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t tell what was wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 179 difficult passage through a bitter sea</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-179-difficult-passage-through-a-bitter-sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 10:38:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-179-difficult-passage-through-a-bitter-sea/</guid>
      <description>The plain courtyard is just like the one outside. It is simply a room against the mountain wall. The middle path is paved with green bricks and leads to the door. There are grass on both sides. It seems that no one has taken care of it seriously. Weeds have grown in many places.
Different from the outside, there is a heavy black curtain hanging on the door of this room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 178 secular Buddha Hall</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-178-secular-buddha-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 10:37:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-178-secular-buddha-hall/</guid>
      <description>Morning bell, evening drum, day after day, as if endless.
Every day is as like as two peas. Yesterday, some people feel boring. Some feel peaceful and quiet.
In a twinkling of an eye, GUI Li has been in Tianyin temple for many days, listening to the bell in the morning and the drum in the evening. He rings from the unknown place in the temple every day on time to live in silence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 177 Zen chamber</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-177-zen-chamber/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 10:37:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-177-zen-chamber/</guid>
      <description>Thunder, lightning, strong wind, rainstorm, seem to have been howling in my ears all the time. The confusion and confusion in my mind seem to have confused me? Just in the intense pain, I feel a gust of wind and rain passing by, towards an unknown place.
It seems that someone is talking. The voice is quite strange. It sounds a bit anxious and faintly hears: &amp;ldquo;there seems to be something wrong with him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 176 man in black</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-176-man-in-black/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 10:37:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-176-man-in-black/</guid>
      <description>Storm, still did not stop the appearance.
In the dark, the little light swept, it is the magic weapon in the hands of Qingyun disciple, with the help of the magic weapon glimmer, searching in the wind and rain. This is close to the outside of Qingyun Mountain. It is densely forested with ancient trees and dense plants. In addition, the weather is extremely bad, and the sky is full of lightning and thunder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 175 escape</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-175-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 10:36:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-175-escape/</guid>
      <description>The ancient sword of Zhuxian didn&amp;rsquo;t move. At that moment, it seemed that everyone held their breath, but the scene was quiet and terrible.
There was no sound, no roar, and the ghost saw that the magic wand, which had been smashed by a thousand Jun, hit the ancient sword of Zhuxian, but suddenly fell into a pile of cotton and was silent.
With the roar of rage, the figures at the end of the forest leaped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 174 swallowing blood</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-174-swallowing-blood/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 10:36:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-174-swallowing-blood/</guid>
      <description>Qingyun Mountain, Tongtian peak.
In front of the magic moon cave, GUI Li, Lu Xueqi and Lin Jingyu stand opposite each other. The already delicate atmosphere suddenly seems to be stiff. All the attention of the three people instantly condenses on the ancient sword which is inserted upside down on the ground.
legend of chusen!
The legendary sword, which is famous all over the world, involves endless past events and determines the fate of many people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 173</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-173/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 10:36:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-173/</guid>
      <description>However, the scale of the fight between Lin Yu and his friends is not as big as that of his childhood.
No one ever thought of it! The man who was once close to each other finally came to this point. The two men&amp;rsquo;s figures were scattered and sometimes collided. They swept around the magic moon cave like a storm. All the trees fell down, or were uprooted or cut off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 172 divine sword</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-172-divine-sword/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 10:35:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-172-divine-sword/</guid>
      <description>In the middle of the air, daoxuan real man&amp;rsquo;s brow was locked, and he faced the beast God in front of him, which was like a devil coming out of the nine hell hell hell. He was not only him, but also all the people in the right path under his feet, and they were all stunned.
The monster in the air was as black as ink, and the muscles of its huge body curled up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 171 monster</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-171-monster/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 10:35:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-171-monster/</guid>
      <description>As time goes by, the overwhelming sword rain has already rushed to the beast God, and the strong wind blows on his face. At the same time, the figure of the beast god suddenly disappeared and disappeared in the black air. On the contrary, the evil spirit of the beast under him was full of black gas and jumped up. The skeleton of his whole body made a sound. Under the black air, it was even more terrible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 170 witchcraft</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-170-witchcraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 12:34:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-170-witchcraft/</guid>
      <description>Apart from the ancient forbidden area, there is no other noise except the sound of fighting and roaring from the distant mountains. There is a gentle mountain breeze, gently blowing from the distance, the green mountains shaking together, as if it is not the scenery of the world.
Under the four strong characters of the magic moon cave, the simple stone wall outside the cave has peeled off a lot, as if recording endless years flowing here quietly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 169 decisive battle</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-169-decisive-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 12:34:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-169-decisive-battle/</guid>
      <description>It seems to be a little embarrassed to see the evil spirits and monsters who have been severely damaged. Half of them are gray, while the other parts are blackened. They look strange and even funny. But in the laughter of those righteous disciples in the distance, the huge and terrifying monster slowly raised its head and suddenly let out a roar. The huge head opened its mouth, and a black air gushed out from it like a whirlwind, and rushed to the three in the air.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 168 red flame</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-168-red-flame/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 12:34:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-168-red-flame/</guid>
      <description>The young man in the sky had no expression, and his eyes swept the battlefield under his feet. Even when he saw the huge monsters who had guarded him fall down one by one, he seemed to have no movement, as if he had seen through the life and death for a long time.
When the wind blows, his figure slowly drops down from the dark clouds. The roar of beasts is more and more deafening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 167 fate</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-167-fate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 12:34:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-167-fate/</guid>
      <description>Like the lightning tearing the night and falling into the human world, the light column that gathers the great power of the Dharma falls from the sky, falls from the top of the White Bone Demon snake, and goes straight in from the top of the head. In an instant, a huge force burst out from the huge body, and several Qingyun disciples swimming around were pushed far away by the invisible and qualitative air flow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 166 forbidden areas</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-166-forbidden-areas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 12:33:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-166-forbidden-areas/</guid>
      <description>It looks like an endless torrent of monsters, which rush on like waves after wave. With those huge monsters as arrows, they hit the light curtain of people in the right way. Seeing the light curtain crumbling, it seemed that the young disciples&amp;rsquo; faces were beginning to show some fear. Xiao Yicai frowned, knowing that if they didn&amp;rsquo;t repel these monsters, they would be out of control.
Xiao Yicai immediately gave a big drink and called on the disciples around him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 165 fighting</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-165-fighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 12:33:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-165-fighting/</guid>
      <description>A strong smell of blood enveloped the Tongtian peak of Qingyun Mountain. Even the lazy water unicorn, the spirit beast of Zhenshan, seemed anxious at the moment, swimming back and forth in the cold water pool, making a low roar. But standing in the Yuqing hall, the noble people of the right path, one by one, looked at the foot of the mountain. After Hongqiao is the huge Yunhai square. At this moment, a fierce and cruel battle has been going on there for a day and a night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 164 The Moon</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-164-the-moon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 12:33:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-164-the-moon/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Master, what&amp;rsquo;s wrong with you? What happened&amp;hellip; &amp;quot;
Lin Jingyu rushes to Wan Jianyi&amp;rsquo;s side and kneels down. His hands are shaking and he wants to help him up. However, the place where he starts is soft, and a cold comes from his heart. Lin Jingyu seems to be in a bottomless ice cellar. Where he touches his hands, there is no bone in the old man that is complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 163 conspiracy</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-163-conspiracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 12:33:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-163-conspiracy/</guid>
      <description>In the morning, the cool wind on Qingyun Mountain gently blows, turning the mist of a mountain slowly, like a gauze floating in the dense forest. Outside the ancestral hall of the three trigeminal Road, GUI Li, Mr. GUI and the old sweeper stand in a triangle, facing each other in a delicate atmosphere.
The wrinkles on the old man&amp;rsquo;s face moved and his hoarse voice said slowly, &amp;ldquo;you are not from Qingyun Mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 162 the Hermit</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-162-the-hermit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 12:32:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-162-the-hermit/</guid>
      <description>The rain stopped for the time being, but the dark clouds in the sky were still very low, layer by layer, which made people feel breathless.
The north gate of Heyang city was opened, and countless people poured out of the city and went northward. Crying was heard all the way. No one knows where the road ahead is?
Xiao Yicai led the disciples of Qingyun to maintain order all the way, constantly comforting the worried and panicked people, telling people around again and again that this time is just a temporary departure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 161 loneliness</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-161-loneliness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 12:32:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-161-loneliness/</guid>
      <description>The low hissing and roaring came from all directions. On the plain 200 miles away from Qingyun Mountain, more and more strange beasts gathered in southern Xinjiang, and some of them kept roaring to the sky. Among the herds, there are six or seven monsters, which are especially huge, far more than the surrounding ordinary beasts. They are standing in the herd and roaring, and the surrounding demons seem to be particularly afraid of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 160 struggle</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-160-struggle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 21:39:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-160-struggle/</guid>
      <description>In the early morning, when the sky was just bright, the sky around Qingyun Mountain was covered with dark clouds, and rain drops soon fell. The rain increased from a small age, and soon became gray between the sky and the earth. The sound of rain was everywhere, enveloping the towering mountains in a water mist, which was hazy and mysterious.
The sound of rain beating green bamboo leaves seems to have not changed for thousands of years, and it always seems lonely on Qingyun Mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 159 Secrets</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-159-secrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 21:39:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-159-secrets/</guid>
      <description>In the face of the ghost, although Mr. ghost still did not appear from the coffin, he was obviously more cautious. The ghost fire in the air was silent burning, and gradually became bright and bigger, reflecting the faces around him turning green.
Staring at the dark green light, he stepped on a step without expression. Almost at the moment when the ghost&amp;rsquo;s body was moving, the ghost fire seemed to be stimulated by something, and suddenly it was full of light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 158 ghost Road</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-158-ghost-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 21:39:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-158-ghost-road/</guid>
      <description>Zhou Yixian and other three were shocked. In this gloomy night, they only felt that their backs were like thorns and their hair was standing up. A faint green fire in that room was burning quietly, and the light was slowly emanating from the cracks of the house. It was strange and unpredictable. With the sound of the night wind around, it was more and more like the sound of ghost crying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 157 night exploration</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-157-night-exploration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 21:39:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-157-night-exploration/</guid>
      <description>The man in black standing at the door was a mysterious figure of the guiwangzong. The wild dog Taoist lived in the guiwangzong for a period of time after being taken over by the ghost. He had seen him several times. Although he still knew little about what Mr. ghost looked like, he understood that he was a very important person and was not a person he could compare with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 156 worship</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-156-worship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 21:38:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-156-worship/</guid>
      <description>Xiao Yicai lowered his voice, and his face became a little dignified and said, &amp;ldquo;my teacher asked me to ask martial uncle, is everything still in good condition?&amp;rdquo;
Tian is not easy to change his face. He suddenly stands up and stares at Xiao Yicai. Xiao Yicai also slowly stands up, but he takes a step back. Tian Bu Yi looks at Xiao Yi for a long time. His face changes constantly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 155 former residence</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-155-former-residence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 21:38:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-155-former-residence/</guid>
      <description>Morning, another day.
At the entrance of Sanfu Town, GUI Li stood face to face with the young man. Xiao Hui was lying on his shoulder, and the evil beast Taotie was following him, looking bored.
The young man took a fierce look and said with a smile, &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s rare to get together. I don&amp;rsquo;t know when to see you again. Take care of yourself.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;So are you,&amp;rdquo; he said</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 154 drinking at night</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-154-drinking-at-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 21:38:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-154-drinking-at-night/</guid>
      <description>Huqishan, the ice stone chamber.
GUI Li silently looks at the Biyao lying on the ice stone platform, the woman sleeping in the curling white smoke. The corner of her mouth seems to always have a trace of smile. Can she still feel at the moment, but does she know that someone is guarding her side?
Or, in her heart, she had no regrets, so she fell asleep peacefully?
He never knew the answer and didn&amp;rsquo;t dare to think about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 153 unfilial</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-153-unfilial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 21:37:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-153-unfilial/</guid>
      <description>Qingyun Mountain leads to Tianfeng and Yuqing hall.
&amp;ldquo;What?&amp;rdquo; With incredible astonishment, daoxuan real man blurted out: &amp;ldquo;the three big faction of the demon sect have been in a decisive battle with the beast demon, the whole army has been destroyed?&amp;rdquo;
Standing at the head of the three current orthodox leaders, and many of the elders sitting or standing beside them, Xiao Yicai, FA Xiang, Lu Xueqi and other orthodox disciples who came back to Qingyun Mountain did not speak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 152 Purgatory</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-152-purgatory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 21:37:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-152-purgatory/</guid>
      <description>Huqishan, the main hall of the ghost King sect of the demon sect, is shrouded in a mass of killing. More than half of the original powerful sect&amp;rsquo;s staff suddenly died, which is a heavy blow to any powerful sect in the world. So many hot blooded disciples set out to fight with high morale, but when they came back, there was only one ghost king with bloody body.
The lingering shadow appeared in the face and heart of everyone in Huqi mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 151 madness</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-151-madness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 21:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-151-madness/</guid>
      <description>Huqi mountain is the main hall of ghost king.
&amp;ldquo;Squeak, squeak!&amp;rdquo; Xiao Hui&amp;rsquo;s familiar cry sounded in the deep passage, and came out of the shadow. On his shoulder, Xiao Hui took the big wine bag and drank a few drinks. Then he cleverly tied up the mouth of the wine bag and dropped it down. There is a long and thin rope on the big wine bag, which is tied to the monkey like a condom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 150 poison</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-150-poison/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 21:22:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-150-poison/</guid>
      <description>Qingyun Mountain, Tongtian peak.
The fragrance of tea curls from the white teacup with green mouth and green cover, and the freshly brewed tea wafts with white air and spreads in the room.
This is a secluded room in the back hall of Yuqing hall. The three most powerful and famous people in the right way all gather in this room to enjoy tea business talks.
It turns out that when the three disciples of Zhenren Lanyun and Qingyun have left the room to wait for tea, they have already left behind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 149 civil strife</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-149-civil-strife/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 21:21:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-149-civil-strife/</guid>
      <description>The night gradually darkened, immersed in the invisible tension, the snake Valley seems to be slowly into sleep, dim lights slowly extinguished, except for the lonely soul hall.
The door of the shrine was still open, and the cold night wind blew through, blowing out the burning candles on the hall, casting strange shadows on the ground. In the distance outside, in the silence, it seems that there is something whispering, crying, laughing, and it seems that the wind is blowing the trees, which makes people not really listen to it, but feel a little chilly in their hearts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 148 Alliance</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-148-alliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 21:21:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-148-alliance/</guid>
      <description>Qingyun Mountain, Tongtian peak.
Outside the Yuqing hall, there are a large group of people standing closely. Looking at the past, they are all people of the right path, including immortal daoxuan, the leader of Qingyun, and Yun Yilan, the master of Fenxiang valley. Behind the two of them, other well-known figures of Qingyun and Huoxiang are standing here. Judging from the situation, it seems that they are going to meet someone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 147 poison trap</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-147-poison-trap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 21:20:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-147-poison-trap/</guid>
      <description>Thousands of miles away, is also the general night, that bright moon hanging in the sky, quietly looking at this earthly world.
On the wilderness, there was also a man who looked up at the cold moon. His robe and long sleeves were still in Taoist costume. On his angular face, his momentum of not being angry but powerful was still vaguely visible.
The night wind on the field is blowing, and the weeds are shaking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 146 meeting</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-146-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 21:20:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-146-meeting/</guid>
      <description>There was no sound, only the sound of branches bursting from time to time in the fire. The strange boy and the ghost didn&amp;rsquo;t speak any more. The flame was stretching and burning between them.
The surface color of the roast pig gradually turned into gold, and a slight burning smell appeared in the rich aroma. At this time, the surface of the whole roast pig was covered with a transparent layer of light oil drops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 145 chance encounter</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-145-chance-encounter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 21:20:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-145-chance-encounter/</guid>
      <description>The catastrophe started in spring and summer of that year. Thousands of years later, people in the world still remember clearly that period of horrible and crazy days.
In the extreme south of Southern Xinjiang, among the 100000 mountains, countless monsters suddenly swarmed out. They were bloodthirsty, and they killed people whenever they saw people. There were also many evil beasts who were greedy for human flesh, and the places they passed were appalling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 144 unwillingness</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-144-unwillingness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 21:19:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-144-unwillingness/</guid>
      <description>The forest gradually quieted down. A moment ago, the monsters who were still barking fiercely were scattered far away. The speed was so fast that Qinglong was really surprised. But in his mind, the reaction of the Golden Vase son when he saw this strange boy was even more elusive to him?
The young man&amp;rsquo;s eyes fell on both of them. He looked at them carefully and said, &amp;ldquo;are you Chinese?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 143 doomsday</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-143-doomsday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 21:19:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-143-doomsday/</guid>
      <description>Qingyunshan.
Tongtianfeng, ancestral hall.
The old man guarding the ancestral hall is still holding his broken broom in his hand, standing at the gate of the ancestral hall and looking out. There was a strange expression on the wrinkled face, which seemed to have some expectation and a little excitement.
The open space outside the hall is empty, but if you look carefully, you will find that there are many strange Charms around the open space than usual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 142 confusion</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-142-confusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 21:19:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-142-confusion/</guid>
      <description>Gray light from the edge of the cold teeth gently radiated, passing the dog Taoist&amp;rsquo;s face. The man lying in front of him is the murderer who destroyed the blood refining hall.
His eyes twinkled and he seemed to have some idea of fighting. However, this opportunity was once in a blue moon. What kind of person is the ghost in ordinary times? Taoist wild dog dare not think that he can kill this man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 141 killing the opportunity</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-141-killing-the-opportunity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 21:18:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-141-killing-the-opportunity/</guid>
      <description>On the Yuqing hall, daoxuan real man, with a dark green robe and a long beard, sits on the throne of the hall. On both sides of the seats are the first seats of other veins of Qingyun. It can be said that during the battle of Qingyun Mountain ten years ago, three of the seven veins of Qingyun gate changed their first seats. Compared with the time when Zhang Xiaofan and Lin Jingyu just arrived at Qingyun, things are different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 140 chance encounter</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-140-chance-encounter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 19:02:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-140-chance-encounter/</guid>
      <description>He put the dishes that had just come out of the pot and were still steaming on the table. Boss he returned to the back of the counter, opened the account book again and pretended to account, but his eyes turned slightly, and he looked at the customers in the shop from time to time.
Zhou Yixian, Xiaohuan and the wild dog Taoist priest are all sitting on the table of the three eyed grey monkey Xiaohui.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 139 decadence</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-139-decadence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 19:02:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-139-decadence/</guid>
      <description>A hundred thousand mountains, an ancient cave.
After the resurrection of the demon demon suppressing cave, the scene is quite different from that of the previous dark clouds and the howling wind. Although the sky is still dark, the black air gathered in the cave has dissipated, and the wind blowing from the cave has disappeared all year round.
In addition to the still barren mountains, only the statue woman standing at the entrance of Zhenmo ancient cave is still standing there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 138 the sad man</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-138-the-sad-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 19:02:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-138-the-sad-man/</guid>
      <description>Huqishan, the general Hall of ghost king.
It has been three days since the great wizard died. Qinglong has cremated the old man&amp;rsquo;s body and collected it in an urn of ashes. At the moment, the small blue and white urn was quietly placed on the table beside him.
Qinglong gazed at the urn for a long time, sighed and turned away. In the past three days, Qinglong and Youji have been responsible for all the affairs in the ghost King&amp;rsquo;s clan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 137 evoking souls</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-137-evoking-souls/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 19:01:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-137-evoking-souls/</guid>
      <description>In the cold stone room, only the great wizard&amp;rsquo;s low breath. The ghost king and GUI Li stood in front of the weak old man, staring at his old face tightly. At the moment, the remaining life of the great wizard was their only hope.
The great wizard gasped a little, raised his head, and laughed at them both. The ghost king was a little relieved. After pondering for a moment, the great wizard said to the ghost king, &amp;ldquo;please find some blood, and blood is the best way to attract ghosts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 136 strange skills</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-136-strange-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 19:01:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-136-strange-skills/</guid>
      <description>Incense Valley, chamber of secrets.
The primitive screen separated the space of the stone chamber. Shangguan CE, dressed in grey, stood quietly in place and waited patiently.
After a long time, the old voice of Yun Yilan, the master of the incense burning Valley, came from behind the screen: &amp;ldquo;I heard that younger martial brother, this time you tracked down Jiuwei Tianhu, and at the last minute, you suddenly ordered all the disciples to withdraw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 135 evil spirit</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-135-evil-spirit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 19:01:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-135-evil-spirit/</guid>
      <description>Two hundred Li to the north of &amp;ldquo;Xianyong mountain&amp;rdquo; in central Turkey is the tall &amp;ldquo;Huqi mountain&amp;rdquo;. Looking up from the foot of the mountain, you can see that the rock falls through the sky, which is abrupt and precipitous. However, there was no vegetation on the whole mountain, which was extremely desolate. On the left side of the mountain range, a river, called Shengshui, emerges from an underground spring in the middle of the mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 134 Resurrection</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-134-resurrection/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 19:00:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-134-resurrection/</guid>
      <description>The darkness is boundless, only the sound of the wind is more and more bleak. The Lich walked in the dark corridor of the ancient cave, just like a ghost walking towards the nine secluded places.
The older the cave is, the wider it becomes, but the darkness around it grows deeper. Walking on this cold and terrible Road, the Lich can even close its eyes and walk forward.
For many years, he wandered alone here, and now, he finally wants to change his own destiny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 133 evil spirits</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-133-evil-spirits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 19:00:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-133-evil-spirits/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Get out of my way! &amp;ldquo;The Lich was silent for a long time and said slowly.
The evil spirit looked at him coldly and said, &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t you regret before the goddess statue? &amp;quot;
The Lich&amp;rsquo;s black clothes moved slightly again. It seemed that he was very excited under the black clothes. However, he did not look back to see the stone statue woman.
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m right. My mother is wrong! &amp;ldquo;He said in an astringent voice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 132 farewell</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-132-farewell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 19:00:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-132-farewell/</guid>
      <description>Qilidong, an altar of Miao nationality.
The new day, as if even the sun shining on the altar platform, feel as if there is a new flavor. GUI Li and Xiao Bai stood on the platform in front of the altar in the middle of the mountain, looking at the land ravaged by the war.
Among the ruins that can be seen everywhere, Miao people come in and go out. From a high point of view, they are like ants busy for their own homes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 131 strange forest</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-131-strange-forest/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 19:00:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-131-strange-forest/</guid>
      <description>The great wizard was silent for a moment and said, &amp;ldquo;yes.&amp;rdquo;
There was a sharp silence.
We hope that you can help the common people to live and die
The corner of his eyes twitched for a moment and said, &amp;ldquo;the five ethnic groups in southern Xinjiang have a large population. Why do you have to ask for help from an outsider?&amp;rdquo;
The great wizard shook his head and said in a bleak voice: &amp;ldquo;since the division of the five clans, the witchcraft has been declining day by day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 130 Legends</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-130-legends/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:38:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-130-legends/</guid>
      <description>Qilidong, Miao people&amp;rsquo;s altar.
Last night&amp;rsquo;s war did not seem to affect the atmosphere of silence here. Under the leadership of the young wizard, GUI Li and Xiao Bai walked silently in the altar. Lying on the shoulder of the small ash, now seems to be a lot of quiet, as if the surrounding solemn atmosphere, let it also be honest.
Through the long corridor, to the stone house deep in the altar, the young wizard nodded slightly, did not say anything to them, turned around and walked away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 129 tracking</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-129-tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:38:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-129-tracking/</guid>
      <description>The sky gradually brightened up, and the fire which had been burning for a night in the Seven Mile cave finally subsided. It&amp;rsquo;s just that after the flame burns, all that remains is broken walls and smoky black wood.
Although the Dharma is high in humanity, he has been busy for a whole night, and there are some scorched marks on his body. Some disciples of the burning incense Valley who have a slightly lower level of Taoism also have some black ashes on their faces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 128 heart</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-128-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:37:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-128-heart/</guid>
      <description>All of them, hold their breath.
The figure, submerged in a huge white column of light, disappeared.
The woman in white standing in the cloud may be over exerting! It was also a stumbling, no longer able to maintain balance, slowly fell down.
But, but, where is the sudden laughter?
It&amp;rsquo;s so desolate, but extraordinary!
In the white light column, red as blood, the man was soaked in blood, like a maniac general, but out, looking up to the sky and howling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 127 the Lich</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-127-the-lich/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:37:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-127-the-lich/</guid>
      <description>The flame clouds in the sky gradually darkened, and ahetai was hidden in the dark clouds, and quickly and incomparably far away from qilidong.
Half an hour later, when he was sure that no foreign people would follow him, he slowly fell down to the cloud, returned to the ground, and landed in a valley.
At the moment, both the Li and the Miao are in a state of failure. However, ahetai seems not eager to find the remaining Li people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 126 sadness</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-126-sadness/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:37:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-126-sadness/</guid>
      <description>The flaming flame lights up the sky, and the gorgeous brilliance will shine like the day, even if it is a hundred miles away, you can still hear the roaring sound.
Looking at the distant place where the flashing red light and fireballs interweave, a group of people stopped in amazement.
More than one official in the burning incense Valley, led by Li Xun and Lv Shun, together with Lu Xueqi of Qingyun gate and FA Xiang of Tianyin temple, were watching the disorderly place on the ancient road 100 li away from qilidong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 125 black fire</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-125-black-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:37:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-125-black-fire/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Dong, Dong, Dong&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
There was a knock on the door, but there was no one outside. Grimly frowned, walked over and opened the door.
Standing at the door was a 13-4-year-old Miao boy with a childish look on his face. He carried a basket in his hand with some meat, wine and vegetables in the middle. It seems that the leader of tumagu clan sent someone to deliver food.
The boy handed the basket over and nodded grimly, &amp;ldquo;thank you very much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 124 the Li Nationality</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-124-the-li-nationality/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:36:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-124-the-li-nationality/</guid>
      <description>Qilidong, the border area of Southern Xinjiang.
Miao altar.
Deep in the dark and silent hall, the still sober ghost and the great wizard did not speak. Only the burning fire made a crackling sound from time to time. In addition, in the quiet altar, there is a strange sound.
Monkey Xiaohui was drunk, and now he was sleeping soundly and snoring.
In the past, GUI Li was often with Xiao Hui, but he didn&amp;rsquo;t realize that Xiao Hui would snore when he was sleeping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 123 the altar</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-123-the-altar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:36:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-123-the-altar/</guid>
      <description>GUI Li was stunned, but I saw the tenderness in Xiaobai&amp;rsquo;s eyes. He was so watery that he reflected his figure and face. He couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but jump in his heart.
&amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re drunk.&amp;rdquo; When he said this, he couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but have a little sweat on his head.
Xiaobai&amp;rsquo;s body, at this moment, seems to have been completely unable to stand, all the weight is leaning on the ghost. But see her white teeth gently bit a red lip, lazy there is a trace of tender pity, the mouth of a low voice * *, as if hook people&amp;rsquo;s soul general amorous feelings, slowly, her head against the ghostly shoulder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 122 liquor</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-122-liquor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:36:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-122-liquor/</guid>
      <description>A group of Miao people walked down the mountain. Looking at it, GUI Li and Xiao Bai saw seven or eight strong Miao soldiers surrounded by an old man in his early fifties.
It was the old man who gave out the loud drink just now.
The surrounding Miao soldiers saluted one after another, and the excited crowd suddenly quieted down, and they bowed their heads to pay homage to the old man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 121 qilidong</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-121-qilidong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:35:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-121-qilidong/</guid>
      <description>Into the narrow mountain road, winding, on both sides of the hard stone wall, from time to time there are sudden rocks stabbing out, a careless, just afraid of the head will hit.
And looking around the stone wall, there are many drops of water in many places, and the most places also converge into a small pool. Stone walls, dark places, but also gave birth to a lot of turquoise moss, so that the air filled with a micro moist cold taste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 120 tracing</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-120-tracing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 11:00:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-120-tracing/</guid>
      <description>Burning grain.
Tianxiangju.
This is a quiet place deep in the burning Valley, built close to the mountains. Surrounded by high walls on three sides, only the front door is hidden, making people not clear the scene inside.
In spite of the great changes that have taken place in the incense Valley these days, there are still no disciples of the incense Valley nearby, because this is the residence of the leader of the incense Valley, Yun Yilan, and the place where he is closed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 119 deep mark</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-119-deep-mark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 11:00:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-119-deep-mark/</guid>
      <description>There was silence all around.
The night is deep, and it&amp;rsquo;s a sad time.
The long street is silent, and the bright moon is hanging in the sky. Under the clear light, the two people standing on the desolate street will pull out their long shadows.
What kind of emotions, like thousands of words entangled in the heart, just face, but can not open up.
Late night lonely wind, gently blowing clothes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 118 cold night</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-118-cold-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 10:59:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-118-cold-night/</guid>
      <description>The southern border area is quite different from the customs of China and Turkey. It is only for many years. Although it is located in a remote place, it still has exchanges with China and Turkey. And the fur, ore and other specialties produced in the south of Xinjiang have always had a good reputation in the Central Plains, attracting many Chinese and Turkish businessmen to trade.
Over time, the Inns that had not existed in southern Xinjiang also appeared in the most bustling towns under the influence of the Chinese and Turkish merchants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 117 Tianshui stronghold</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-117-tianshui-stronghold/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 10:59:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-117-tianshui-stronghold/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t know whether the sky in southern Xinjiang is always so cloudy in this season. After coming out from that small mountain, under the guidance of Xiaobai, two people and a monkey go to the west of the burning incense valley.
That night, the volcano erupted in the xuanhuotan of the burning incense valley. The heaven and the earth changed. It was very powerful. There was induction within a hundred miles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 116 hope</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-116-hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 10:59:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-116-hope/</guid>
      <description>The body of the ghost was shocked, and the expression of instant ecstasy came to his face, which would be solidified on his face for a long time. Reluctantly restrain the excited mood, but still can&amp;rsquo;t control the slight shaking in the voice, &amp;ldquo;please, please teach me!&amp;rdquo;
Nine tail sky fox is gazing at him, after a moment suddenly smile, way: &amp;ldquo;that woman must be the person that you love deeply?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 115 getting out of trouble</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-115-getting-out-of-trouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 10:59:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-115-getting-out-of-trouble/</guid>
      <description>XuanHuo altar
The majestic and almost indestructible huge altar suddenly began to shake violently. Nine Tailed Tianhu and Xiaohui, who are on the third floor of xuanhuotan, are all shaken aside by this sudden huge force. But after all, they are all psychic animals, and soon they are stable.
In the dark depth of the front, the dark red light gradually brightened up, showing a ghostly figure.
The XuanHuo chain, which is bound to the waist of the Nine Tailed Tianhu, gradually becomes bright from the deep dark red color to the bright color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 114 white fox</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-114-white-fox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 10:58:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-114-white-fox/</guid>
      <description>China is vast and vast. In addition to the people who are called the spirits of all things, there are also countless people born in this world. Such as poultry, chickens, pigs and dogs, beasts such as wolves, tigers and leopards, are familiar to people.
Since ancient times, there have been a lot of anecdotes and legends in the world. In the wild and remote places of Shenzhou, among the poor mountains and rivers, there are some ancient beasts, wild Taoism, and human remains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 113 Tianhu</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-113-tianhu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 10:58:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-113-tianhu/</guid>
      <description>The fire beast looked up at the small ash surrounded by the golden awn in the air. After a while, the whole hall suddenly roared, and the temperature suddenly rose, just like the sea of fire.
In the roar, his attention was obviously shifted from the fierce side to Xiaohui. He stepped on the ground with all his arms and legs and jumped up to Xiaohui. Its whole body is ablaze with flames, even the mysterious flame totem diaphragm that is constantly rotating behind it is as bright as a fire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 112 foreign animals</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-112-foreign-animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 10:58:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-112-foreign-animals/</guid>
      <description>XuanHuo altar.
Although it&amp;rsquo;s a wooden door, it still feels heavy. Under the fierce force, the heavy and thick door on the XuanHuo altar makes a dull &amp;ldquo;squeak&amp;rdquo; and slowly pushes it open.
In the door, a light red light came out, and the air around seemed to rise a little bit, extremely hot and dry.
The ghost Li frowned and saw sweat on his forehead. He suddenly remembered what he had heard just now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 111 assassination</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-111-assassination/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 10:57:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-111-assassination/</guid>
      <description>Looking in the dark, GUI Li saw the old man&amp;rsquo;s face was clear and thin. He was dressed in a grey robe. He was simple and simple. He had a calm manner. There was nothing outstanding. If you walk on the streets of ordinary towns, no one will recognize him as a man of cultivation.
But look at the two people behind him, not to mention Yan Hong, is Li Xun, who has always been proud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 110 XuanHuo altar</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-110-xuanhuo-altar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 20:17:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-110-xuanhuo-altar/</guid>
      <description>Ghost Li left the dead porpoise in the corner of the wall, and looked at the hole where the porpoise was. As expected, a very thin line was drawn out of the hole and connected to a bell in the distance. I think he and jinpinger have repeatedly failed to infiltrate in the past few days. They were all found by this little grey dolphin.
He once read and recorded in the fragmented script &amp;ldquo;different spirits&amp;rdquo; in the secret collection of the ghost King School.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 109 stealth</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-109-stealth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 20:17:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-109-stealth/</guid>
      <description>The mountains in southern Xinjiang are quite different from those in the Central Plains, which are a little less beautiful and secluded, and a little more majestic and precipitous.
Under the night, a series of rolling mountains stand towering, crisscross, far away, it is a sense of annihilation.
With his hand in his hand, he stood up and looked up. There were two lower hills and a relatively flat wilderness. Suddenly, four tall peaks rose up on the earth, which were linked to form a valley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 108 magic array</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-108-magic-array/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 20:16:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-108-magic-array/</guid>
      <description>Huqishan.
The main hall of the ghost King sect is located.
Under the desolate mountains, the general Hall of the ghost king is hidden in the hard caves. In the winding tunnel, in a deep and quiet place, there is no one in the long tunnel. Only the stone walls on both sides are inlaid with a copper lamp every few feet, illuminating some places.
You Ji, with a black veil on her face, wanders forward alone, looking like a ghost in the dark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 107 ancient temples</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-107-ancient-temples/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 20:16:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-107-ancient-temples/</guid>
      <description>The evil land in the south of the vast land of Shenzhou is said to be rich in poisonous insects and beasts. The most obvious boundary between the Central Plains and the Central Plains is in the extreme south. Suddenly, it rises like a flat land. The tall and lofty mountains are connected one by one, towering into the clouds and separating the north and the south.
Since ancient times, few people in the rich land of the Central Plains have gone to the south of Xinjiang for no other reason.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 106 inquiry</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-106-inquiry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 20:16:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-106-inquiry/</guid>
      <description>The wind is bleak, the ancient road is bleak, and it stretches forward lonely.
On Monday, Xian and her granddaughter Xiaohuan had left zuoze and headed east for three days.
In the middle of the day, they still walk on the ancient road, but the original flat wilderness on both sides of the ancient road has been replaced by more and more hills and forests.
Zhou Yixian looked forward and saw a broken stone pavilion on the road not far ahead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--105 Octopus monster</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-105-octopus-monster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 20:15:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-105-octopus-monster/</guid>
      <description>The dead swamp, the top of the great tree.
Lu Xueqi, FA Xiang, Lin Jingyu and Zeng Shushu slowly fell on a huge tree trunk which was in a mess. They saw cracks and numerous branches around. Even after a long time, they still made people shrug and move towards the fight between the two ancient giants.
But at this moment, their attention is obviously more focused on the people in front of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 104 Xiaohui</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-104-xiaohui/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 20:15:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-104-xiaohui/</guid>
      <description>He opened his eyes slowly in the dark.
Around a dark, and then, not far ahead, slowly lit up a faint light, like a faint candle in the night, quietly burning.
He looked at it silently. The light was light lavender, then turning blue, then slowly turning dark green. Then he kept changing and flashing all kinds of lights. It was very beautiful.
&amp;ldquo;Squeak, squeak&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
All of a sudden, just beside him, there was the low voice of the little grey monkey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 103 yellow birds</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-103-yellow-birds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 20:15:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-103-yellow-birds/</guid>
      <description>The trunk shakes even more. Even this incredible tree, under the huge body of black water snake, seems to be shaking.
It seems that it is an evil beast from ancient times. The black water black snake wraps its huge body around the trunk of the tree. Where it passes, its branches and leaves are in a mess, and the vines and flowers are withered and broken one after another. It wags its head and wags its tail to move forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 102 black snake</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-102-black-snake/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 20:14:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-102-black-snake/</guid>
      <description>The wind blows, countless flowers shake together.
Lu Xueqi stood in the sea of flowers with no expression, silently looking at the ghost that landed opposite her.
Faint fragrance, dark floating.
Ghost Li lightly shrugged his shoulders, small ash swished from his shoulders, opened his eyes to see the master, looked at Lu Xueqi in the opposite direction, grabbed his head, and ran to one side.
His eyes fell on the tall stone gate behind Lu Xueqi, and he suddenly smiled and said, &amp;ldquo;this is what we are looking for?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 101 personal feelings</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-101-personal-feelings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 20:14:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-101-personal-feelings/</guid>
      <description>In addition to the dead water, on the ancient road to the West from Dawang village, on Monday, Xianhe and Xiaohuan walked slowly.
Xiaohuan&amp;rsquo;s bright eyes looked around, only to see that the ancient road was overgrown with weeds and desolate. I walked out of Dawang village for a long time, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t even see a human figure.
Looking from afar, I can see that this place is located in the wilderness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 100 giant trees</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-100-giant-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 20:32:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-100-giant-trees/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s getting brighter.
The rain stopped and the wind stopped. The first light of the morning came down through the thick clouds in the sky and the mist floating in the dead water.
The forest is full of silence, but slowly, with the light, gradually began to make noise. In the unknown place, there was the first bird song. All of a sudden, the whole forest seemed to wake up from the deep sleep of the night, or far or near, full of early morning cheers, to welcome the new day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 99 strange omens</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-99-strange-omens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 20:32:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-99-strange-omens/</guid>
      <description>It rained in the sky.
The rain is not big, and the sky is a little yellow. It has been raining for the second day in a row.
Xiao Yicai frowned tightly, turned his head suddenly, and said to the nearby man, &amp;ldquo;younger martial sister Yan, do you have any discovery?&amp;rdquo;
It was Yan Hong in the burning incense Valley who stood with him. Xiao Yicai entered the neize after all the people were separated in the miasma on that day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 98 the old meaning</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-98-the-old-meaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 20:31:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-98-the-old-meaning/</guid>
      <description>Qin Wuyan&amp;rsquo;s eyes turned, and he looked at the four people who were equal in law one by one. From his eyes, he naturally saw that these four people were outstanding talents. If he acted according to the real way, he was afraid that he would not get benefits from them.
It&amp;rsquo;s just that the ten thousand poisons sect has always been practicing the eccentric sword. There are so many strange methods or devious ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 97 night talk</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-97-night-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 20:31:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-97-night-talk/</guid>
      <description>The three of them were silent for a while, or Zeng Shushu was lively and smart. Seeing the embarrassment between Lin Jingyu and FA Xiang, they started with a smile and said, &amp;ldquo;brother Lin, how did you come?&amp;rdquo;
Although Lin Jingyu and Zeng Shushu are not very familiar, they first get close to each other when they see their classmates in such a strange place. Secondly, he knows that Zeng Shushu and Zhang Xiaofan were good friends at that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 96 strange flowers</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-96-strange-flowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 20:31:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-96-strange-flowers/</guid>
      <description>Dawang village.
Xiaohuan stood at the entrance of the village and looked at him with some worry. He saw only the direction of him. In the morning, there was still a clear sky. Now it was getting dark. It seemed that there would be another heavy rain.
Late last night, she and her grandfather, Zhou Xian and Jin pinger, were in the dead water together. But after Jin pinger went out for a visit, she looked very tired and sent them out of the dead water overnight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 95 miasma</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-95-miasma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 20:30:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-95-miasma/</guid>
      <description>The wind passes through the dead water.
At the foot of the water grass fluttering, water ripples, at a glance, boundless, although no one angry, but another moving scenery.
Soul devouring sends out a light dark blue light. The light flows and stops in the middle of the sky. Ghost Li body in its, hand and stand, staring at the front.
This day is a rare good weather in the dead river.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 94 the end</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-94-the-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 20:30:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-94-the-end/</guid>
      <description>The night is dark and cold.
Suddenly, a ray of light crossed in the dark, flying quickly and incomparably from afar, but from afar, the light seemed to tremble faintly, showing signs of instability.
On the ground, Meng Ji is walking back and forth anxiously. Behind him are the remaining disciples of the longevity hall. Roughly speaking, there are about fifty or sixty people. They look scared one by one and look forward to the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 93 yellow finches</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-93-yellow-finches/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 20:30:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-93-yellow-finches/</guid>
      <description>All of a sudden, things suddenly changed in the dark. The disciples of the longevity hall were shocked for a moment, and didn&amp;rsquo;t react immediately.
In this moment of lightning and stone fire, the people who had been prepared for the right path appeared one after another, and each of them controlled the magic weapon and killed them. It&amp;rsquo;s a great advantage to kill those who don&amp;rsquo;t want to. All the disciples here are excellent successors from all schools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 92 Mantis</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-92-mantis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 20:29:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-92-mantis/</guid>
      <description>The wild dog Taoist followed Guili and walked to the deep of the dead water.
Because just after a heavy rain, the soft land is now more muddy. But somehow, after meeting Qin Wuyan and Jin pinger just now, he insisted that he would not control the magic weapon again, but walk on the ground.
It seems that, like the Golden Vase, he is secretly afraid of something.
In the past, even though the wild dog Taoist didn&amp;rsquo;t swear, at least he complained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 91 good people and wild dogs</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-91-good-people-and-wild-dogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 20:29:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-91-good-people-and-wild-dogs/</guid>
      <description>In the dead water, with more and more rain, the wind is blowing gradually.
The fur on little grey monkey&amp;rsquo;s body is wet. It&amp;rsquo;s attached to his body. Now he curls up and hides in Xiao Huan&amp;rsquo;s arms motionless. He only has a pair of smart eyes. He still drips and turns. He looks at the distance and Xiao Huan.
The rain fell all over the sky, and the originally dark swamp was now more gray, and the surrounding area was gray.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 90 death</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-90-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 17:20:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-90-death/</guid>
      <description>The sky is gray, and it seems to be very low. There is a murky wind that doesn&amp;rsquo;t know where it comes from. When it blows over the body, it makes people feel chilly.
There is a faint path between the marshes where there are many weeds. It extends to the inside.
Zeng Shushu and other disciples of Qingyun sect stood at the entrance of the death swamp and looked inside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 89 look at the picture</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-89-look-at-the-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 17:20:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-89-look-at-the-picture/</guid>
      <description>Xiaohuan frowned slightly, but a pair of eyes gradually brightened up. She carefully looked at the white paper in her hand, and the three words &amp;ldquo;Qin Wuyan&amp;rdquo; on it were written with neat workmanship, upright and mellow strokes, and the connection corner was introverted and smooth, which was quite beautiful.
Xiaohuan blinked, smiled suddenly, and said: &amp;ldquo;my guest, your name has&amp;rdquo; Yan &amp;ldquo;, which is the power of double fire to Yang, but in the middle of the word&amp;rdquo; no &amp;ldquo;to suppress, turning around, it&amp;rsquo;s Yin and soft; and the word&amp;rdquo; Qin &amp;ldquo;lies in the west, and the Lord, you go to the west, where it&amp;rsquo;s Yin and cold!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 88 Dawang Village</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-88-dawang-village/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 17:19:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-88-dawang-village/</guid>
      <description>White hair and sideburns are growing, and age is like water!
The ghost King took his eyes away from the mirror like water, sighed a little, turned around, smiled and said, &amp;ldquo;I haven&amp;rsquo;t looked in the mirror for a long time, but I see more white hair today.&amp;rdquo;
Standing behind him, the ghost face was expressionless, and said lightly, &amp;ldquo;you have more than one heart.&amp;rdquo;
At the moment, there is a small lake in Huqi mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 87 old land</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-87-old-land/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 17:19:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-87-old-land/</guid>
      <description>Qingyun Mountain, Dazhu peak.
The cloud is ethereal in the mountains, like the gentle white ribbon, changing gently. In the early morning, the moist air and the fresh and cool wind swept over the green bamboo forest and the mountain top of Dazhu peak.
The building centered on Shoujing hall stands quietly in the morning light. Everything seems so peaceful
Just a burst of barking sound suddenly came, mixed with &amp;ldquo;squeak&amp;rdquo; in the middle, breaking the silence here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 86 long journey</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-86-long-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 17:19:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-86-long-journey/</guid>
      <description>There was silence all around, as if the only sound echoed in my ears was my own fierce heartbeat, and the fear of the unknown death was like endless cold water, drowning the wild dog.
He couldn&amp;rsquo;t help shivering
Countless pairs of eyes staring at the figure, it is very poor and lonely, but he accidentally insisted, shaking hands holding the black heart, still very tight, very tight.
This appearance suddenly had some familiarity, as if many years ago, that stubborn and stoic young man had inexplicable persistence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 85 ten years</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-85-ten-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 17:18:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-85-ten-years/</guid>
      <description>Black clouds hover in the night sky. The sky is dark as if it is pressing against the ground. The rain falling from the sky rolls over the vast land in the wind.
In the wilderness, there is no village before and no village behind. There is only one ancient road extending from afar, and it extends to the distance alone.
In the dark clouds of the night sky, there was a low thunder sound, and the rain between the heaven and the earth gradually increased.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 84 blood curse</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-84-blood-curse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 17:18:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-84-blood-curse/</guid>
      <description>The angry scolding finally subsided. FA Xiang doesn&amp;rsquo;t care about other people at all, even the murderous dragon cutting sword in Lin Jingyu&amp;rsquo;s hands doesn&amp;rsquo;t look at it. His eyes only look at Zhang Xiaofan, which is not only worried, but also lamented.
When everyone was completely quiet, the Dharma phase slowly went on.
&amp;ldquo;The murderer is my third martial uncle, a master of wisdom among the four great monks.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 83 old evils</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-83-old-evils/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 17:18:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-83-old-evils/</guid>
      <description>They made a mess and helped immortal daoxuan into the Yuqing palace. However, at this moment, the Yuqing palace is already in a state of disrepair. At this moment, more than half of the original majestic buildings collapsed, and there are broken stones and wood everywhere.
Tian is not easy to wait for young disciples to quickly organize a space, drag a chair from the side, and let immortal daoxuan sit down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 82 ancient sword</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-82-ancient-sword/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 17:17:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-82-ancient-sword/</guid>
      <description>The bright light in the direction of the magic moon cave is more and more bright and dazzling, accompanied by a faint and deep sound of different roars.
The haggard old man standing in front of the ancestral hall stared at the brilliant light and was stunned until Lin Jingyu asked him, &amp;ldquo;old master, is that the treasure of Qingyun sect, the ancient sword
The old man nodded silently, and suddenly turned around, as if he didn&amp;rsquo;t want to pay attention to anything more, and said in a low voice: &amp;ldquo;once the immortal is killed, it&amp;rsquo;s on the Qingyun Mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 81 ancestral hall</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-81-ancestral-hall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 17:17:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-81-ancestral-hall/</guid>
      <description>There are two important places in the back mountain of Qingyun Mountain. One is the most important holy land of Qingyun gate, the magic moon cave. The amazing founder of Qingyun gate thousands of years ago closed his door and became the leader of the world.
After the founder of Qingye, the magic moon cave became the most sacred place of Qingyun sect. For thousands of years, only the leader could enter here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 80 calculation in progress</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-80-calculation-in-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 17:16:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-80-calculation-in-progress/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Who? &amp;quot;
At the same time, there were several loud voices of Qingyun disciples outside the Yuqing hall, but only a few of them were brushed. It seemed that some high-ranking people came to fight against the sky. Then there were several thumps. Several Qingyun disciples fell in and rolled to the ground.
At the door, there are four figures. They are the four masters of the demon sect.
Yuyangzi and poison God stood in the middle, the ghost king and Sanmiao fairy stood on both sides, four people looked at the hall and walked in slowly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 79 Xiaoqiang</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-79-xiaoqiang/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 19:07:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-79-xiaoqiang/</guid>
      <description>Above the hall, immortal daoxuan hasn&amp;rsquo;t come back, but there are whispers among all the people.
When Shuiyue and his three disciples came back, they saw that they were separated, but Zhang Xiaofan was still kneeling on the ground alone. Lu Xueqi seemed to hesitate for a moment, but after Shuiyue&amp;rsquo;s stern eyes swept over, she finally stood behind her in silence.
A moment later, immortal daoxuan came out of the back hall slowly and returned to his seat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 78 interrogation</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-78-interrogation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 19:07:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-78-interrogation/</guid>
      <description>After crossing the threshold, a solemn and solemn air suddenly came to you. The most sacred place in Qingyun gate is still as magnificent and amazing as before.
There are many people standing and sitting on the huge hall, but somehow, what Zhang Xiaofan saw at the first sight was not these people, but in the deepest part of the hall, he saw the Sanqing God in the shadow so far away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 77 loss</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-77-loss/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 19:06:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-77-loss/</guid>
      <description>The bamboo shadow is whirling, and the sun is shining down, and it falls on the open space in the bamboo forest.
Zhang Xiaofan looked at the bamboo forest in the distance and said in a low voice: &amp;ldquo;actually, I sometimes think I&amp;rsquo;m stupid. Elder martial sister she obviously likes elder martial brother Qihao, but I still However, at that time, I saw her standing in front of Kui Niu, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to think, so I rushed up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 76 mind</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-76-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 19:06:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-76-mind/</guid>
      <description>On the bamboo peak of Qingyun Mountain.
Zhang Xiaofan sat in his room, stunned.
It was a sunny afternoon. Soft light came from the window of the room and sprinkled on the bluestone floor inside. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s because there&amp;rsquo;s some lazy breath in the air. The rhubarb and ash in this room are also a little lazy at the moment.
Rhubarb lies at Zhang Xiaofan&amp;rsquo;s feet, buries his head on his two front feet, his eyes are half closed, his ears are drooped down, his whole body is up and down, only his glossy tail swings from time to time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 75 conspiracy</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-75-conspiracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 19:06:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-75-conspiracy/</guid>
      <description>See blue clouds again.
When Zhang Xiaofan saw Qingyun Mountain again, it was several months since he went down with Lu Xueqi, Qi Hao and Zeng Shushu last time.
The mountain, which is still towering and straight into the cloud, is still ethereal and solemn, but Zhang Xiaofan&amp;rsquo;s situation has completely changed.
After discussing with Taoist Cangsong and xiaoyicai, Zhang Xiaofan was temporarily taken back to dazhufeng by Tian, and Taoist Cangsong and xiaoyicai went back to report to Taoist XuanZhen, the leader, in detail, before making a decision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 74 You Ji</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-74-you-ji/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 19:05:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-74-you-ji/</guid>
      <description>This dream seems to have passed another millennium.
He walked alone in the dark until he saw the village, where the sun was shining and familiar. He galloped away, the familiar faces smiling at him, joking.
The fresh air seemed sweet to his heart. He could not help rolling freely on the grass near the village and laughing heartily.
All around, suddenly, there were many more children, who rushed over. The always bright surprised feather laughed and said, &amp;ldquo;do you agree with this, or not?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 73 desperate situation</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-73-desperate-situation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 19:05:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-73-desperate-situation/</guid>
      <description>The red light curtain suddenly trembled. The ghost king and other people in black, including the trapped Kui Niu, almost turned around at the same time.
The red light flashed, and Tian linger was shocked. However, he saw the red light around the dark red iron tap trembling, but it was still under the protection of the red light.
In a moment, all the people around had already responded. The people in black rushed to Tian ling&amp;rsquo;er one after another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 72 Kui Niu</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-72-kui-niu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 19:05:17 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-72-kui-niu/</guid>
      <description>Like a sudden rain falling from the dark night sky, and in the deep sea far away, waves of strong winds, like wild animals breaking through their cages, roared to this lonely island in the boundless sea.
The wind and rain, overwhelming over, in a flash, these people fell into the wind and rain.
Zhang Xiaofan, following the crowd, stopped and raised his hand to cover the urgent wind and rain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 71 ambush</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-71-ambush/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 19:04:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-71-ambush/</guid>
      <description>These five people are all born under the Qingyun gate. At this moment, they are flying fast with magic weapons. However, in a moment, under the light of all magic weapons, they have seen the end of the forest edge in front of them, and even farther, the sea in the dark night.
The sea breeze comes, along with the whistling, reverberates in this late night.
The hearts of all the people are full of joy and spirit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 70 past events</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-70-past-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 18:45:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-70-past-events/</guid>
      <description>In the forest in the middle of the night, the light that has been emitted by countless magic weapons is like the day. From the depths of the forest to the most intense open space, it seems that there are sharp lights flying everywhere. Under the colorful and beautiful light, the bright red blood is constantly rising and sprayed on the slightly trembling trees.
It coagulates into blood beads and drips silently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 69 Qinglong</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-69-qinglong/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 18:44:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-69-qinglong/</guid>
      <description>At this time, someone had come to hold the old blood sucking demon. The bald old man seemed to have a lot of friendship with the old blood sucking demon. He came to him and asked him something in a low voice. The ghost king came out empty, smiling but speechless, with a relaxed expression and no sense of hostility at all. The white faced scholar standing next to him looked at him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 68 red flame</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-68-red-flame/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 18:44:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-68-red-flame/</guid>
      <description>The old blood sucking demon snorted, but there was no fear at all. His haggard face was fierce. He said, &amp;ldquo;in those days, you righteous people, but depending on the large number of people, do I really fear you? &amp;quot;
As soon as his hands vibrated, the red flashing skull in front of him &amp;ldquo;whine&amp;rdquo; across the air, flying rapidly around him, and his eyes began to turn red.
It&amp;rsquo;s not easy for Tian to breathe deeply and be alert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 67 blood sucking old demon</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-67-blood-sucking-old-demon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 18:44:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-67-blood-sucking-old-demon/</guid>
      <description>This hideous old man is an old devil in the demon sect who has been hidden for many years. He is called &amp;ldquo;the blood sucking ancestor&amp;rdquo;. People in the right way, including many people in the demon sect, privately call him &amp;ldquo;the blood sucking old devil&amp;rdquo;. The main reason for this is that the &amp;ldquo;blood sucking method&amp;rdquo; of the evil sect he practiced is to suck the blood essence of the living people into the body before he can practice it, which is very strange and terrible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 66 past events</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-66-past-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 18:43:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-66-past-events/</guid>
      <description>When the atmosphere began, it seemed a little depressed. Tian could not slowly straighten his body. His face was cloudy and clear, and he could not see what he was thinking.
Xiao Yicai was silent for a while and said, &amp;ldquo;Uncle Tian, I&amp;rsquo;ve been hesitating about this for a long time, but I can&amp;rsquo;t keep it from you.&amp;rdquo;
Tian could not breathe deeply and nodded, &amp;ldquo;I know what you mean, nephew Xiao.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 65 hidden worries</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-65-hidden-worries/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 18:43:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-65-hidden-worries/</guid>
      <description>Zhang Xiaofan looks at the middle-aged scholar in front of him, the &amp;ldquo;ghost king&amp;rdquo; who is suffering from serious problems. His mind is in chaos. These days, from time to time in his heart, he has little doubts about his past beliefs, which are actually rooted in a conversation in the tea stall at the foot of kongsang mountain.
Now, seeing the old man again, this mood is really complicated, which almost makes him forget the situation here and now for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 64 ghost King</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-64-ghost-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 18:43:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-64-ghost-king/</guid>
      <description>Not to mention Zhang Xiaofan&amp;rsquo;s sudden sight of Baguio, he was shocked. A group of people from the demon sect, who were just loud, immediately calmed down when they saw Baguio coming out. They seemed to be very afraid of Baguio. Even the wild dog Taoist who looks like he is not afraid of the earth has no voice at the moment.
For a moment, no one dared to speak to her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 63 demon cult</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-63-demon-cult/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 18:42:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-63-demon-cult/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Ah!&amp;rdquo;
A light shout, Zhang Xiaofan woke up from a dream, panted in the dark, and felt his whole body was wet with cold sweat.
These days, it seems that Zhang Xiaofan suddenly began to dream about his childhood nightmare when he heard the words &amp;ldquo;general wisdom&amp;rdquo; mentioned by FA Xiang. The scene of the village, which was deeply engraved in his heart, rushed to him, as if to swallow him up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 62 the old man</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-62-the-old-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 18:42:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-62-the-old-man/</guid>
      <description>The light from the forest passes through the luxuriant branches and leaves. It is not easy to sprinkle it on Tian and Zhang Xiaofan. Zhang Xiaofan stood in front of Tian not easy and was embarrassed. After a while, he called out in a low voice: &amp;ldquo;Shifu&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
It was not easy for Tian to look at him, but the little apprentice&amp;rsquo;s pale face was suddenly a little bloodstained at the moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 61 wind and rain</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-61-wind-and-rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 18:42:17 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-61-wind-and-rain/</guid>
      <description>Dark night, no moon and stars, no light in the night sky.
Zhang Xiaofan has been kneeling at the entrance of the cave for nearly six hours. Most of the disciples of other sects have gone to sleep. Even the last light in the dazhufeng cave, which was lit at the end of the day, has gradually died out.
In the cave, Tian didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to say a word. Tian linger almost immediately called out, &amp;ldquo;Dad!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 60 violence</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-60-violence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 18:41:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-60-violence/</guid>
      <description>In the match with the wild dog Taoist, an eminent monk of Tianyin temple, who is a man of profound Taoism, used a golden wooden fish magic weapon, and chased the wild dog Taoist as if he were alive in the air. The wild dog Taoist was extremely embarrassed. The strange fanged magic weapon in his hand was no longer shining. I&amp;rsquo;m afraid it was broken by the other side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 59 sadness</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-59-sadness/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 15:58:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-59-sadness/</guid>
      <description>After slapping himself in the face, Zhang Xiaofan stood still and could not help breathing. After a long time, his mood gradually calmed down. Then he shook his head and smiled bitterly. He said to himself, &amp;ldquo;Zhang Xiaofan, you are the old man. A little disciple of Qingyun sect, who is not in the mainstream, dare to question the morality handed down by his ancestors. It&amp;rsquo;s beyond his capacity. Qingyun gate has been passed on for more than two thousand years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 58 going to sea</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-58-going-to-sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 15:57:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-58-going-to-sea/</guid>
      <description>The night is deep, the wind and rain blows between the heaven and the earth. I don&amp;rsquo;t know where the fallen leaves come from. They flutter gently in the wind and rain, passing by with the wind.
Under the turquoise oilcloth umbrella, her clothes flicked gently, with several strands of black hair sticking to her snow-white cheek.
Zhang Xiaofan stood in the same place, but in such a moment, his mind was lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 57 Changhe City</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-57-changhe-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 15:57:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-57-changhe-city/</guid>
      <description>After leaving Xiaochi Town, Zhang Xiaofan, Biyao and Shitou went east, flew for a distance, and then fell to the ground.
Stone first asked Zhang Xiaofan, &amp;ldquo;brother Zhang, where are you going next?&amp;rdquo;
Zhang Xiaofan pondered for a moment and said: &amp;ldquo;since elder martial sister Yanhong of burning incense Valley said that my master was going to Liubo mountain in the East China Sea, I would also meet them. And you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 56 death together</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-56-death-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 15:57:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-56-death-together/</guid>
      <description>The xuanhuojian on her chest gradually calmed down, and all the light slowly disappeared. Zhang Xiaofan suddenly realized that the huge fire dragon that had tumbled under him had disappeared at some time.
Really, I don&amp;rsquo;t know how long it took
He was stunned in the local area, and millions of thoughts were stirring in his mind. However, he still felt that there was a blank in his mind.
Six tail white fox was silent for a long time, then slowly raised his head and said to Zhang Xiaofan, &amp;ldquo;young Lang, come here for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 55 Demon death</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-55-demon-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 15:56:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-55-demon-death/</guid>
      <description>In the fiery underground caves, the heat waves rolled, and the red magma under the platform kept tumbling and bursting from time to time.
Zhang Xiaofan only felt that breathing seemed to be gradually becoming more difficult, and it seemed that the air sucked into his lungs was also hot. In this sense, wherever you take a step, you will step out of Mars. The white six-tailed fox in front is still lying there quietly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 54 Foreign animals</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-54-foreign-animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 15:56:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-54-foreign-animals/</guid>
      <description>It wasn&amp;rsquo;t long after the pursuit of Biyao and others, this dark place just experienced a fierce fight. Just as it was about to recover gradually, I heard the sharp sound of &amp;ldquo;abetting and abetting&amp;rdquo; from the top. A white, a green and two lights shot down. After two shakes, I stopped for a while. There was a man and a woman in the light group. They were Li Xun and Yan Hong under the gate of incendiary valley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 53 Fire Dragon</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-53-fire-dragon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 15:56:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-53-fire-dragon/</guid>
      <description>Countless eyes in the dark are looking at the people in the three halos at the moment. Zhang Xiaofan somehow felt a little hairy in his heart. Looking at the jade and the stone, he found that their faces were not very good-looking either. I think they had never experienced such a scene before.
However, the countless creatures around them did not make any action to attack them. Apart from a few angry tigers and leopards roaring twice, there was basically no movement, just watching in silence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 52 black stone cave</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-52-black-stone-cave/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 15:55:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-52-black-stone-cave/</guid>
      <description>In the field, everyone frowned and saw that the enchanting woman was surrounded. They took out this strange magic weapon. Most of them thought that they were going to be trapped animals. Now they are on guard. But the stone gave a loud drink, and the staff of the breaking Dharma flew in the air, and rushed forward.
Zhang Xiaofan didn&amp;rsquo;t have time to call out &amp;ldquo;be careful&amp;rdquo; at the back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 51 XuanHuo Jian</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-51-xuanhuo-jian/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 15:55:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-51-xuanhuo-jian/</guid>
      <description>In the distance, in the darkness of the woods, the creeping Monday fairy and Xiaohuan are hiding behind the tall trees, in the shadow, looking at all the people in the field.
Xiaohuan frowned and whispered, &amp;ldquo;Grandpa, instead of running for your life, what are you going to do in this dangerous place?&amp;rdquo;
On Monday, the fairy still looked at the scene and whispered, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve heard that there are many treasures in these monster caves, but they can&amp;rsquo;t be used in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 50 the fox</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-50-the-fox/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 15:55:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-50-the-fox/</guid>
      <description>Zhang Xiaofan stayed for a while. He didn&amp;rsquo;t expect to see her again so soon. He didn&amp;rsquo;t recognize her. But he finally lived and died in the blood hole of the dead soul pit. He had a strange feeling in his heart. He had to smile awkwardly and said, &amp;ldquo;how can you come here?&amp;rdquo;
Stone beside see Zhang Xiaofan look some strange, strange way: &amp;ldquo;Xiaofan, who is this person?&amp;rdquo;
Zhang Xiaofan rushed out: &amp;ldquo;she is&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; Suddenly, I realized that if someone knew the identity of Biyao and the relationship between myself and Biyao, I was afraid that the trouble would not be shallow, so I would go back to my mouth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 49 look at the picture</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-49-look-at-the-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 17:17:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-49-look-at-the-picture/</guid>
      <description>It was not easy to shake the dirt under his feet. Zhang Xiaofan turned around and saw that the little girl had come to the old man&amp;rsquo;s side. At the moment, she said something gently to the old man. The old man listened, nodded slightly and smiled.
Zhang Xiaofan blushed, wondering if they were laughing at him there, hesitated for a moment, or walked over and said, &amp;ldquo;old gentleman, what do you mean when you just said I have a fierce face?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 48 town</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-48-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 17:16:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-48-town/</guid>
      <description>Zhang Xiaofan looked deeply at the middle-aged scholar who called himself &amp;ldquo;ten thousand people&amp;rdquo; in front of him, with a bad premonition in his heart, but at the same time, there was another power in his heart, which made him involuntarily ask: &amp;ldquo;please give me some advice.&amp;rdquo;
Ten thousand people took a deep look at him, and said slowly, &amp;ldquo;the black short stick is very powerful. The black light is moist and introverted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 47 scribes</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-47-scribes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 17:16:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-47-scribes/</guid>
      <description>When Zhang Xiaofan woke up, it was already dark. I was afraid that she had slept for at least five or six hours, but Biyao was still awake. She held his clothes tightly with both hands, and looked like a frightened and timid child. No one wanted to get her. She was actually an important thing in the demon cult!
Zhang Xiaofan put his hand under his head and listened to the &amp;ldquo;whirling&amp;rdquo; sound of the trees blowing by the mountain wind in the forest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 46 getting out of trouble</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-46-getting-out-of-trouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 17:15:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-46-getting-out-of-trouble/</guid>
      <description>This past event of Biyao seems to her to be a deep pain. She has been deeply buried in her heart in recent years. Unexpectedly, at this critical moment of life and death, she looks back again. Her mind is agitated. In addition, her food is scarce and her body is weak these days. She has been in a coma for a long time.
Zhang Xiaofan looks at the young devil cult girl who is still clinging to her sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 45 pain</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-45-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 17:15:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-45-pain/</guid>
      <description>After that terrible nonsense, I don&amp;rsquo;t know whether Zhang Xiaofan&amp;rsquo;s body was originally strong, or whether Biyao&amp;rsquo;s comfort had an effect. The high fever that had been going on gradually subsided. Zhang Xiaofan&amp;rsquo;s mind slowly recovered, and people were awake, but the illness was still not light, mostly lying down and resting.
On this day, Baguio wandered in the cave without any business. Finally, she went to the four sentences left by Mrs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 44 Jinling</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-44-jinling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 17:15:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-44-jinling/</guid>
      <description>After a pause, Biyao looked at them carefully again, and saw that the strokes of these four lines were more meticulous, which was quite different from the Tianshu stone carving in the stone room just now. It seemed that it was the work of another person.
But the meaning of this is like the words of an infatuated woman, but how can it appear in the &amp;ldquo;blood hole&amp;rdquo; of this demon sect?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 43 Tianshu</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-43-tianshu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 17:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-43-tianshu/</guid>
      <description>I saw Biyao stand up and take a look at Zhang Xiaofan. He looked elsewhere and stood still. His brow frowned, but he didn&amp;rsquo;t say anything. He said lightly, &amp;ldquo;let&amp;rsquo;s go!&amp;rdquo;
Zhang Xiaofan had some good feelings for the woman when he came in the tunnel, but when he saw these two evil gods, he thought of the difference between the sects and the teachings of his teacher since he was a child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 42 blood dripping hole</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-42-blood-dripping-hole/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 17:14:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-42-blood-dripping-hole/</guid>
      <description>Zhang Xiaofan didn&amp;rsquo;t expect that Biyao had such a big reaction. She was shocked and pointed to the top of the cave and said, &amp;ldquo;there are some red stones&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
Biyao immediately approached and looked at the top of the cave. Sure enough, through the water drop, there were seven and a half palm sized red stones inlaid in the top of the cave. The texture of the stone was the same as the stone beside, except for the color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 41 Jedi</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-41-jedi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 17:14:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-41-jedi/</guid>
      <description>The waves of the merciless sea gradually subsided, but the fear in the hearts of the people did not abate at all. The huge body of the black water black snake is coiled in front of the eyes, standing there like a demon from ancient times.
It seems that the snake head of this behemoth is slightly swinging. I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect to encounter the breath of living people in the lifeless abyss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 40 black water snake</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-40-black-water-snake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 17:14:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-40-black-water-snake/</guid>
      <description>At this time, the young girl also saw Zhang Xiaofan and Lu Xueqi, who were still unconscious beside him. Obviously, she didn&amp;rsquo;t expect that there were still living people under the lifeless abyss. When her face changed, she was surprised.
Then, she saw Zhang Xiaofan&amp;rsquo;s face clearly, stupefied for a while, a trace of surprise flitted across her face, and then she smiled.
&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s true that we don&amp;rsquo;t meet each other in life!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 39 reunion</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-39-reunion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 10:31:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-39-reunion/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Zheng&amp;rdquo;!
It was a crackle in the dark!
Lu Xueqi&amp;rsquo;s face was as cold as frost, and she stood in front of Zhang Xiaofan and pulled out her sword.
Out of the sheath!
Blue light, pure and brilliant light, reflects the dark world.
In an instant, all the dark lights of the spirits lost their luster in front of the blue light. However, the spirits seemed to be fearless and rushed from all directions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 38 abyss</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-38-abyss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 10:30:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-38-abyss/</guid>
      <description>According to the legend, the world was originally dark. In the following forty-eight thousand years, there was Pangu, a giant god, who opened up the world and turned mountains and rivers. In another forty-eight thousand years, Nuwa made people.
According to legend, the first light between heaven and earth is born in the darkest place.
Zhang Xiaofan only felt that his whole body was cold and cold into the bone marrow, as if it was not only his body, but also his heart, and he was going to die.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 37 the abyss of death</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-37-the-abyss-of-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 10:30:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-37-the-abyss-of-death/</guid>
      <description>Zhang Xiaofan watched them fall into trouble, and rushed up at once. In his eyes, the big man turned his head slightly and shot out a red light, rushing to Zhang Xiaofan.
Zhang Xiaofan has no way to go back. Although Qi Hao and Zeng Shushu are in his eyes, they can&amp;rsquo;t do anything when it comes to the end. So he has to sacrifice the fire stick to meet them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 36 strange items</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-36-strange-items/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 10:30:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-36-strange-items/</guid>
      <description>In the distance behind, the roaring and fighting sound was heard all the time, and the light was shining. It was obvious that the three of Qingyun sect were fighting fiercely with other demons in the dark. But here, Zhang Xiaofan suddenly fell into a strange silence.
Zhang Xiaofan was stunned, but the owner of the Yellow flying sword and the gray tusk in the dark witnessed the strange scene with his own eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 35 The Devil</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-35-the-devil/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 10:29:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-35-the-devil/</guid>
      <description>The Dharma phase stood in front of him and whispered a Buddha&amp;rsquo;s name. A moment later, a round bead flashing with Zhuang&amp;rsquo;s serious Mu Jinguang sacrificed from his hand. At first, the light seemed to be attached to the Dharma phase. But with the urging of Dharma phase, the golden light was very prosperous. The golden light rushed to all directions like tide water with the bead as the center. Zhang Xiaofan stood in the same place and almost mistakenly felt the &amp;ldquo;shout&amp;rdquo; in his ear Roaring, the Golden Circle of light had passed by him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 34 ancient caves</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-34-ancient-caves/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 10:17:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-34-ancient-caves/</guid>
      <description>Four people finally came out of the mountain of bat corpses, but they were all in a mess. They were covered with filthy and dark blood. Even the smell was very bad.
All four of them are from Qingyun family. They are always clean, especially Lu Xueqi from xiaozhufeng. At this moment, it&amp;rsquo;s worse than cutting her three knives.
The four of them are busy walking to the distance. At the moment, they just want to be as far away from the disgusting bat corpse as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 33 ten thousand bats</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-33-ten-thousand-bats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 10:16:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-33-ten-thousand-bats/</guid>
      <description>Zhang Xiaofan was stunned for a moment, and recognized that this was the beautiful girl who was arguing about the sleeping fish at dinner. At the moment, he saw that she was still dressed in a suit of water green clothes, and her skin was like snow, beautiful and fairy like under the moonlight.
The young girl put the newly folded flowers on her nose and inhaled deeply. Her face was intoxicated and even more breathtaking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 32 going down the mountain</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-32-going-down-the-mountain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 10:16:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-32-going-down-the-mountain/</guid>
      <description>When Qi Hao and Zeng Shushu saw Zhang Xiaofan here, they all greeted him more or less with a smile. Only Lu Xueqi was still indifferent, but his eyes still glanced at him. There seemed to be some unknown emotions in his eyes, but they disappeared in a flash.
Immortal daoxuan looked at the four people in the hall and said with a smile, &amp;ldquo;let the four of you come here today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 31 the right way</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-31-the-right-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 21:32:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-31-the-right-way/</guid>
      <description>Rhubarb lies on the ground, squinting his eyes, wagging his tail from time to time, while monkey Xiaohui lies on his bed, with bright eyes looking at Zhang Xiaofan, who looks haggard. Zhang Xiaofan glared at it and said, &amp;ldquo;what are you looking at?&amp;rdquo;
Xiaohui naturally won&amp;rsquo;t say anything to Zhang Xiaofan, but &amp;ldquo;squeak&amp;rdquo; twice. Look at its monkey face. The owner is hurt. Not only is he not worried about it, but he looks more like gloating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 30 doubt</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-30-doubt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 01:07:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-30-doubt/</guid>
      <description>Like the passage of the netherworld, a huge whirlpool of dark and invisible bottom hangs upside down in the sky, like the nine hell demons opening their horrible mouths to devour everything in the world. The wind is strong, and the clouds are whirling. Thunder rumbled, electricity darted.
Zhang Xiaofan deceiving himself to fly in, the dark light of the fire staff flickers, which is noticeable under the dark clouds. Lu Xueqi looks at Zhang Xiaofan&amp;rsquo;s figure in the green light, and her jade face is white.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 29 magic</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-29-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 01:06:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-29-magic/</guid>
      <description>And into the night.
Zhang Xiaofan couldn&amp;rsquo;t sleep, and the monkey Xiaohui beside him also opened his eyes, blinked at him. As for other senior brothers, they had already snored a lot, that is rhubarb. Now they are sleeping on the ground.
Moonlight, like water, came in through the window and sprinkled on the ground like frost and snow.
Zhang Xiaofan stealthily gets up, and Xiaohui rushes into his arms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 28 the first four</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-28-the-first-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 01:06:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-28-the-first-four/</guid>
      <description>The next day, when the sun rose as usual, all the people of Dazhu peak came to the square and found that the original eight challenge arenas had been demolished, and the rest were arranged in four directions, Southeast, northwest.
Tian is not easy to walk in front of Su Ru. Zhang Xiaofan&amp;rsquo;s injury seems to get better overnight. He looks flattered when he walks among the people. He looks back and says to Du Bishu in a low voice: &amp;ldquo;six elder martial brother, is the elder martial brother seriously hurt?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 27 persistence</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-27-persistence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 01:06:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-27-persistence/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Good!&amp;rdquo;
Applause thundered, &amp;ldquo;dry&amp;rdquo; position, is another world. Everyone was shouting, obsessed with the two beautiful figures on the stage.
The brilliant light of amber and Zhuling and the endless blue light of Tianya divine sword make it look like a fairyland on earth, which is extremely beautiful. But what is more beautiful is the two young women who are flying in and out of the clothes. From morning till now, an hour has passed, and the two sides still haven&amp;rsquo;t won.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 26 self esteem</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-26-self-esteem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 01:06:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-26-self-esteem/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Xiaofan, didn&amp;rsquo;t you say you wanted to find Xiaohui and that rhubarb dog? How did you bring me to the kitchen?&amp;rdquo; Zeng Shushu follows Zhang Xiaofan and goes into the kitchen to nag.
Zhang Xiaofan looked into the kitchen carefully, only to find that it was much more spacious and bright than dazhufeng&amp;rsquo;s kitchen. He looked at it carefully and said, &amp;ldquo;although I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen them in the morning, I guess it&amp;rsquo;s mostly here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 25 luck</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-25-luck/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 01:05:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-25-luck/</guid>
      <description>For a long time, the old man with white beard was the first to react. He jumped up to the challenge arena and came to Chu Yuhong. After a careful inspection, he found that he was in good condition and showed no signs of poisoning. It seemed that he was severely damaged by the magic weapon of the immortal family and his inner organs were severely shaken.
He frowned, stood up and looked at Zhang Xiaofan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 24 accidents</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-24-accidents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 01:05:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-24-accidents/</guid>
      <description>At once, several people rushed to the challenge arena, helped Fang Chao up, and watched the fairy swords broken into two pieces on the ground. They were all full of anger, and stared at Xueqi, hoping to eat the beautiful woman.
Under the stage, Taoist Cangsong clenched his fists and said coldly, &amp;ldquo;sister Shuiyue, you are really cruel. It&amp;rsquo;s not enough to win, but you have to rely on the magic weapon to produce and destroy other people&amp;rsquo;s immortal swords.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 23 divine sword</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-23-divine-sword/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 01:05:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-23-divine-sword/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Ha ha, younger martial brother Zhang!&amp;rdquo;
Suddenly, Zhang Xiaofan was slapped heavily on the shoulder.
Zhang Xiaofan&amp;rsquo;s whole attention is focused on Tian linger, who is going away. He doesn&amp;rsquo;t notice the situation around him at all. He is shocked. The whole person jumps aside and looks at it in a twinkling of an eye, but it&amp;rsquo;s Zeng Shushu that he just knew in the morning.
I saw Zeng Shushu smiling and relaxed, looking up and down at Zhang Xiaofan, and then my eyes moved to the monkey Xiaohui beside him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 22 Competition</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-22-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 22:49:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-22-competition/</guid>
      <description>The monkey Xiaohui saw the man in front of him staring straight at him, his eyes were weird and furious, he turned up the monkey claws and grabbed the past. The man was caught off guard and almost caught his face. Fortunately, he responded quickly, and he tilted his head back, hiding from it when he could not let it go.
Zhang Xiaofan was taken aback, quickly stopped Xiaohui, and turned to look at the man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 21 The Dark Night</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-21-the-dark-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:59:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-21-the-dark-night/</guid>
      <description>The Seven Veins Meeting Martial Arts is a grand event for the Qingyunmen Yijiazi. There are hundreds more people on the Tongtian Peak, and the accommodation naturally becomes tense. Dazhufeng people want to live the kind of free time on Dazhufeng one by one, that is delusion. Except for Tian Ling&amp;rsquo;er who lived in Xiaozhufeng&amp;rsquo;s daughters, Dazhufeng started with Song Daren. There were seven male disciples, all packed in a room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 20 magic trace</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-20-magic-trace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:55:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-20-magic-trace/</guid>
      <description>All of a sudden, everyone&amp;rsquo;s eyes fell on this humble Dazhufeng disciple. Tian Zhuan and Su Ru looked at each other, Su Ru smiled slightly and nodded.
Da Zhufeng smiled all over, and all came around. Lv Daxin repeatedly shot Zhang Xiaofan&amp;rsquo;s shoulders and smiled: &amp;ldquo;Stinky boy, I can&amp;rsquo;t see your good luck!&amp;rdquo;
Zhang Xiaofan scratched his head and threw his tongue out, and his heart has changed from a surprise to a surprise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 19 Lottery</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-19-lottery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:54:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-19-lottery/</guid>
      <description>I saw at the edge of the Bishuitan, the water beast that had been sleeping fast, suddenly woke up, turned around fiercely, his huge eyes showed endless fierce light, the hair roots on his back were raised, and a blood basin was opened. Big mouth, showing two long sharp fangs, actually put on an attacking gesture. And its goal is the disciples of Qingyunmen standing on the steps.
This water unicorn is a wilderness spirit, an ancient beast, this power, I suddenly saw the change of wind and clouds, the blue sky had darkened in an instant, and as it took the first step to the steps, it was originally calm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 18 meeting</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-18-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:53:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-18-meeting/</guid>
      <description>Song Daren froze for a moment, the sound lingered in his ears, just like fairy music. After a while, he woke up like a dream and turned around like lightning, only to see five or six female disciples standing behind him. In the Qingyun Gate, under the door of Xiaozhufeng who always only accepted female disciples.
The first to face them was a beautiful woman with a melon seed face, her hair like clouds, her skin like snow, and a faint smile on the corner of her mouth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 17 going to the meeting</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-17-going-to-the-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:52:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-17-going-to-the-meeting/</guid>
      <description>This morning, everyone on the Dazhu Peak of Qingyunmen was in high spirits, especially the disciples, all smiling, although there was no lack of tension, but most of them were submerged in excitement.
Among all the people, only the master brother Song Daren and the second son Wu Dayi, the third son Zheng Dali, the fourth elder He Dazhi, and the old Wu Lu Daxin and the sixth elder Du Bishu were all not easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 16 drive</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-16-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:50:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-16-drive/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Wang Wang Wang&amp;rdquo;!
&amp;ldquo;Squeak&amp;rdquo;!
&amp;hellip;
The bark of the dog is intertwined with the scream of the monkey, echoing on the Dazhu Peak of Qingyun Mountain, breaking the tranquility here. Holding the black burning stick in his hand, Zhang Xiaofan rushed out of the kitchen door and was furious: &amp;ldquo;Dead dog! Dead monkey! Don&amp;rsquo;t run!
The monkey jumped on the back of the big yellow dog with a swish, and the already-running rhubarb spread out on all four feet and ran, Zhang Xiaofan couldn&amp;rsquo;t catch up, watching Xiao gray making a face, and put a fragrant meat bone on the rhubarb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 15 Private Biography</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-15-private-biography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:49:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-15-private-biography/</guid>
      <description>This beautiful woman is naturally Tian Ling&amp;rsquo;er. When she saw that Zhang Xiaofan was injured, she was worried and ran quietly to visit. Unexpectedly, her mother was here too, so she hid outside the door until Su Ru left.
At this time she looked at Zhang Xiaofan as if froze, could not help but sigh: &amp;ldquo;What are you doing standing there?&amp;rdquo;
Zhang Xiaofan woke up with a red face, and was just trying to find an excuse to distinguish, but he saw Tian Ling&amp;rsquo;er lower his head.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 14 magic</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-14-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:42:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-14-magic/</guid>
      <description>Tian is not easy to stand up, looking at Lin Jingyu in Shangbu, his face is extremely ugly, and he said coldly in his mouth, &amp;ldquo;Good ability! Good murderous!&amp;rdquo;
Qi Hao whispered to Lin Jingyu: &amp;ldquo;Brother, please stay with me.&amp;rdquo;
Lin Jingyu was young and angry, his brows were tight, and he took a step, but said to Zhang Xiaofan who was standing on the side: &amp;ldquo;Xiaofan, I was just wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 13 Wizards</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-13-wizards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:41:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-13-wizards/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Longshoufeng Cangsong real disciples Qi Hao and Lin Jingyu met with Uncle Tian and Uncle Su.&amp;rdquo;
In the Shoujing Hall, Tian is not easy to sit with Su Ru, and the rest of the disciples are beside him. Two white men in the field, namely Lin Jingyu and another handsome young man named Qi Hao, are facing Tian Tian not easy to salute. Zhang Xiaofan stood at the end of the disciple list and looked at Lin Jingyu in the field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 12 Reunion</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-12-reunion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:39:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-12-reunion/</guid>
      <description>After returning from Yougu, another half a month later, Zhang Xiaofan had been in Qingyunmen for three full years, and also ended his bamboo cutting career, but at the end of the time he handed over the results, even blushing for himself.
Because of that inexplicable trip to the valley, Zhang Xiaofan often felt dizzy, lack of energy and lack of blood in the next half month, and the whole person was particularly tired.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 11 Changes</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-11-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:01:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-11-changes/</guid>
      <description>Zhang Xiaofan looked at the bead for a long while, and his breathing gradually calmed down, but apart from seeing the difference in color brightness, the others did not see anything, and had to put it back on his chest again. He looked at Tian Ling&amp;rsquo;er next to him and saw that she was still unconscious, but her face was getting bloodied, and the situation was much better.
He picked up the amber Zhu Ling and took a closer look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 10 The Valley</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-10-the-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:59:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-10-the-valley/</guid>
      <description>Zhang Xiaofan came up to the mountain and came to the familiar bamboo forest, but he saw the mountains full of verdant mountains, cascading layers, mountain breezes passing by, the bamboo sea undulating, like the waves of the sea, extremely magnificent, and his heart suddenly widened.
He took a deep breath of fresh air in the mountains, moved around, and walked into the bamboo forest with a hatchet. The place he went to at this time was different from when he came three years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 9 Buddha and Tao</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-9-buddha-and-tao/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:57:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-9-buddha-and-tao/</guid>
      <description>Song Daren was a teacher at first. When he saw Zhang Xiaofan holding his cheek on his face, he was fascinated by it, and he could not help but talk about it and talk happily:
The process of Taiji Xuanqing Dao is easy and difficult. Most people in the first level of Yuqingjing can be cultivated in the first year, but from then on, the difficult and difficult places will show up, and the ordinary people on the second level will have to practice five.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 8 Impart</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-8-impart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:56:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-8-impart/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Zhang Xiaofan!&amp;rdquo;
A loud shout, sweet voice, but deafening. Zhang Xiaofan awakened from the dream, opened his eyes, and suddenly saw a big mouth, two rows of fangs, lying in front of his eyes, screamed in shock: &amp;ldquo;Ah!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Giggle&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; A laugh came from behind.
Zhang Xiaofan finally settled down, only to see that there was a big yellow dog in front of him, half of them came to the height, a bright yellow hair, lying on his bed, and behind the yellow dog, Tian Linger was alone Red dress, tight-fitting dress, where he smiled and bent down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 7 Initial</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-7-initial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:55:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-7-initial/</guid>
      <description>At supper, it was dark.
On the Dazhu Peak, Houshan is a whole piece of bamboo forest. The housing of all people is in Qianfeng. The biggest and most important thing is the main hall guarding the quiet hall. Tian Yiji and his three daughters live in the back hall. Next to the Shoujing Hall is the small corridor where all the disciples live, but because there are too few people, there are more houses than everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 6 Apprenticeship</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-6-apprenticeship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:54:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-6-apprenticeship/</guid>
      <description>Zhang Xiaofan woke up wandering for a long while, slowly sat up, and the past was like a tide, and his heart surged for a moment.
A nightmare!
&amp;ldquo;You wake up, that&amp;rsquo;s fine.&amp;rdquo; A voice came from the door and walked in.
Zhang Xiaofan looked up and recognized Song Daren, who had been seen on Tongtian Peak at the time, tall and rude. In his current state of mind, somehow, seeing this acquaintance is somewhat kind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 5 Getting Started</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-5-getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:53:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-5-getting-started/</guid>
      <description>At this time, everyone in the hall was talking, as if talking about something. The young priest who led Zhang Xiaofan and Lin Jingyu came to the front of the door in a robe, and said in courtesy: &amp;ldquo;Master, fellow uncles, disciples often arrows, ordered two young&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
He didn&amp;rsquo;t finish his words. Suddenly above the sacred and solemn hall, a shouting cry broke out, interrupting him: &amp;ldquo;Ghost, evil spirit! Ghost!&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 4 Shock Change</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-4-shock-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:52:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-4-shock-change/</guid>
      <description>In the early morning, the rain finally stopped.
The water droplets on the tree were crystal clear, slipped quietly from the edge of the leaf, and fell down. Because of the wind, it crossed the beautiful arc in the air and hit Zhang Xiaofan&amp;rsquo;s face.
The cold coolness awakened Zhang Xiaofan from his dream. He opened his eyes and subconsciously shouted, &amp;ldquo;Master&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; But there is no one in Shiye, only Lin Jingyu is lying beside him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 3 Vision</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-3-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:51:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-3-vision/</guid>
      <description>In Zhang Xiaofan&amp;rsquo;s eyes, the clouds in the sky, whether it is white clouds or dark clouds, have never seen as close to the ground as the black clouds tonight, the thunder has never been so deafening, the lightning has never been so dazzling, almost making it difficult for him Look straight.
It seems that this day is about to fall.
He stood there staring blankly, watching the men in black and the old monk in the grass temple glaring at each other as a way of fighting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 2 Maze</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-2-maze/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:50:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-2-maze/</guid>
      <description>The old monk didn&amp;rsquo;t answer, only looked at the two children with his eyes, but couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but looked at Lin Jingyu a few more times, and said, &amp;ldquo;Good qualification, but why is the temperament so extreme?&amp;rdquo;
At this time Zhang Xiaofan took a step and said, &amp;ldquo;Hey, who are you, how have you never seen you?&amp;rdquo;
Cao Miao Village is near Qingyun Gate, where Taoism is revered, and Buddhist disciples are extremely rare, so Zhang Xiaofan has this question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 1 Qingyun</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-1-qingyun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:49:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-1-qingyun/</guid>
      <description>The Qingyun Mountains are towering, the tigers are in the Central Plains, there is a big river &amp;ldquo;Hongchuan&amp;rdquo; in the mountain shade, and &amp;ldquo;Heyang City&amp;rdquo; in the important town of Shanyang. The geographical position is very important.
There are hundreds of miles of mountains in Qingyun Mountain, and the peaks are ups and downs, with seven peaks at the highest, towering into the clouds. On weekdays, I can see white clouds surrounding the mountainside, and I don’t know the true beauty of the top.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:11:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/about/</guid>
      <description>A Chinese Internet Literature Fan</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>