<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MyNovel - A Chinese Internet Literature World</title>
    <link>http://www.mynovel.top/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MyNovel - A Chinese Internet Literature World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 10:31:05 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.mynovel.top/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 39 reunion</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-39-reunion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 10:31:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-39-reunion/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Zheng&amp;rdquo;!
It was a crackle in the dark!
Lu Xueqi&amp;rsquo;s face was as cold as frost, and she stood in front of Zhang Xiaofan and pulled out her sword.
Out of the sheath!
Blue light, pure and brilliant light, reflects the dark world.
In an instant, all the dark lights of the spirits lost their luster in front of the blue light. However, the spirits seemed to be fearless and rushed from all directions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 38 abyss</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-38-abyss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 10:30:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-38-abyss/</guid>
      <description>According to the legend, the world was originally dark. In the following forty-eight thousand years, there was Pangu, a giant god, who opened up the world and turned mountains and rivers. In another forty-eight thousand years, Nuwa made people.
According to legend, the first light between heaven and earth is born in the darkest place.
Zhang Xiaofan only felt that his whole body was cold and cold into the bone marrow, as if it was not only his body, but also his heart, and he was going to die.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 37 the abyss of death</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-37-the-abyss-of-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 10:30:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-37-the-abyss-of-death/</guid>
      <description>Zhang Xiaofan watched them fall into trouble, and rushed up at once. In his eyes, the big man turned his head slightly and shot out a red light, rushing to Zhang Xiaofan.
Zhang Xiaofan has no way to go back. Although Qi Hao and Zeng Shushu are in his eyes, they can&amp;rsquo;t do anything when it comes to the end. So he has to sacrifice the fire stick to meet them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 36 strange items</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-36-strange-items/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 10:30:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-36-strange-items/</guid>
      <description>In the distance behind, the roaring and fighting sound was heard all the time, and the light was shining. It was obvious that the three of Qingyun sect were fighting fiercely with other demons in the dark. But here, Zhang Xiaofan suddenly fell into a strange silence.
Zhang Xiaofan was stunned, but the owner of the Yellow flying sword and the gray tusk in the dark witnessed the strange scene with his own eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 35 The Devil</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-35-the-devil/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 10:29:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-35-the-devil/</guid>
      <description>The Dharma phase stood in front of him and whispered a Buddha&amp;rsquo;s name. A moment later, a round bead flashing with Zhuang&amp;rsquo;s serious Mu Jinguang sacrificed from his hand. At first, the light seemed to be attached to the Dharma phase. But with the urging of Dharma phase, the golden light was very prosperous. The golden light rushed to all directions like tide water with the bead as the center. Zhang Xiaofan stood in the same place and almost mistakenly felt the &amp;ldquo;shout&amp;rdquo; in his ear Roaring, the Golden Circle of light had passed by him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 34 ancient caves</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-34-ancient-caves/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 10:17:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-34-ancient-caves/</guid>
      <description>Four people finally came out of the mountain of bat corpses, but they were all in a mess. They were covered with filthy and dark blood. Even the smell was very bad.
All four of them are from Qingyun family. They are always clean, especially Lu Xueqi from xiaozhufeng. At this moment, it&amp;rsquo;s worse than cutting her three knives.
The four of them are busy walking to the distance. At the moment, they just want to be as far away from the disgusting bat corpse as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 33 ten thousand bats</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-33-ten-thousand-bats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 10:16:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-33-ten-thousand-bats/</guid>
      <description>Zhang Xiaofan was stunned for a moment, and recognized that this was the beautiful girl who was arguing about the sleeping fish at dinner. At the moment, he saw that she was still dressed in a suit of water green clothes, and her skin was like snow, beautiful and fairy like under the moonlight.
The young girl put the newly folded flowers on her nose and inhaled deeply. Her face was intoxicated and even more breathtaking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 32 going down the mountain</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-32-going-down-the-mountain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 10:16:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-32-going-down-the-mountain/</guid>
      <description>When Qi Hao and Zeng Shushu saw Zhang Xiaofan here, they all greeted him more or less with a smile. Only Lu Xueqi was still indifferent, but his eyes still glanced at him. There seemed to be some unknown emotions in his eyes, but they disappeared in a flash.
Immortal daoxuan looked at the four people in the hall and said with a smile, &amp;ldquo;let the four of you come here today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 31 the right way</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-31-the-right-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 21:32:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-31-the-right-way/</guid>
      <description>Rhubarb lies on the ground, squinting his eyes, wagging his tail from time to time, while monkey Xiaohui lies on his bed, with bright eyes looking at Zhang Xiaofan, who looks haggard. Zhang Xiaofan glared at it and said, &amp;ldquo;what are you looking at?&amp;rdquo;
Xiaohui naturally won&amp;rsquo;t say anything to Zhang Xiaofan, but &amp;ldquo;squeak&amp;rdquo; twice. Look at its monkey face. The owner is hurt. Not only is he not worried about it, but he looks more like gloating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 30 doubt</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-30-doubt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 01:07:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-30-doubt/</guid>
      <description>Like the passage of the netherworld, a huge whirlpool of dark and invisible bottom hangs upside down in the sky, like the nine hell demons opening their horrible mouths to devour everything in the world. The wind is strong, and the clouds are whirling. Thunder rumbled, electricity darted.
Zhang Xiaofan deceiving himself to fly in, the dark light of the fire staff flickers, which is noticeable under the dark clouds. Lu Xueqi looks at Zhang Xiaofan&amp;rsquo;s figure in the green light, and her jade face is white.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 29 magic</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-29-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 01:06:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-29-magic/</guid>
      <description>And into the night.
Zhang Xiaofan couldn&amp;rsquo;t sleep, and the monkey Xiaohui beside him also opened his eyes, blinked at him. As for other senior brothers, they had already snored a lot, that is rhubarb. Now they are sleeping on the ground.
Moonlight, like water, came in through the window and sprinkled on the ground like frost and snow.
Zhang Xiaofan stealthily gets up, and Xiaohui rushes into his arms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 28 the first four</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-28-the-first-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 01:06:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-28-the-first-four/</guid>
      <description>The next day, when the sun rose as usual, all the people of Dazhu peak came to the square and found that the original eight challenge arenas had been demolished, and the rest were arranged in four directions, Southeast, northwest.
Tian is not easy to walk in front of Su Ru. Zhang Xiaofan&amp;rsquo;s injury seems to get better overnight. He looks flattered when he walks among the people. He looks back and says to Du Bishu in a low voice: &amp;ldquo;six elder martial brother, is the elder martial brother seriously hurt?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 27 persistence</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-27-persistence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 01:06:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-27-persistence/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Good!&amp;rdquo;
Applause thundered, &amp;ldquo;dry&amp;rdquo; position, is another world. Everyone was shouting, obsessed with the two beautiful figures on the stage.
The brilliant light of amber and Zhuling and the endless blue light of Tianya divine sword make it look like a fairyland on earth, which is extremely beautiful. But what is more beautiful is the two young women who are flying in and out of the clothes. From morning till now, an hour has passed, and the two sides still haven&amp;rsquo;t won.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 26 self esteem</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-26-self-esteem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 01:06:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-26-self-esteem/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Xiaofan, didn&amp;rsquo;t you say you wanted to find Xiaohui and that rhubarb dog? How did you bring me to the kitchen?&amp;rdquo; Zeng Shushu follows Zhang Xiaofan and goes into the kitchen to nag.
Zhang Xiaofan looked into the kitchen carefully, only to find that it was much more spacious and bright than dazhufeng&amp;rsquo;s kitchen. He looked at it carefully and said, &amp;ldquo;although I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen them in the morning, I guess it&amp;rsquo;s mostly here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 25 luck</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-25-luck/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 01:05:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-25-luck/</guid>
      <description>For a long time, the old man with white beard was the first to react. He jumped up to the challenge arena and came to Chu Yuhong. After a careful inspection, he found that he was in good condition and showed no signs of poisoning. It seemed that he was severely damaged by the magic weapon of the immortal family and his inner organs were severely shaken.
He frowned, stood up and looked at Zhang Xiaofan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 24 accidents</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-24-accidents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 01:05:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-24-accidents/</guid>
      <description>At once, several people rushed to the challenge arena, helped Fang Chao up, and watched the fairy swords broken into two pieces on the ground. They were all full of anger, and stared at Xueqi, hoping to eat the beautiful woman.
Under the stage, Taoist Cangsong clenched his fists and said coldly, &amp;ldquo;sister Shuiyue, you are really cruel. It&amp;rsquo;s not enough to win, but you have to rely on the magic weapon to produce and destroy other people&amp;rsquo;s immortal swords.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 23 divine sword</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-23-divine-sword/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 01:05:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-23-divine-sword/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Ha ha, younger martial brother Zhang!&amp;rdquo;
Suddenly, Zhang Xiaofan was slapped heavily on the shoulder.
Zhang Xiaofan&amp;rsquo;s whole attention is focused on Tian linger, who is going away. He doesn&amp;rsquo;t notice the situation around him at all. He is shocked. The whole person jumps aside and looks at it in a twinkling of an eye, but it&amp;rsquo;s Zeng Shushu that he just knew in the morning.
I saw Zeng Shushu smiling and relaxed, looking up and down at Zhang Xiaofan, and then my eyes moved to the monkey Xiaohui beside him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 22 Competition</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-22-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 22:49:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-22-competition/</guid>
      <description>The monkey Xiaohui saw the man in front of him staring straight at him, his eyes were weird and furious, he turned up the monkey claws and grabbed the past. The man was caught off guard and almost caught his face. Fortunately, he responded quickly, and he tilted his head back, hiding from it when he could not let it go.
Zhang Xiaofan was taken aback, quickly stopped Xiaohui, and turned to look at the man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 21 The Dark Night</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-21-the-dark-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:59:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-21-the-dark-night/</guid>
      <description>The Seven Veins Meeting Martial Arts is a grand event for the Qingyunmen Yijiazi. There are hundreds more people on the Tongtian Peak, and the accommodation naturally becomes tense. Dazhufeng people want to live the kind of free time on Dazhufeng one by one, that is delusion. Except for Tian Ling&amp;rsquo;er who lived in Xiaozhufeng&amp;rsquo;s daughters, Dazhufeng started with Song Daren. There were seven male disciples, all packed in a room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 20 magic trace</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-20-magic-trace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:55:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-20-magic-trace/</guid>
      <description>All of a sudden, everyone&amp;rsquo;s eyes fell on this humble Dazhufeng disciple. Tian Zhuan and Su Ru looked at each other, Su Ru smiled slightly and nodded.
Da Zhufeng smiled all over, and all came around. Lv Daxin repeatedly shot Zhang Xiaofan&amp;rsquo;s shoulders and smiled: &amp;ldquo;Stinky boy, I can&amp;rsquo;t see your good luck!&amp;rdquo;
Zhang Xiaofan scratched his head and threw his tongue out, and his heart has changed from a surprise to a surprise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 19 Lottery</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-19-lottery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:54:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-19-lottery/</guid>
      <description>I saw at the edge of the Bishuitan, the water beast that had been sleeping fast, suddenly woke up, turned around fiercely, his huge eyes showed endless fierce light, the hair roots on his back were raised, and a blood basin was opened. Big mouth, showing two long sharp fangs, actually put on an attacking gesture. And its goal is the disciples of Qingyunmen standing on the steps.
This water unicorn is a wilderness spirit, an ancient beast, this power, I suddenly saw the change of wind and clouds, the blue sky had darkened in an instant, and as it took the first step to the steps, it was originally calm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 18 meeting</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-18-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:53:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-18-meeting/</guid>
      <description>Song Daren froze for a moment, the sound lingered in his ears, just like fairy music. After a while, he woke up like a dream and turned around like lightning, only to see five or six female disciples standing behind him. In the Qingyun Gate, under the door of Xiaozhufeng who always only accepted female disciples.
The first to face them was a beautiful woman with a melon seed face, her hair like clouds, her skin like snow, and a faint smile on the corner of her mouth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 17 going to the meeting</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-17-going-to-the-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:52:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-17-going-to-the-meeting/</guid>
      <description>This morning, everyone on the Dazhu Peak of Qingyunmen was in high spirits, especially the disciples, all smiling, although there was no lack of tension, but most of them were submerged in excitement.
Among all the people, only the master brother Song Daren and the second son Wu Dayi, the third son Zheng Dali, the fourth elder He Dazhi, and the old Wu Lu Daxin and the sixth elder Du Bishu were all not easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 16 drive</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-16-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:50:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-16-drive/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Wang Wang Wang&amp;rdquo;!
&amp;ldquo;Squeak&amp;rdquo;!
&amp;hellip;
The bark of the dog is intertwined with the scream of the monkey, echoing on the Dazhu Peak of Qingyun Mountain, breaking the tranquility here. Holding the black burning stick in his hand, Zhang Xiaofan rushed out of the kitchen door and was furious: &amp;ldquo;Dead dog! Dead monkey! Don&amp;rsquo;t run!
The monkey jumped on the back of the big yellow dog with a swish, and the already-running rhubarb spread out on all four feet and ran, Zhang Xiaofan couldn&amp;rsquo;t catch up, watching Xiao gray making a face, and put a fragrant meat bone on the rhubarb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 15 Private Biography</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-15-private-biography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:49:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-15-private-biography/</guid>
      <description>This beautiful woman is naturally Tian Ling&amp;rsquo;er. When she saw that Zhang Xiaofan was injured, she was worried and ran quietly to visit. Unexpectedly, her mother was here too, so she hid outside the door until Su Ru left.
At this time she looked at Zhang Xiaofan as if froze, could not help but sigh: &amp;ldquo;What are you doing standing there?&amp;rdquo;
Zhang Xiaofan woke up with a red face, and was just trying to find an excuse to distinguish, but he saw Tian Ling&amp;rsquo;er lower his head.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 14 magic</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-14-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:42:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-14-magic/</guid>
      <description>Tian is not easy to stand up, looking at Lin Jingyu in Shangbu, his face is extremely ugly, and he said coldly in his mouth, &amp;ldquo;Good ability! Good murderous!&amp;rdquo;
Qi Hao whispered to Lin Jingyu: &amp;ldquo;Brother, please stay with me.&amp;rdquo;
Lin Jingyu was young and angry, his brows were tight, and he took a step, but said to Zhang Xiaofan who was standing on the side: &amp;ldquo;Xiaofan, I was just wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 13 Wizards</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-13-wizards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:41:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-13-wizards/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Longshoufeng Cangsong real disciples Qi Hao and Lin Jingyu met with Uncle Tian and Uncle Su.&amp;rdquo;
In the Shoujing Hall, Tian is not easy to sit with Su Ru, and the rest of the disciples are beside him. Two white men in the field, namely Lin Jingyu and another handsome young man named Qi Hao, are facing Tian Tian not easy to salute. Zhang Xiaofan stood at the end of the disciple list and looked at Lin Jingyu in the field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 12 Reunion</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-12-reunion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:39:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-12-reunion/</guid>
      <description>After returning from Yougu, another half a month later, Zhang Xiaofan had been in Qingyunmen for three full years, and also ended his bamboo cutting career, but at the end of the time he handed over the results, even blushing for himself.
Because of that inexplicable trip to the valley, Zhang Xiaofan often felt dizzy, lack of energy and lack of blood in the next half month, and the whole person was particularly tired.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 11 Changes</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-11-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 21:01:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-11-changes/</guid>
      <description>Zhang Xiaofan looked at the bead for a long while, and his breathing gradually calmed down, but apart from seeing the difference in color brightness, the others did not see anything, and had to put it back on his chest again. He looked at Tian Ling&amp;rsquo;er next to him and saw that she was still unconscious, but her face was getting bloodied, and the situation was much better.
He picked up the amber Zhu Ling and took a closer look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 10 The Valley</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-10-the-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:59:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-10-the-valley/</guid>
      <description>Zhang Xiaofan came up to the mountain and came to the familiar bamboo forest, but he saw the mountains full of verdant mountains, cascading layers, mountain breezes passing by, the bamboo sea undulating, like the waves of the sea, extremely magnificent, and his heart suddenly widened.
He took a deep breath of fresh air in the mountains, moved around, and walked into the bamboo forest with a hatchet. The place he went to at this time was different from when he came three years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 9 Buddha and Tao</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-9-buddha-and-tao/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:57:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-9-buddha-and-tao/</guid>
      <description>Song Daren was a teacher at first. When he saw Zhang Xiaofan holding his cheek on his face, he was fascinated by it, and he could not help but talk about it and talk happily:
The process of Taiji Xuanqing Dao is easy and difficult. Most people in the first level of Yuqingjing can be cultivated in the first year, but from then on, the difficult and difficult places will show up, and the ordinary people on the second level will have to practice five.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 8 Impart</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-8-impart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:56:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-8-impart/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Zhang Xiaofan!&amp;rdquo;
A loud shout, sweet voice, but deafening. Zhang Xiaofan awakened from the dream, opened his eyes, and suddenly saw a big mouth, two rows of fangs, lying in front of his eyes, screamed in shock: &amp;ldquo;Ah!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Giggle&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; A laugh came from behind.
Zhang Xiaofan finally settled down, only to see that there was a big yellow dog in front of him, half of them came to the height, a bright yellow hair, lying on his bed, and behind the yellow dog, Tian Linger was alone Red dress, tight-fitting dress, where he smiled and bent down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 7 Initial</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-7-initial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:55:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-7-initial/</guid>
      <description>At supper, it was dark.
On the Dazhu Peak, Houshan is a whole piece of bamboo forest. The housing of all people is in Qianfeng. The biggest and most important thing is the main hall guarding the quiet hall. Tian Yiji and his three daughters live in the back hall. Next to the Shoujing Hall is the small corridor where all the disciples live, but because there are too few people, there are more houses than everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 6 Apprenticeship</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-6-apprenticeship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:54:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-6-apprenticeship/</guid>
      <description>Zhang Xiaofan woke up wandering for a long while, slowly sat up, and the past was like a tide, and his heart surged for a moment.
A nightmare!
&amp;ldquo;You wake up, that&amp;rsquo;s fine.&amp;rdquo; A voice came from the door and walked in.
Zhang Xiaofan looked up and recognized Song Daren, who had been seen on Tongtian Peak at the time, tall and rude. In his current state of mind, somehow, seeing this acquaintance is somewhat kind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 5 Getting Started</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-5-getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:53:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-5-getting-started/</guid>
      <description>At this time, everyone in the hall was talking, as if talking about something. The young priest who led Zhang Xiaofan and Lin Jingyu came to the front of the door in a robe, and said in courtesy: &amp;ldquo;Master, fellow uncles, disciples often arrows, ordered two young&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
He didn&amp;rsquo;t finish his words. Suddenly above the sacred and solemn hall, a shouting cry broke out, interrupting him: &amp;ldquo;Ghost, evil spirit! Ghost!&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 4 Shock Change</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-4-shock-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:52:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-4-shock-change/</guid>
      <description>In the early morning, the rain finally stopped.
The water droplets on the tree were crystal clear, slipped quietly from the edge of the leaf, and fell down. Because of the wind, it crossed the beautiful arc in the air and hit Zhang Xiaofan&amp;rsquo;s face.
The cold coolness awakened Zhang Xiaofan from his dream. He opened his eyes and subconsciously shouted, &amp;ldquo;Master&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; But there is no one in Shiye, only Lin Jingyu is lying beside him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 3 Vision</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-3-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:51:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-3-vision/</guid>
      <description>In Zhang Xiaofan&amp;rsquo;s eyes, the clouds in the sky, whether it is white clouds or dark clouds, have never seen as close to the ground as the black clouds tonight, the thunder has never been so deafening, the lightning has never been so dazzling, almost making it difficult for him Look straight.
It seems that this day is about to fall.
He stood there staring blankly, watching the men in black and the old monk in the grass temple glaring at each other as a way of fighting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 2 Maze</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-2-maze/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:50:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-2-maze/</guid>
      <description>The old monk didn&amp;rsquo;t answer, only looked at the two children with his eyes, but couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but looked at Lin Jingyu a few more times, and said, &amp;ldquo;Good qualification, but why is the temperament so extreme?&amp;rdquo;
At this time Zhang Xiaofan took a step and said, &amp;ldquo;Hey, who are you, how have you never seen you?&amp;rdquo;
Cao Miao Village is near Qingyun Gate, where Taoism is revered, and Buddhist disciples are extremely rare, so Zhang Xiaofan has this question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jade dynasty--Chapter 1 Qingyun</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-1-qingyun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:49:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/post/jade-dynasty-chapter-1-qingyun/</guid>
      <description>The Qingyun Mountains are towering, the tigers are in the Central Plains, there is a big river &amp;ldquo;Hongchuan&amp;rdquo; in the mountain shade, and &amp;ldquo;Heyang City&amp;rdquo; in the important town of Shanyang. The geographical position is very important.
There are hundreds of miles of mountains in Qingyun Mountain, and the peaks are ups and downs, with seven peaks at the highest, towering into the clouds. On weekdays, I can see white clouds surrounding the mountainside, and I don’t know the true beauty of the top.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.mynovel.top/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:11:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mynovel.top/about/</guid>
      <description>A Chinese Internet Literature Fan</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>